Chapter 1212: Primal Universe Spirit Root

As the Cultivator died from the arrow through his throat, his face had an expression of utter disbelief. His face turned dark before he finally blacked out.

Before the Cultivator’s body fell to the ground, Zhao Hai quickly let out a clump of black gas that wrapped the Cultivator’s body. Then when the black gas vanished, the Cultivator was nowhere in sight. He had already become an Undead in Zhao Hai’s army.

Seeing that Zhao Hai had killed the Cultivator, Xiong Li and the others cheered. But at this moment, a person was suddenly seen flying in the distance. This person wasn’t far away, and he was also flying at full speed.

Seeing this situation, Xiong Li and the others began to turn anxious. They quickly put up their guard, afraid that the person was an enemy.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t seem to be nervous. He said, “There’s no need to be afraid. It’s a team leader.” Just as his voice was heard, a person wearing Mage Robes appeared in front of them.

This person didn’t waste any time as he said, “Quickly follow me. You just killed a core disciple of the Seamount Faction. He’s one of the participants in the Six Realm Beginner Competition. When the Seamount Faction knew about this situation, they quickly sent over reinforcements.” It was clear that this team leader took a route that was different than the Seamount Faction’s.

As soon as they heard this, Zhao Hai and the others stared for a moment before nodding and then following behind the team leader.

A short while after Zhao Hai and the others left, a group of people arrived at the scene of battle. The leader of the group was the head of the Seamount Faction. He glanced around and said, “I can sense the breath of the kid here. Him and another person fought here. It seems like his murderous scheme has been overturned.”

Then an Elder at his side said, “This is impossible. The last time I saw the kid, he was with those bumpkins from the Machine Field. They killed that kid? How is that possible?”

The head sighed and said, “It looks like we underestimated the strength of the Machine Field. Machine Field’s Zhao Hai can block Li Chuche’s three swords, so he’s quite strong. Compared to Li Chuchen, our candidate is still far off. Four years of our effort has been wasted.”

The Elder coldly snorted and said, “Sect Leader, we should immediately look for the Machine Field’s people and have them hand over Zhao Hai. If they don’t, we can just clean them up.”

The Sect Leader shook his head and said, “It’s useless. The Machine Field would never hand someone over. They didn’t even take us seriously during the last fight. They don’t fear the Seamount Faction, they were just on guard against the huge sects behind us. Now that the people from the other sects had left, the Machine Field’s people will certainly deal with us if we go there. You think those great sects would support the Seamount Faction if the Machine Field attacks? That’s impossible. Those great sects are ruthless. They wouldn’t care about a small sect like ours.”

The Elder was silent. He knew that the Sect Leader was telling the truth. In the eyes of those huge sects, the Seamount Faction was just a small sect controlling a small city. They were simply ants in their eyes. Even if these sects look at the Seamount Faction, it was only times where they would issue orders. And even then, those sects might not remember their names.

The leader sighed and said, “People from the Machine Field can be complete lunatics. Don’t think that the Machine Field are pushovers since they could be easily overwhelmed by the sects. You should take into account how much effort it needs to deal with them. If the Machine Field was truly provoked, then their assassins would be a headache to deal with. Compared to the Machine Field, the Seamount Faction is still lacking. Also, we don’t want to take part in these troubled waters. Let’s give up on the Six Realm Beginner Competition this time. At worst, we will have no benefits for five years. If we provoked the Machine Field, then we wouldn’t even survive for five years.” The elders sighed and said, “The Machine Field will now be attaching more importance to Zhao Hai. If we dealt with him, then the Machine Field would certainly go all out against us.”

The leader nodded, then he said, “Let’s head back. We’re just unlucky this time. Now I want to see how far this Zhao Hai can go in the competition.”

At this time, Zhao Hai and the others had already returned to their courtyard. Just as they arrived, Ma Rulong immediately found them. Upon seeing Zhao Hai and the others return, Ma Rulong couldn’t help but let out a sigh of relief. Then his expression returned to its cold state as he nodded towards Zhao Hai and said, “Let’s talk inside.” Then he turned and walked towards Zhao Hai’s room.

Zhao Hai and the others immediately followed behind. As soon as they entered the room, Ma Rulong suddenly laughed. This caused Zhao Hai and the others to feel awkward. After some time, Ma Rulong calmed down and then he patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said, “Zhao Hai, good job, good job. You’re really giving the Machine Field face. You actually killed a core member of the Seamount Faction. He’s one of the top 100 of the realm qualifiers, Gongsun Zheng. Hahaha. Good, this is great!”

Zhao Hai and the others were stunned. They remembered that they knew nothing about their opponent. But it seems like Ma Rulong was aware.

Ma Rulong looked at Zhao Hai and the others. Then he smiled and said, “When you went out, I had some people follow you. You’re now the treasure of the Machine Field, so I can’t have anything happen to you. When Gongsun Zheng began to provoke you, the team leader responsible for guarding you was going to make an attack, but he didn’t do it in the end. I really didn’t expect you to be strong enough to kill him. We’ve been collecting information about the other top 100 participants from the other realms. Once it’s completed, we can let you take a look. But in the meantime, you should go and take a break.”

Zhao Hai only knew that Ma Rulong was sending someone to follow him. However, he didn’t know that Ma Rulong was also collecting information. It seems like there were still a lot of secrets that the Machine Field held here in the Cultivation Realm.

Once Ma Rulong left, Zhao Hai chuckled and said, “I didn’t expect the person I killed is someone from the Seamount Faction. Hahaha. Interesting.”

Xiong Li and the others looked at Zhao Hai as though he was a monster. After a while, Xiong Li sighed and said, “It seems like Zhao Hai will definitely get a high rank in the Six Realm Beginner Competition. He actually killed a top 100 participant from the Cultivation Realm.” Dongfang Yu and the others nodded. If they weren’t clear about Zhao Hai’s strength before, this time they really understood Zhao Hai’s strength.

The top 100 of the Cultivation World always held the dominant positions in the Six Realm Beginner Competition. One day they might just be the top 100 of the Cultivation Realm’s qualifiers, but once the Six Realm Beginner Competition ends, it’s very possible that the same 100 would take the top 100 spots.

And now, Zhao Hai managed to kill one of the top 100 beginners in the Cultivation Realm. What does this mean? In other words, Zhao Hai has the strength to become top 100 in the Six Realm Beginner Competition!

Upon thinking about this, Xiong Li and the others couldn’t help but be happy for Zhao Hai as well as the Machine Field. The Machine Field has been suppressed by the Cultivation Realm for a long time. Now, Zhao Hai was here to vent some of the Machine Field’s anger. Xiong Li couldn’t help but feel excited.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “My goal this time isn’t as simple as being in the top 100. I’m here to challenge the authority of the Cultivation Realm. I want to let the Cultivators know that the Machine Field can be as strong as any of them.”

Xiong Li and the others simultaneously shouted ‘good’. Then Li Kuangren laughed and said, “Today is worth celebrating. Little Hai, do you still have some wine? I’ll be sad if I can’t drink today.” Zhao Hai and the others laughed. Then a few jars of wine appeared in the room. Xiong Li and the others’ eyes widened. Then they picked up the jars and headed out. Zhao Hai followed behind them as they sat in the stone chairs outside. Then he took out some side dishes from the Space. The group proceeded to drink merrily much to the envy of everyone else in the courtyard.

After becoming drunk, Zhao Hai and the others returned to their own room. Zhao Hai immediately went to the Space and drank some spatial water. Then he took out the small tree that he just obtained earlier.

Just as Zhao Hai took out the small tree, the Space immediately issued a prompt, “Primal Universe Spirit Root detected. The Space has leveled up to 180. The concentration of spiritual qi inside the Space has been increased by 100%. Plants in the Space has been increased by ten levels. Time accelerated area has increased tenfold. The time accelerated has been upgraded by 100 times. Host now has the ability to purchase high-level cultivation backgrounds, high-level technology backgrounds, and high-level magic backgrounds. Space has evolved into a small universe. All backgrounds purchased by the host has now been turned into individual planets. The speed of spirit vein generation in the Space has been increased by tenfold. All ores inside the Space can now be transformed into veins with the ability to grow autonomously. Level of the Universal Processing Machine becomes advanced. Level of the Universal Scanner becomes advanced. Host’s abilities have been increased by ten times. Magic beasts in the Space increased by ten levels, they are now officially Demonic Beasts!”

Everyone turned silent, not only Zhao Hai, but Laura and the others as well. The Space just crazily leveled up. It rose my several levels. Moreover, everything inside the Space has been upgraded. All of these was far from what Zhao Hai expected.

The Space levelled up by several tens of times. In the past, Zhao Hai didn’t experience this even at the early stages of the Space. At that time, although it was very easy for the Space to level up, it wasn’t as crazy as this time. Moreover, it seems like the Space has become a small universe. In other words, the Space has become a miniature version of the World of Cultivation. All backgrounds have also become planets. This was good news for Zhao Hai.

The backgrounds turning into planets might look like a loss to Zhao Hai because this meant that the backgrounds now had limited area. Backgrounds from before seemed endless with no end in sight. One could see from this point that Zhao Hai had suffered a loss.

However, one shouldn’t forget that the Space has something special, and that was the Hundred Spirits Tree. The Hundred Spirit Tree would produce a planetoid every hundred years. Moreover, this planet can float in the universe. If the Space doesn’t become a small universe, then where would this planetoid be placed in? In the small planet? Then that would provide some issues.

But now, this issue has been solved. Moreover, the plants and the animals of the Space has leveled up. This was an abundance of strength increase for Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai also believed that the Undead could now go beyond their limit.

There was also the Universal Processing Machine, the Universal Scanner, the increase in Spiritual Qi density, mineral veins, spirit veins, and more. All of these changes was very advantageous for the future development of the Space.

Zhao Hai finally let go of his worries. Then he turned his head to the small and dried up tree. Who would have thought that this small tree was a spirit root left behind by the universe when it was formed. If the Cultivators knew about this, they would certainly go crazy.

The Cultivators being unable to recognize the plant surprised Zhao Hai. However, he couldn’t blame them for not taking note of it. First, this thing appeared quite suddenly. Second, it was a divine object, and such treasures were difficult to look for and was only found by luck. Moreover, such treasures would hide itself so that no average person could see it.

This spirit root can be said to be a pinnacle treasure in the Cultivation Realm. However, this precious item actually appeared in a stall in the small Seamount City. Apart from people in the Seamount City, nobody would give attention to such a stall. Moreover, the Seamount Sect wouldn’t look around in the marketplace every day. There was also the arrival of the Machine Field’s delegates, causing the Seamount Faction to shift their attention. This wasn’t the time to care about something in some stall somewhere.

Gongsun Zheng just felt that the small tree wasn’t simple, he didn’t know what it was. Additionally, it was Zhao Hai who bought the spirit root. He wanted to teach Zhao Hai a lesson by forcing him to hand over the root. Gongsun Zheng had no idea about its true value.

After Zhao Hai thought of this, he turned his head to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, give the spirit root a place to settle in. Make sure to take care of it.” Cai’er complied and immediately went to the spirit root. After thinking for some time, Cai’er decided to plant the spirit root at an area not far from the Hundred Spirits Tree. This was a good place to monitor it and it offered an advantage for Zhao Hai.

But just as Cai’er placed the spirit root on the ground, the spirit root suddenly wriggled itself out fiercely. When it fell to the ground, the root burrowed down fast. Cai’er stared and then immediately tracked the root using her spiritual force. It didn’t take long before she discovered the spirit root uniting with the roots of the Hundred Spirits Tree. Soon enough, the two looked indistinguishable from each other.

It wasn’t only Cai’er who was shocked, Zhao Hai was shocked as well. He didn’t know what was happening. Then at this time, the Space has issued a prompt!

Chapter 1213: Spirit Root Union

“Spirit Root has unified with the Hundred Spirits Tree. Hundred Spirit Tree has leveled up. Because the Hundred Spirits Tree is originally a spirit tree, after unifying with the spirit root, the Hundred Spirits Tree will slowly transform into a Primal Universe Spirit Tree. Every hundred years, the tree will produce 100 fruits. Once these fruits fall down, the biggest fruit will continue developing in the universe. Planetoids may be occupied by people, can be planted on, and has mineral resources. The remaining 99 fruits can recognize owners and become spatial equipment.”

When Zhao Hai heard the prompt, he was too shocked to cheer out loud. Formidable, too formidable. He didn’t think the spirit root would fuse with the Hundred Spirits Tree.

Naturally, this wasn’t the best outcome. The best would be the Hundred Spirits Tree turning into a planet itself. Then it could grow on its own since it was still a plant.

Laura and the others were also very happy. The Space’s progression this time was too formidable. Not only had the Space obtained numerous upgrades, Zhao Hai’s strength has also increased. This was very important for their future.

Now that the Space had leveled up, its functions have been upgraded. Zhao Hai had yet to understand all that happened in the Space, so he didn’t worry too much about it. He didn’t try his strength either. He was working with Cai’er to look at the changes that happened in the Space.

The Space’s upgrade this time was a comprehensive improvement. Therefore, the functions inside as well as Zhao Hai’s strength had been improved. In the past, when Zhao Hai used Liquid Silver, it would take some time for him to cast 1000 and 10,000-layer formations. This wasn’t very useful for actual combat.

But now it was different. After obtaining new strength, Zhao Hai can now use 10,000-layer formations with ease. Although he was unable to use 100,000-layer formations instantaneously, Zhao Hai believes that it wouldn’t take long before he could do it. After all, the spiritual qi inside the Space would allow him to practice twice as much with only half the effort.

If he used the entire might of Liquid SIlver, then Zhao Hai would be able to use 300,000-layer formations. With this strength, even if he wasn’t the strongest person in the Machine Field, he would still be able to contend against Nascent Soul Stage Cultivators.

Zhao Hai was now very confident, but he didn’t become complacent. He knew that there was still room for him to improve. After all, he could still absorb more astral qi into his body. This would elevate his strength once more.

He had already absorbed astral qi before, moreover, he had digested astral qi into his own energy. Now that the Space leveled up and gave him a promotion in strength, Zhao Hai’s energy levels were more powerful than before. Because of this, Zhao Hai would still need some time before he could saturate his body with astral qi once more.

Besides Zhao Hai’s personal promotion in strength, the Undead had also gotten much stronger. The Space had improved a lot of things, naturally the Undead weren’t absent from getting the benefits.

In the past, if we evaluate the Undead using the Machine Field’s metric, then they would have level 9 Apprentice strength. But now it was different. The Undead were now level 3. Such strength was already comparable to the newcomers of the past five years.

Besides the promotion of the Undead, the golden combat suits as well as the beast bone combat suits were also improved. Whether it be attack or defense, both were increased by five times. They can now be used in the World of Cultivation.

But what made Zhao Hai happy the most were the mineral ores in the Space. Besides becoming mineral veins, they could now autonomously grow. In other words, the Space would produce mineral veins for every ore that was taken to the Space. Moreover, these veins would grow over time, just like a tree would. For Zhao Hai, this was very important.

Why were there so many disputes in the World of Cultivation? In one word, it’s resources. Resources were the essence of cultivation. If one wanted to be immortal, then they would need resources to support them on this path. Not a lot of people could succeed by just cultivating closed door all the time.

Mineral resources were one of the main things that were heavily competed on. This was because resources in the World of Cultivation don’t replenish themselves like in the Space. When it’s gone it was gone. And practitioners needed a lot of different minerals. Whether it was making weapons or defensive equipment, mineral ores were inseparable from these processes. This was especially true for precious ores.

The Six Realm Beginner Competition had mineral ores as rewards. One could see from this point how important ores were.

There were three things that were heavily competed on in the World of Cultivation. It was spirit medicine, mineral ores, and spirit veins. There was nothing much to say about spirit medicines. They could heal wounds and allow people to break through bottlenecks. Everyone needs spirit medicines. Mineral ores were more important. They were needed in making good weapons and defensive equipment. And one could get a lot of crystal stones by trading them. The most important of the three were spirit veins. The stronger a spirit vein in an area was, the better its effects on cultivation would be.

The best spirit veins in the Cultivation Realm were controlled by huge sects. The places where small sects situated themselves in were small veins. The density of spiritual qi in those places wasn’t that much.

Although the concentration of spiritual qi inside Zhao Hai’s Space couldn’t compared to high-level spirit veins, it was still much stronger than ordinary spirit veins. Zhao Hai didn’t lack spirit medicines nor was he short on mineral ores. It can be said that with this upgrade, the Space was now a perfect place for cultivation. This was why it was very important for Zhao Hai.

After staying inside the Space the entire evening, Zhao Hai refreshingly went out of the Space in the morning. Although Zhao Hai hasn’t been able to rest much last night, he was not tired. Conversely, because of the Space’s upgrade, he had more energy than the day before.

Xiong Li and the others had also got up at this time. The group were all in good spirits. Although they had drunk a lot of liquor, the liquor wasn’t that strong to knock them out. Therefore, everyone was full of energy and weren’t hungover.

When the group saw Zhao Hai, they immediately welcomed him. Li Kuangren laughed and said, “Yesterday was the best time I had while drinking. Little Hai, do you want to head out and take a stroll?”

Although Zhao Hai was thinking about heading out, he shook his head in the end and said, “Let’s not. We just killed a core disciple of the Seamount Faction yesterday. The Seamount Faction would certainly look for trouble if we went out. Let’s stay here instead of being plotted against.”

Li Kuangren nodded. At this time, Xiong Li opened his mouth and said, “I can’t head out as well. The family said that they would deliver my weapon today. Little Hai, I’ll have to depend on you when it arrives.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t worry about it. I’ll make sure that you’ll be satisfied with the result. Little Fei, I’ll give this to you first. These are formation sets that I had researched. They should be good for you.”

After he said that, Zhao Hai handed a card over to Sun Fei. Stored in this card were several magic formation sets. The sets spanned from 10-layers to 50-layers. They were appropriate for Sun Fei’s uses.

Sun Fei excitedly received the card before connecting it to his wrist computer. Zhao Hai looked at him and said, “Alright, go back to your room and read them. In any case, we won’t be heading out today.” Then with a nod, Sun Fei quickly ran to his room.

Dongfang Yu looked at Sun Fei with envy, then he sighed and said, “Now I’m the only one left without any benefits. Little Hai, that’s not good. You need to prepare something for me. Or else I won’t forgive you.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Alright, while I’m refining Boss Xiong’s hammer, I’ll make sure to make you something as well.”

Dongfang Yu gave a satisfied nod. They didn’t ask Zhao Hai what he would do to Xiong Li’s hammer. Although they were good friends, they knew that each one of them had their own secrets.

Zhao Hai and the others were in very good terms. Additionally, their temperaments matched very well with each other. All of them had already treated Zhao Hai like their own brother. Naturally, they wouldn’t ask him about things and just believed in him.

Zhao Hai also wanted to prepare one or two weapons for Dongfang Yu. One reason why Cultivators were very strong was their myriad of magical artifacts. During a fight, a Cultivator could literally flood their enemies to death using these items. These magical artifacts also provided them with a lot of patterns to attack.

On the other hand, due to the lack of resources, the Machine Field was limited in their items. Most practitioners in the Machine Field would only have one weapon and a set of techniques to complement it. Seeing from this point, it was no wonder that they were inferior to the Cultivators.

Zhao Hai wanted to change this situation. He can now make simple magic items. But with the methods of the Machine Field, they wouldn’t be able to use these items in the real world. Therefore, Zhao Hai wanted to make weapons that Dongfang Yu and the others could use.

On a certain degree,  magic items weren’t inferior to the Cultivation Realm’s magical artifacts. This was especially true for low-level practitioners. Low-level practitioners often had very few items on hand since they couldn’t use high-level items. And in terms of low-level items, the gap between the Machine Field and the Cultivation Realm wasn’t that far.

Take Dongfang Yu as an example. His only weapon was his fire dragon sword. If he had a shield for defense, then it would be able to play a crucial role at a critical time.

In addition to the shield, there were also other useful weapons. For example, a few people in the World of Cultivation still used bows and arrows. But this doesn’t mean that this was a bad choice.

Chapter 1214: Bow and Arrow

The bow and arrow, this was a weapon that was universally used in the lower realms. However, this was a weapon that almost nobody used in the World of Cultivation. This was because in the eyes of the practitioners, the bow and arrow was a weak weapon.

The bow and arrow cannot be used by Mages. As for Warriors, they already had their sword qi. Moreover, as Warriors gets stronger, the range of their attacks would go beyond the range of bows and arrows. Because of this, nobody used bows and arrows in the Machine Field.

Not to mention the Cultivation Realm. Even the lowest level of artifacts in the Cultivation Realm can fly out to attack the enemy. Also, once the weapon flew up, they could be controlled using spiritual force. Compared to the fixed flight of a bow and arrow, this method was evidently stronger.

Due to all of these reasons, almost nobody used bows and arrows in the World of Cultivation. One couldn’t even see a shadow of this weapon anywhere.

But why was it ‘almost’, why not perfectly? This was because there were still people in the World of Cultivation that used bows and arrows. Moreover, these people belong to a quite powerful sect.

The Cultivation Realm had a sect called the Shooting Sun Sect. This was a sect that specialized in the use of bows and arrows. Their bows and arrows were specially made. It can be said that their bow and the arrow were two separate weapons. One could be used without the other.

The method of manufacturing for this unique style of bow and arrow wasn’t released to the public. Moreover, only a select few in the Shooting Sun sect knew how to do it. But one shouldn’t underestimate the Shooting Sun Sect. The fighting strength of their Core Disciples is astonishing. In the Cultivation Realm’s participants in the competition, the third strongest beginner was someone from the Shooting Sun Sect.

The reason why Zhao Hai wanted Dongfang Yu to used a bow and arrow was because of the weapon shattering property that he just discovered.

Weapon shattering was used by Mechs. It’s purpose was to destroy the armor and weapons of the enemy. This was an effect that was heavily reliant on energy to support it. Zhao Hai saw how strong a Warrior’s energy can be. Therefore, he planned to make a set of bows and arrows that had the property of weapon shattering.

Naturally, it was impossible for normal people to use these bows and arrows immediately. Using this weapon requires time and practice.

However, one shouldn’t forget that Dongfang Yu and the others were ascendants from the Lower Realms. Moreover, their formidable weapons required the eyesight and arm strength that bows and arrows also need. Also, Zhao Hai wasn’t making them switch to using bows and arrows. Instead, he wanted them to use it as a secondary weapon. In this case, it wouldn’t be a problem for Dongfang Yu and the others to use bows and arrows.

On each arrow, Zhao Hai placed weapon shattering formations, energy storing formations, and other supplementary formations. The arrows would have energy stores inside them that would only be activated during flight. The energy inside each arrow was enough for one activation of weapon shattering.

In essence, arrows were consumables. Therefore, not much energy was needed to be stored inside. Moreover, Zhao Hai also included an explosion formation in the arrows. This way, after the arrow uses weapon shattering, it would also explode.

These ideas made Zhao Hai prepare bows and arrows for Dongfang Yu and the others to use. He believes that it would improve their combat strength by quite a margin.

The attacking strength of bows and arrows wasn’t that far behind sword qi. But compared to energy use, the consumption of using arrows can be said to be negligible.

Besides bows and arrows, Zhao Hai also made shields. These shields had protection formations inside that could block any Foundation Establishment level attacks.

The reason why Zhao Hai prepared these things was to enhance the strength of his brothers. This way, they would have a much greater chance in surviving later on.

The people of the Cultivation Realm weren’t a friendly bunch. If there was an opportunity, they would no doubt kill anyone from the Machine Field. During the elimination round, Zhao Hai could team up with Xiong Li and the others to ensure their safety. But after that, during the arena matches, nobody can say what would happen. Therefore, Zhao Hai hoped that Dongfang Yu and the others would become stronger. Even if they couldn’t win against their opponent, they should at least be able to preserve their lives.

The group continued to chat as they sat by the stone table. The other participants from the Machine Field looked at them with envious gazes. Of the top 100 participants from the Machine Field, only a few of them were from the same faction. Because of this, most of the participants weren’t familiar with each other. Some even had enmity with another. It was very rare to see a scene similar to what Zhao Hai and the others had.

These people knew that making friends was very important for the upcoming elimination round. However, they wouldn’t dare make friends that recklessly. This was because they still didn’t know whether the others had any ulterior motives or not. If the other party used you and then stabs you in the back during critical moments, then their deaths would be unjust. Therefore, they could only stare at Zhao Hai and the others with envy.

As the group chatted, another party walked in from the outside. When Xiong Li saw them, he immediately stood up and said, “The people from my family have arrived.”

After he said that, Xiong Li immediately stepped forward to meet the one leading the group. Then he bowed and said, “Camp Lord, why did you come here personally?” It was clear that this Camp Lord was favoring Xiong Li, he smiled and answered, “It’s all paid for by the family, so how could I miss it? Here, this is your new weapon. Try to see if it fits you well.” then as he said that, the Camp Lord took out a pair of chained hammers from his spatial equipment.

At this time, Zhao Hai and the others had stepped forward to salute the person. While he was giving his greetings, Zhao Hai was also sizing up this Camp Lord from the Wu Family. He had an appearance of a Warrior and was wearing very ordinary clothing. One couldn’t see anything noteworthy about him. However, Zhao Hai could see that his strength was at least level 6. This was a true expert of the Machine Field.

This person wasn’t tall and had a face that was indistinguishable from others. If not for Xiong Li calling him Camp Lord, then Zhao Hai and the others wouldn’t have known that he was a Camp Lord of the Wu Family.

The Camp Lord was also sizing up Zhao Hai and the others. Seeing these group of youngsters giving him a salute, he returned the greeting. Then he turned to look at Zhao Hai as he chuckled and said, “Zhao Hai, the Machine Field’s champion. I just heard about what happened yesterday from Ma Rulong. I must say, that was fantastic, good job. Make sure to show everyone the might of the Machine Field.”  Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Thank you Camp Lord. This Zhao Hai will certainly work hard.”

At this time, Xiong Li has taken up his hammers. To be honest, he didn’t really care about their quality. Zhao Hai had given him word that he would reforge them. Therefore, when he took the two hammers, he pretended to be satisfied as he nodded and said, “Good, very good. Thank you, Camp Lord.”

The Camp Lord smiled faintly then he said, “You’re welcome. Right, where’s your previous weapon? The family told me to take it back.” Xiong Li nodded, then he handed over his original chained hammers. The Camp Lord exchanged a few more words with Xiong Li before turning around and leaving.

Seeing that the Camp Lord had left, Xiong Li quickly turned towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then whispered, “Hand it over to me tonight. It’ll be too eye catching if you give it to me immediately.” Xiong Li nodded before putting his hammers inside his spatial equipment. This action caused everyone in the courtyard to be stunned. This was because Xiong Li never puts his hammers away. He would always hang them by his waist.

When Zhao Hai saw Xiong Li’s action, he couldn’t help but smile. Xiong Li was truly smart. Zhao Hai’s refining of Xiong Li’s hammer wasn’t a matter of minutes, but days. Xiong Li couldn’t hang his hammers by his waist during that time. If Xiong Li didn’t do anything, then people would get suspicious. Now that Xiong Li placed his hammers inside his spatial equipment, even if it was strange, when Zhao Hai closes up, people wouldn’t put the two matters together.

Sun Fei was still inside his room busily studying Zhao Hai’s formation sets. He would have his meals delivered to his room.

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything regarding this situation. It was also good that Sun Fei was working hard. At this time, Zhao Hai hoped that Sun Fei can learn a formation or two before the competition begins. This way, his arsenal of formations would increase, allowing him greater chances of survival.

The day quickly passed. In the evening, Xiong Li and the others went to Zhao Hai’s room to drink again. However, they didn’t drink much that night. They were just there mainly for Xiong Li to leave his hammer.

After Xiong Li handed his hammer over, the group drank for a while before they returned to their rooms. At the same time, Zhao Hai returned to the Space, it was time for him to be closing up.

Zhao Hai already thought about which formations to place inside Xiong Li’s hammers. After returning to the Space, he first used the Universal Processing Machine to turn Xiong Li’s hammers back into raw materials. Then according to the data produced, he could remake the hammers anew.

But what Zhao Hai didn’t expect was that in the process of reconstructing Xiong Li’s hammer, the Space would gain new metallic materials. Because of this, the Space produced mineral veins for each material found. This caused Zhao Hai to be very surprised.

After taking care of Xiong Li’s hammer, Zhao Hai proceeded to the manufacturing of the bows, arrows, and shields. The bows were quite hard to manufacture, they were very demanding when it came to materials. However, arrows were relatively simpler.

Fortunately, Zhao Hai had plenty of materials inside the Space. And with the help of the processing machine, making the bows and arrows became easy.

The next step was the manufacturing of the shields. Requirements for making the shields were also very high. The main reason for this was because it needed a lot of formations in order for its defensive capabilities to be good enough.

Zhao Hai didn’t add any counter-attack formations to the shields. In Zhao Hai’s view, there was no need for such things. Shields should focus on being as defensive as possible. Bows and arrows were present, so counter-attacking shields weren’t needed.

There were ten processing machines in Zhao Hai’s Space. Although the quantity didn’t increase during the recent level up, the speed of each machine had increased. Even Xiong Li’s hammers wouldn’t take a long time to make. Moreover, the quality was much better than before.

Chapter 1215: The Dense But Also Sensitive Li Kuangren

After cultivating for three days in the yellowsand planet inside the Space, Zhao Hai went out. What came out with him was a pile of things. There were three bows as well as about 1000 arrows. There were also four shields as well as Xiong Li’s hammer.

Although Ma Rulong was somewhat puzzled that Zhao Hai was closing up, he didn’t say anything. It was well known that Zhao Hai liked to seclude himself. He had secluded himself a lot of times back when he was in the Ashley Family. The time he spent outside was very short. If he wasn’t doing missions or participating in competitions, Zhao Hai would spend most of his time closing up. This caused everyone to be very curious about him.

Xiong Li and the others were still guarding the door into Zhao Hai’s room and wouldn’t let anyone approach. Everyone had already been used to this. While the brothers were chatting, the door to Zhao Hai’s room opened. Zhao Hai was there smiling faintly like before.

Upon seeing Zhao Hai, Xiong Li’s eyes couldn’t help but light up. Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Come in.” Xiong Li and the others immediately entered the room.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and took out Xiong Li’s hammers. As he gave them to Xiong Li, he said, “Boss Xiong, give it a try. I installed 80 formations inside. Naturally, there’s weapon shattering as well.”

Xiong Li anxiously nodded with excitement. He took the hammers and then gave it a couple of waves before he nodded with satisfaction. After that, Zhao Hai took out a shield and then said, “Try it out.”

This shield wasn’t the one he prepared for Xiong Li and the others. Xiong Li didn’t hesitate as he hit the shield with his hammer. It didn’t take long before the shield exploded and turned into dust. Xiong Li became even more satisfied with the result.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “In addition to its original formations, I also added the weapon shattering formation. At the same time, I added a defense strengthening formation to your chains. There’s also an energy storage formation added, this way, even if you use your hammer as a projectile, it could still inflict weapon shattering.”

Xiong Li laughed as he waved his hammer a few more times. Then after putting his hammers away he hugged Zhao Hai and said, “Thank you for the hammers, Little Hai. This will increase my combat ability by at least three layers.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then said, “Right, I have other things to give you.” After he said that, he took out the bows and arrows that he made. Xiong Li and the others could only stare at what they saw. They were all looking puzzled as they looked at Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai proceeded to explain the use of these bows and arrows. Xiong Li and the others were pleasantly surprised. Just like what Zhao Hai thought, XIong Li and the others were very familiar with bows and arrows. They had used it in some manner back in the lower realms. Xiong Li and the others immediately received their bows and arrows. They didn’t even need to try them out.

After that, Zhao Hai took out a few shields. These several hundred shields weren’t only for Warriors like Xiong Li, some were for Sun Fei as well. Once he had handed out the shields to everyone, Zhao Hai said, “I also added weapon shattering to these shields. The property of weapon shattering cannot only be used for offense, it’s effective for defense as well. It’s vibration would cause the enemy’s energy to dissipate, allowing the shield to block the attack better. These shields can only block one full strike from someone like Li Chuchen. Therefore, be careful when using them.”

Xiong Li and the others nodded. Then Zhao Hai turned to Sun Fei and said, “Little Fei, how is your research on magic formations doing?”

With shining eyes, Sun Fei replied, “I understood several formations. Brother Hai, you’re really great. When I experimented, the magic formations have truly marvelous effects. They may look similar to ordinary formations, but their effects are three layers above. It’s mystical.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he patted Sun Fei’s shoulder and said, “Use the remaining time to study more formations. If your mastery gets higher, I can teach you more magic formation sets. I can even teach you the weapon shattering formation.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Sun Fei’s eyes lit up. He looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, do you mean?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “What I mean is if your mastery goes higher, I can give you the weapon shattering formation. Think about a fireball with weapon shattering. What would that look like.”

Sun Fei repeatedly nodded, yearning could be seen in his eyes. Zhao Hai looked at him and said, “Don’t think about it too much. Focus on practicing. With your current spiritual force, there’s no way for you to use weapon shattering. Even I need to exert effort in order to use it.”

Sun Fei nodded, “Brother Hai, rest assured, I will work hard.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then after the group sat down, he said, “Now that we’re in the Cultivation Realm, we have no place to spar in. Even if there is, we still can’t go since the Cultivators could spy on us. The best opportunity to practice the bows and arrows is right in the elimination round. I don’t want to offend you, but your present strength is still far off compared to the Cultivators. The bows and arrows that I gave you isn’t for defeating your opponents rather it’s for you to protect yourself. The Cultivators wouldn’t be holding back, and I need you all to survive. Let’s wait a couple of years before coming back to clean them all up.”

Xiong Li and the others nodded. They didn’t feel that they were great just because Zhao Hai managed to kill Gongsun Zheng. Zhao Hai effortlessly beat his opponents in the realm qualifiers. This fully explained how strong Zhao Hai was. Although he had ascended for less than a year’s time, Xiong Li and the others had already recognized him as the core of their group.

Although Zhao Hai’s words weren’t pleasant to hear, Xiong Li and the others weren’t fools. They knew the strength of the Cultivation Realm. They weren’t even a match against Gongsun Zheng, not to say about the others higher ranked than him.

The fight between Zhao Hai and Gongsun Zheng might look very relaxed, but this was only because Zhao Hai was using light element magic which happens to restrain ghosts. Moreover, Zhao Hai could cast 50 and 100-layer formations easily. This made it possible for Zhao Hai to eliminate Gongsun Zheng in a swift manner. If it was Xiong Li and the others, then they wouldn’t have as good of a fighting chance as Zhao Hai.

Sun Fei was a Mage, so he was the one who was most aware about Zhao Hai’s strength. Even if the two of them were level 4 Mages, only Zhao Hai was able to effortlessly cast 100-layer formations.

After seeing the others nod, Zhao Hai added, “After the competition, I’ll go and find ourselves a base. There, we brothers can practice together. If we head back to the Machine Field, then we’ll just be going back to being workhorses.” Upon listening to Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others stared. Then their eyes turned bright before their eyebrows knit themselves in.

To be honest, Zhao Hai’s proposal was very good. However, they didn’t have much confidence in Zhao Hai. In their minds, Zhao Hai might be strong, but not enough to take on the entire Machine Field.

Upon seeing their reactions, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I didn’t say that we would separate from the Machine Field, or treat them as an enemy. I just want us to have a place where we could live independently. I believe this wouldn’t be difficult to do.” Xiong Li nodded, “Of course, that wouldn’t be difficult. There are a lot of experts in the Machine Field that took in asteroids or meteorites as bases, living in relative independence. With Little Hai’s current strength, it’s possible for us to be allowed to do that. If we can get good rankings, I reckon they wouldn’t stop us.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, then that’s settled. I will definitely get a good ranking. When the time comes, we would have our own place and can do whatever we want.”

Xiong Li and the others let out a long breath filled with yearning. To be honest, although their families had attached great importance to them, this didn’t make them feel good. They wanted to be independent and free.

Suddenly, Li Kuangren said, “Little Hai, have you discussed this with Margaret? To be honest, women like Margaret are very hard to find. You should treasure her opinion. If she opposes this, what would you do?”

Zhao Hai didn’t expect Li Kuangren to say such words. He seemed like a dense person, but he actually had a sensitive side. Being able to think about this thing meant that he was quite the sentimental person.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t worry about it Third Brother. I already told Margaret about this and she agreed to it. In fact, her relationship with the Ashley Family wasn’t that good because of her mother. She had been independent from a very young age. She agrees to this decision as long as I lend the Ashley Family a hand during times of crisis.”

Li Kuangren made a sigh of relief before he looked at Zhao Hai with envy and said, “You’re a lucky kid to meet a good woman like Margaret. Well, it’s good that Margaret agrees. Otherwise, I don’t think we can continue. If you quarrel with Margaret, then I think we would all feel restless.” Xiong Li nodded and said, “Right, what Third Brother said is correct. If this makes your relationship with Margaret unpleasant, then I don’t think anyone here would feel great.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Be relieved, Margaret agrees. Right, all of you should use the rest of the days to practice. Use these potions to practice. This will allow you to improve your strength. In any case, we can’t head out now. We might as well use the time to practice.”

As he said that, Zhao Hai took out several bottles of potions. The Machine Field’s medicines were different to the Cultivation Realm’s. In the Machine Field, medicines came in liquid form while the Cultivation Realm had medicinal pills. Pills were more convenient to carry. And when it came to effects, they were much better compared to the Machine Field’s potions. This was mainly because the Cultivation Realm had much better materials than the Machine Field.

Each large sect in the Cultivation Realm had its own medicinal garden. Moreover, these gardens were divided into ordinary gardens and advanced-level gardens. Planted inside ordinary gardens were the ordinary herbs that doesn’t take a long time to mature. As for the advanced-level gardens, they had the more valuable herbs planted in. Their maturity time was a very long time. There were some herbs that required several hundred years while some were over a thousand. These kinds of valuable herbs couldn’t be found in the Machine Field.

The major sects of the Cultivation Realm existed for tens of thousands of years. With their deep foundation, it was no wonder that they would have high-level medicinal gardens. Others simply couldn’t compare.

Because of such medicinal gardens, pills in the Cultivation Realm were much better compared to the Machine Field’s potions. However, this didn’t mean that potions didn’t have an advantage. Since potions were in liquid form, they were easier to absorb and were thus faster in its effects.

However, the Machine Field didn’t have a lot of variety when it comes to potions. It was very different compared to the Cultivation Realm where each sect had their own pill formulas. In the Machine Field, not a lot of people could use potions to help with their cultivation. Moreover, these potions were very precious, ordinary people could never get ahold of them.

The bottles that Zhao Hai took out weren’t small. Each bottle had about five jin(2.5kg) of liquid inside. Seeing the contents of each bottle, Xiong Li and the others couldn’t help but get startled.

Seeing these huge bottles, Xiong Li suddenly said, “It seems like I need to take a walk in the Wu Family more often. If I also get a young miss as a wife, then maybe I can drink these potions as water.”

Xiong Li’s remark caused Li Kuangren and the others to laugh. But all of them knew that Zhao Hai didn’t get these potions through Margaret. After getting to know Zhao Hai for the past few days, they knew that he wasn’t that kind of person.

Although they made their own comments, the brothers weren’t too polite. All of them took one bottle and then left. With their current relationship with Zhao Hai, politeness was no longer needed. Instead, being overly polite would just make the situation awkward.

After the others left, Zhao Hai went out of his room and found a team leader in the courtyard. He told the team leader that they were going to be closing up for a while, and that nobody should disturb them.

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the team leader couldn’t help but look at him as though he was a monster. However, the team leader didn’t say anything and just nodded.

Zhao Hai didn’t bother to think about what the team leader thought. When he returned to his own room, he locked the door and then entered the Space. Although he had been practicing in the yellowsand environment for the past three days, he had yet to saturate his body with astral qi. He still needed some time to finish his practice. Zhao Hai believed that as long as his body gets saturated with astral qi once more, then his strength would skyrocket.

Zhao Hai didn’t dare to underestimate the Cultivators. Even if he had gotten stronger recently, he didn’t let his guard down. This was because the methods of the Cultivators were still too mysterious for the Machine Field. One wouldn’t know what secret techniques a Cultivator might have. Zhao Hai didn’t want to reveal his cards too soon. After all, he still needs to compete for the top spot in the competition.

Chapter 1216: Devil Planet Fabio

Time passed unknowingly and more than half a month had passed. During this half month, Streep and the others discovered something strange, it seems like Zhao Hai’s group had secluded themselves as if they had an agreement.

They felt strange about Xiong Li and the others’ seclusion. To be honest, even if the Cultivation Realm had a different density of spiritual qi compared to the Machine Field, it only took two days to get used to it. There was no need to close up in order to adapt.

To be honest, this courtyard wasn’t suitable for cultivation Moreover, they didn’t close up until a few days after arriving here. This was a very strange action for the others.

It wasn’t only Streep and the others, Ma Rulong was the same. However, Ma Rulong was relieved. Although the Seamount Faction no longer came looking for trouble, Ma Rulong was still afraid that Zhao Hai and the others would keep heading out. If the Seamount Faction sent someone to attack them, then it would be bad if they were injured. The elimination round was happening soon, the safety of Zhao Hai needed to be ensured.

Actually, Ma Rulong appreciated Zhao Hai. He regarded Zhao Hai as the hope of the Machine Field. Zhao Hai’s ability to kill someone from the top 100 of the Cultivation Realm moved Ma Rulong.

For many years, the Machine Field never had an ascender as talented as Zhao Hai. Whenever the Cultivation Realm and the Machine Field face each other in the competition, the former would always kill the latter. This fate never changed. This was also the reason why the Cultivation Realm suppressed the Machine Field at all times.

And now there was Zhao Hai. First he blocked three swords from the Cultivation Realm’s Li Chuchen. He also killed someone from the top 100 of the Cultivation Realm’s beginners. This caused Ma Rulong to feel relieved. Therefore, he didn’t want Zhao Hai to get injured before the competition.

Zhao Hai’s decision to seclude himself made Ma Rulong relieved. He also sent people to make sure that nobody would disturb them.

But as the days passed, Ma Rulong began to grow concerns about Zhao Hai and the others. The elimination round was going to start in seven days. They also need to leave in two days since they would need to travel to the planet where the elimination round would be held. Zhao Hai’s and the others’ seclusion caused Ma Rulong a bit of trouble.

It wasn’t strange for a practitioner to seclude themselves. There would always be occasions where someone would need to close up for practice. However, this meant that the person would be cut off from the outside world. Forcefully breaking a session of seclusion would possibly erase all progress made. It was even possible for one to suffer backlash, which was extremely dangerous.

Ma Rulong felt a bit awkward. Although there was still seven days before the start of the competition and they wouldn’t have to use spaceships due to transmission formations, the place they were going to wasn’t a good destination. The planet was called Devil Planet Fabio.

Fabio Planet was a planet located between the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm. This planet was famous in both realms and was also quite known by others. It can be said that it was even crazier than Yellowsand Planet.

Yellowsand Planet was famous because of its astral qi and not because of its beasts. On the other hand, Fabio Planet was actually famous because of the lifeform inhabiting it. They’re called the Bug Race!

The Bug Race was the most glaring feature of Fabio planet, the ones holding true control over the entire planet!

Nobody knew where these bugs came from or how they came to be. At the same time, nobody knew when they populated Fabio Planet. The moment the Cultivation Realm discovered the planet, these bugs were already thriving on it.

Fabio planet’s environment was very good. It’s spiritual qi was alright, and there were even veins of crystal stones and ores that could be found on its surface. For the Cultivators, Fabio Planet was very useful. It was even better than most planets in the Machine Field.

In the beginning, when the Cultivators discovered these bugs, they didn’t treat them too seriously. In their opinion, the Bug Race were just insects that grew big. Moreover, it seems like they had no fighting strength. They simply weren’t worthy of paying attention to.

But since Fabio Planet had useful resources, the Cultivation realm decided to mine them. And in order to do so, they need to exterminate the Bug Race.

Correct, exterminate. This wasn’t the first time the Cultivators did this. When they discover any planet with resources they want, they would generally eliminate all native life on it. But if the native population was useful, then they would be turned into slaves. If these natives were useless, then they would just be massacred. The Cultivators weren’t strangers to completely eradicating all the inhabitants of a planet.

But as the Cultivators began to cleanse the planet from the bugs, something surprising happened. As the bugs were about to be exterminated, they suddenly evolved. Their fighting strength got stronger and began to cause the Cultivators to suffer losses.

The Cultivators became furious because of this. Cultivators had always been aloof. Seeing mere insects kill them off, the Cultivation Realm began to send large-scale armies to cleanse the planet from the insects.

This cleansing initially went smoothly. The second batch of Cultivators were much stronger than the first batch. It didn’t take long before the bugs were pushed back and were once more brought to the brink of extinction.

However, the Cultivators didn’t expect how hard it was to get rid of these bugs. As the Cultivators continued to kill the bugs, the bugs were also  unceasingly evolving. Every time the Cultivators send a person, the bugs would get stronger. Such speed of promotion caused the Cultivation Realm to be apprehensive and fearful.

People in the Cultivation Realm didn’t know whether these bugs would evolve if a powerful expert was sent over. If they did, then the Cultivation Realm would be overwhelmed.

Therefore, the Cultivation Realm changed its tactics. Instead of sending powerful experts to kill the Bug Race in one fell swoop, they made Fabio Planet a smelting ground. They established transmission formations on the planet and had young disciples from sects sent over in order to kill bugs as a test.

This new method turned out to be good. Although Fabio Planet was mostly populated by the Bug Race, the humans were still able to build a few strongholds and managed to gain a solid foothold on the planet.

But at the same time, the Bugs of Fabio Planet weren’t hospitable. The planet has now become the most infamous smelting grounds of the Cultivation Realm. It was also treated as a place for exile. If one offended someone from a sect, then they might be assigned to Fabio Planet. Being assigned to Fabio Planet was considered to be one of the most dangerous tasks one could undergo. The number of casualties in this planet was much higher than one could imagine. Therefore, Fabio Planet had earned itself the name Devil Planet Fabio.

However, one has to recognize that those who could survive in Fabio Planet was among the strongest among their peers.

After years of fighting, the bugs in Fabio Planet evolved into a variety of forms. Some have even evolved to use spell-type attacks. This made Fabio Planet much more dangerous than it was before.

Ma Rulong had some complaints about Fabio Planet being the stage for the competition’s elimination round. However, since his opinion was basically useless, he can only accept this condition.

The reason why Ma Rulong wanted to go to Fabio Planet ahead of time was because he wanted Zhao Hai and the others to get acquainted with the planet. This way, their probability of surviving would increase.

If not for this batch of newcomers being strong, then Ma Rulong would have sent word back to the higher-ups advising them to withdraw from the competition. This was because an elimination round in Fabio Planet would be very dangerous. Even Cultivators would suffer heavy losses there, not to say people from the Machine Field. If their team composition was like the previous years, then Ma Rulong was certain that the Machine Field’s delegates would be totally annihilated.

But since the Machine Field had acquired a strong contender like Zhao Hai, Ma Rulong couldn’t take this matter lightly. After all, they were going to Fabio Planet.

Ma Rulong was very confident in this particular Six Realm Beginner Competition. It might as well be said that he was confident in Zhao Hai. Ma Rulong knew that even if there were powerful experts in the competition, they were still far off compared to Cultivators. The only person that was able to contend against Cultivators was Zhao Hai.

And since he was placing great importance to Zhao Hai, Ma Rulong didn’t dare disturb Xiong Li and the others. Ma Rulong was well aware of Zhao Hai’s relationship with Xiong Li and the others. If Xiong Li and the others were injured because their seclusion was abruptly ended, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t be happy.

Ma Rulong wasn’t necessarily afraid of Zhao Hai. However, Zhao Hai was the hope of the Machine Field. Ma Rulong didn’t want to offend a person like that, especially at this time.

Just as Ma Rulong was thinking about this dilemma, Zhao Hai had gone out. And after Zhao Hai went out, he immediately went to the rooms beside him to call Xiong Li and the others. Xiong Li and the others took the potion and had their strengths improved. However, this improvement wasn’t very obvious. After all, the time they spent cultivating was too short.

Meanwhile, Zhao Hai’s strength was rapidly rising. This was because the Space’s recent upgrade had brought him a lot of advantages. And this time, he was able to saturate his body with astral qi. His fighting strength has increased further.

The reason Zhao Hai chose to head out at this time was because he knew that Ma Rulong was feeling awkward about the seclusion. Zhao Hai didn’t want to cause problems to Ma Rulong. After all, Ma Rulong had been taking good care of them.

When Zhao Hai got out, Ma Rulong’s headache was immediately solved. Naturally, Ma Rulong was delighted. Without him knowing, he was favoring Zhao Hai more and more.

This was how things sometimes worked. There were times where your actions unknowingly win someone’s favor. There were also times where currying favor would instead cause the other party to be offended. In this situation, Zhao Hai didn’t intend to win Ma Rulong’s favor. He just didn’t want Ma Rulong to be put in an awkward situation.

The day after Zhao Hai and the others ended their seclusion, Ma Rulong led the Machine Field’s delegates to the transmission formation that led to Fabio Planet.

Chapter 1217: A Sudden Fight

White light flickered and Zhao Hai felt a slight dizziness. But he knew that this was normal. Transmission formations had this effect to those who use it.

Once he felt the slight dizziness, Zhao Hai knew that they had arrived at their destination. However, almost immediately, he felt a dangerous aura waft over him. This caused Zhao Hai to be puzzled. He didn’t know what was going on, but just to be sure he took out liquid silver.

The white light slowly disappeared and Zhao Hai began to sense the situation outside. But as he sensed what was happening, his expression quickly changed as he shouted, “Watch out, the bugs are attacking!” His voice was very loud, so everyone heard him.

Everyone’s response upon hearing Zhao Hai’s warning wasn’t to be alert. Instead, they looked at Zhao Hai blankly. Only Xiong Li and the others didn’t delay and immediately took their weapons out. They believed Zhao Hai.

At this time, the white light vanished. People then began to see the shadows on top of them. There were large quantities of dark green beings in mid-air. On their backs were transparent wings while their forelegs were two bladed appendages. These were insects that were attacking.

These bugs were very agile. They flew on top of heads and then turned one time as they removed the head from the body.

Upon seeing this situation, everyone else called out in alarm before responding with their sword qi and magic. Meanwhile, as Zhao Hai released attacks towards the insects, he also erected a protective shield to cover Xiong Li and the others.

Zhao Hai counted and the attack had already claimed the lives of 33 people, five of which were team leaders while 28 were participants. Among these people were experts who weren’t weak at all.

The insects didn’t retreat far, they flew up in the air to prepare for their second attack. At this moment, Ma Rulong finally assessed the situation. At the same time, he surveyed the area and found that a battle was currently taking place.

They were currently in Fabio Planet’s base number 5. This was Fabio Planet’s second largest base. It was a frontier base that was meant to confront the Bug Race. Ma Rulong intended to have Zhao Hai and the others experience the Bug Race here. Base Number 5 had bugs running around just outside its walls.

However, Ma Rulong didn’t expect that Base Number 5 would be attacked even before he had Zhao Hai and the others observe the Bug Race. He was truly caught by surprise.

At this time, the people in Base Number 5 were fighting against the Bug Race. Just outside the transmission formation were several Cultivators fighting against some bugs. One could even see a crack on the wall in the distance.

Ma Rulong loudly gave his command, “Warriors go forward and protect the Mages. Mages, cast your magic. Give priority to large-scale attacks.”

Upon hearing Ma Rulong’s command, those who were panicking began to calm down. Everyone quickly followed the command. Warriors took their weapons before stepping forward. Meanwhile, Mages retreated to the middle of the crowd, forming a circle formation.

Then at this moment, large quantities of bugs welled up from outside. These bugs weren’t winged insects, instead they had eight sharp feet that looked like spears.

These insects were very fast. Moreover, each and every one of them were tall. These three-meter tall insects began to throw themselves towards the Machine Field’s circle formation.

Ma Rulong began leading the group. Upon seeing the insects, he calmly ordered, “Warriors, prepare your attacks. Rotate the circle after each attack.” Every Warrior quickly moved. The entire formation rotated as sword qi after sword qi were sent flying towards the bugs. The middle of the formation wasn’t idle. Mages also began sending attacks outwards.

However, the insects weren’t to be trifled with. One by one, they charged. Even if their arms were being severed, these bugs still continued to pounce.

Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t hold back. He sent forth his ten thousand fiery arrows. After a series of explosions, the bugs were exploded beyond recovery.

But not all Mages achieved the same result as Zhao Hai. Even if their spells hit the bugs, they just hurt the bugs at most. In turn, not a lot of bugs were killed. One could see from this point the gap between Zhao Hai and the other Mages.

Ma Rulong wasn’t in the outskirts of the formation but instead was in the middle as he was commanding the revolution of the formation. At the same time, he was also paying attention to the flying head detaching insects. These bugs were still flying overhead waiting for an opportunity to attack.

Naturally, Ma Rulong saw Zhao Hai’s results. He also remembered that Zhao Hai gave the initial warning. Upon seeing Zhao Hai’s spell kill a lot of insects, Ma Rulong couldn’t help but feel a special fondness towards Zhao Hai.

Moreover, Ma Rulong discovered that besides him, Zhao Hai was also paying attention to the bugs flying overhead. The others were focused on the bugs on the ground that they had forgotten about those flying above.

At this time, a transmission formation nearby lit up before a group walked out from it. It was clear that these people already knew the situation. When they appeared, they already had their weapons out. Moreover, they immediately attacked the bugs.

Upon seeing this, Ma Rulong’s tension couldn’t help but loosen. It seems like the Cultivators haven’t given up on this base yet. Then at this moment Zhao Hai’s voice was heard, “Everyone pay attention. Let’s slowly move to the side and clear the transmission formation. We don’t want to block any reinforcements.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Ma Rulong felt the urge to shout in shame. He forgot that they were still standing on a transmission formation. Since they were occupying such a huge formation, it would be impossible for others to use it. Ma Rulong hadn’t thought through this point.

Fortunately, Ma Rulong was quickly able to respond, “Everyone, head eastwards. Maintain the formation, move slowly!” With Ma Rulong’s order, the huge formation of people began to move eastward. There was a street there with enough width that would make it better for them to deal with the bugs. The street wasn’t very wide so the bugs would be unable to surround then. This also gave them a stable foothold in the ground.

But Ma Rulong wasn’t proud about being able to repel the bugs. Although he had never met these bugs before, he made sure to get information about them ever since it was decided that Fabio Planet would be the stage for the elimination round. According to the information he got, the Bug Race was also divided into levels, and it was even more detailed than the human race. The eight footed bugs that were just repelled were called eight-legged insects. They were the most inferior type of bug, cannon fodders. If the cannon fodder of the Bug Race was this strong, then how formidable were the other insects?

The circular formation slowly moved eastward. Not long after they left the transmission formation, the formation flashed as Cultivators were finally allowed to access it. These people were also here to combat the bugs.

And now that Ma Rulong had moved the group to the street, they immediately felt the pressure on them lighten. This was because the bugs were now only able to attack from the left and the right, the north and south positions were blocked by buildings. Under the command of Ma Rulong, they were able to deal with the bugs with not too much effort.

As batches upon batches of Cultivators arrived, the number of bugs began to dwindle. Zhao Hai and the others began to relax. However, they felt confused. They don’t understand how Base Number 5 had been breached by the bugs. Were the bugs this strong?

Several hours later, almost all of the bugs in Base Number 5 were cleared up. Ma Rulong also led Zhao Hai and the others out of the street.

As they went out, they were immediately discovered by the Cultivators. Several Cultivators flew over and couldn’t help but stare at what they saw. One of the Cultivators looked at Ma Rulong and said, “Are you guys from the Machine FIeld?”

Ma Rulong nodded and said, “Right. We came here for the Six Realm Beginner Competition. I didn’t think the bugs would attack this place, so we immediately joined the battle.”

The Cultivator looked at the insect corpses. There were quite a lot of insects here, enough for two small hills worth of corpses. Ma Rulong’s group had to fly up in order to go out.

The Cultivator nodded and said, “Thank you. I apologize for startling you. Please come with me, let me offer you somewhere to stay.”

Ma Rulong nodded, “Thanks. However, please let us collect the corpses of our comrades first.” The Cultivator nodded. Ma Rulong proceeded to instruct team leaders to go to the battlefield and collect the corpses. Then he led Zhao Hai and the others to follow the Cultivator.

A short while after flying, Ma Rulong turned to the Cultivator and said, “May I know Mister’s name? And how did this base get breached?”

The Cultivator replied, “Captain of the Five Elements Team of Base Number 5, Zheng Li. The base has been broken through by a Silverback Gold-winged Insect. Fortunately, Base Number 5 has Nascent Soul Experts stationed inside. They were able to drive that Silverback Gold-winged insect away. However, the base had already been broken through. Bugs began to enter from the breached wall.”

Ma Rulong nodded and then didn’t ask anything more. Before long, Zheng Li led them outside of a courtyard. After landing on the ground, Zheng Li turned to Ma Rulong and said, “This is the place prepared for those who will be undergoing the smelting trial. This should be enough for you to use. Everybody, please take a rest. I’m still busy at the moment, so I can only accompany you for a short time.” Ma Rulong gave Zheng Li a bow and said, “Thanks a lot Mister Zheng.” Zheng Li nodded, then he turned around and fell away. Ma Rulong also turned around and led Zhao Hai and the others into the courtyard.

It was a very big courtyard divided into two. The first area was very large with more than fifty rooms inside. Since the courtyard wasn’t damaged, Ma Rulong immediately assigned people their own rooms. Besides Ma Rulong and the other team leaders, Zhao Hai and the others were assigned to this first area. Those who couldn’t get a room in this area were sent on the second one. Naturally, Xiong Li and the others were in the first courtyard, and their rooms were right next to each other.

Chapter 1218: Fire Dragon Sword’s Seal

Zhao Hai looked around his room and saw that it was very similar to the one he had in Seamount City. It wasn’t very big, just enough for a person to comfortably stay inside. There were also some furniture in the room that can be easily moved around.

When he was done looking around his room, Zhao Hai headed out. Just as he walked out, he saw Xiong Li and the others outside. Seeing Zhao Hai come out, the brothers immediately got together and then sat down in the courtyard. Upon settling down, Xiong Li sighed and said, “I only heard about the bad reputation of Fabio Planet. I didn’t expect it to be this dangerous. We were just given an introduction of what we’ll see.”

Dongfang Yu replied, “It seems like the elimination round wouldn’t be easy. The Machine Field’s participants are in danger. The bugs that attacked us are just some low-level creatures. They couldn’t represent the entire Bug Race. Even so, they are very strong. One needed several sword qi from me in order to die. They’re very difficult to kill. I can’t help but imagine how strong high-level bugs are.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Dongfang Yu and said, “Second Brother, let me borrow your sword tonight. I’ll try to take another look and see if I can do anything to it. If we can find out the secret of the fire dragon sword, then your fighting strength would certainly increase.”

Dongfang Yu nodded. Then Zhao Hai looked at the others and said, “The elimination round will be very dangerous. Therefore, we need to act in unison starting now. No matter where we go, we need to be together.”

The group nodded, then at this time Zhao Hai felt someone walking over. He turned his head and saw that it was Ma Rulong. The group of brothers immediately gave Ma Rulong their greetings.

Ma Rulong nodded, then he motioned for everyone to sit down. After everyone had settled down, he said, “Today’s accident has been unexpected. However, you shouldn’t be surprised about it. Let me remind you that the Cultivation Realm’s bases in Fabio Planet are made like fortresses. Their walls are made entirely of metal engraved with numerous formations. There are also a lot of traps in the base. You could see from this event how strong the Bug Race really are.”

Zhao Hai and the others nodded. Ma Rulong continued, “When I was chatting with Zheng Li, he said that the base has been broken through by a Silverback Gold-winged bug. I just looked it up and read that these SIlverback Gold-winged bugs are one of the most powerful members of the Bug Race. Their power equates to Nascent Soul Experts of the Cultivation Realm. Moreover, the innate skills of the Bug Race are higher. A lone Nascent Soul Expert would never be able to contend with one SIlverback Gold-winged Insect. Although the bug has been chased away by the base’s defenders, they weren’t able to kill it. Fabio Planet is the territory of these bugs, so you need to be careful. That Silverback Gold-winged insect will be holding a grudge. And it isn’t like other humans that would ignore weaker level beings. It has no sense of honor, so it will certainly take revenge on every human it sees. This elimination round is now much more dangerous, you need to watch out.”

Zhao Hai and the others nodded. They also knew how dangerous this elimination round has become. They wouldn’t dare treat it lightly.

Ma Rulong looked at the group for a moment before he whispered, “I have an eye on your small group. In this elimination round, you need to stay together and ensure your safety first. Even if you see others being attacked by someone or something that is too strong, take care of your safety first. Understood?”

Upon hearing Ma Rulong, Zhao Hai and the others couldn’t help but stare. Ma Rulong’s words were very simple. He was telling Zhao Hai and the others that if they met people who were in danger, then they shouldn’t go and save them. Zhao Hai and the others didn’t expect Ma Rulong to say this.

Ma Rulong saw their expressions, he couldn’t help but smile bitterly as he said, “It’s not because I want to end them and cut off their progress. But because of the Bug Race and the Cultivators, I need you all to survive. The Machine Field needs you to fight for benefits.”

When Zhao Hai and the others heard the unwillingness in Ma Rulong’s tone, they couldn’t help but nod. Ma Rulong sighed as he stood up and said, “Have a good rest. I’ll provide you with information about the other top 100 participants as well as the Bug Race tomorrow. It’s best if you keep them in mind.”

Zhao Hai and the others stood up and gave Ma Rulong a salute. Ma Rulong turned around and left. Looking at Ma Rulong’s departing back, Zhao Hai and the others couldn’t help but turn solemn.

Ma Rulong’s words represented the aspiration of a lot of people in the Machine Field. They paid too much in order to compete with the Cultivation Realm. Zhao Hai suddenly felt the burden on his shoulder getting heavier.

But what Zhao Hai and the others didn’t think was that while Ma Rulong was talking to them, someone was paying attention in the distance. And in their eyes was hate and envy.

Naturally, the owner of these eyes were Streep. In his view, Ma Rulong was kindly talking to Zhao Hai and whispering secret information to him. Streep was thinking that this privilege should belong to him. But now it has been snatched by Zhao Hai.

Actually, being able to chat with Ma Rulong wasn’t anything great. Other people wouldn’t care much about it, after all Ma Rulong treated everyone well.

But to Streep, such a thing was an honor. Streep wanted to be the center of attention. He enjoyed being the center of attention until Zhao Hai appeared. Zhao Hai snatched Streep’s reputation. Now, everyone was looking at Zhao Hai, nobody was looking at Streep.

Because of this, Streep envied and hated Zhao Hai very much. But since Xiong Li and the others were always by Zhao Hai’s side, and that all of them weren’t weak, Streep wasn’t given the chance to deal with Zhao Hai.

However, Streep didn’t make his hatred towards Zhao Hai visible. This was because he was waiting for the opportunity to take Zhao Hai’s life.

Streep believed that an opportunity would definitely arrive. Especially because they were in Fabio Planet. This was an extremely dangerous place where countless Experts of the Cultivation Realm were killed.

Not only Zhao Hai, Streep also wanted to take Xiong Li, Dongfang Yu, Li Kuangren, and Sun Fei’s life. Streep wanted everyone that had been close to Zhao Hai dead.

After giving Zhao Hai a vicious look, Streep left. He went to find other participants in order to form a team.

Streep was not a fool. He knew that he needed to form a team for the elimination round. This way, he would have a much better chance in surviving. Therefore, he needed to find teammates. Even if these people weren’t strong, as long as he teamed up with them, they could be sacrificed whenever necessary.

But as he turned around to leave, Streep was unable to discover Zhao Hai looking at his direction for a brief moment. Initially, Zhao Hai was unable to see Streep. But after a murderous wisp went through Streep’s eyes, Zhao Hai was able to notice him. Zhao Hai was extremely sensitive to killing intent, so he quickly took note of it.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t linger too long in that direction. He immediately ordered Cai’er look into the matter. Cai’er took through the recordings and saw Streep looking over for some time. It also managed to capture the murderous look in Streep’s eyes.

Zhao Hai already placed Streep in his to-kill list. As long as he has a chance, then he wouldn’t let Streep go. Therefore, he didn’t care about Streep’s murderous intent.

The day quickly turned dark. Zhao Hai and the others left Seamount City at a late time. And then there was the battle. So most of the day has already passed.

After looking at the sky, Zhao Hai invited Xiong Li and the others to his room to have a drink. Xiong Li and the others quickly understood Zhao Hai. It was time for Dongfang Yu to hand his weapon over.

When the group entered the room, they drank for a while before Dongfang Yu left his fire dragon sword behind. Then the group returned to their own rooms.

After everyone else left, Zhao Hai immediately returned to the Space. This time, he didn’t try to investigate the fire dragon sword using his spiritual force. This was because he had been attacked by it the last time. This time, he plans to have the fire dragon sword go through the scanner to be analyzed. He intends to see what’s going on with the sword.

Zhao Hai took the fire dragon sword to the Space. And instead of heading to the villa, Zhao Hai went directly to the Universal Scanner. After the recent upgrade, the capability of the scanner and the processing machine had been increased. Since then, their functions had exceeded Zhao Hai’s imagination.

Whether it be potions or weapons, as long as Zhao Hai places a request, then the processing machine would immediately make it. Moreover, its output was of the highest quality.

There was no need to talk about the Universal Scanner. Even if Zhao Hai placed a lump of soil into the scanner, it could instantly identify every component, and what he could do to it. The scanner was currently skirting towards going against heaven’s will.

Seeing Zhao Hai head towards the scanner, Laura and the others also walked out of the villa in order to go to the scanner. They would accompany Zhao Hai to wait for the result.

Not too long after the fire dragon sword was placed in the scanner, the scanner issued a prompt, “Sealed sword detected. Sword is made up of fire dragon ash and fine goldsand. Weapon has already recognized its own host. Host can now use Everpresent Ancient Sand to weather down the seal and uncover the sword’s true form.”

Zhao Hai stared. Actually, he didn’t expect that he could remove the fire dragon sword’s seal. He quickly took out Everpresent Ancient Sand and rubbed it over the sword. As he was rubbing the sword with the sand, he was also watching the change that was going on. As the sword was being rubbed with the Everpresent Ancient Sand, it became redder and redder and was also becoming brighter. Three batches of everpresent ancient sand later, the fire dragon sword flew out of Zhao Hai’s hand. A dragon’s roar came out of the sword before a red dragon flew out. The fire dragon flew round and round the sky as though it was venting its anger about being sealed for a long time.

It took a while for the red dragon to disappear. But when it vanished, the fire dragon sword slowly fell down. This time, the fire dragon sword was different compared to before. In the past, the fire dragon sword was only red, with no other redeeming quality. But now, the fire dragon sword was emanating anger and was now fully exuding its imposing manner. The sword hilt of the fire dragon sword had also changed. The entire aesthetic flowed more smoothly compared to before. The hilt of the sword was the dragon tail, the dragon claws became the cross-guard, and then the dragon head extended up into the blade as though it was swallowing it.

Zhao Hai rubbed the sword gently. But he also felt a burst of resistance from the sword body. It seems like the fire dragon sword was also a genuine treasure and had already recognized Dongfang Yu as its owner.

Zhao Hai didn’t envy Dongfang Yu, after all, he already had Liquid Silver. There was no weapon more suited to him than liquid silver. Although the fire dragon sword was good, it still falls short compared to his staff.

Zhao Hai stored the fire dragon sword before he turned to Laura and the others and said, “How about we get some of those bugs for the Space?”

Naturally, Laura and the others had already thought about this problem. Laura smiled and said, “We made an initial analysis about them through the scanner. The results are already in. We can talk about it inside.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he entered the villa alongside everyone. Then Laura immediately took out the results of the analysis.

Although the Space had yet to get a bug, a video recording was made about them during Zhao Hai’s battle. This was enough for the scanner to make some analysis about them. The results state that the Bug race was a race that had a strong evolutionary and reproductive abilities. When not under stress, their evolution wouldn’t be quick. But once their race was placed in danger of extinction, an explosive evolutionary chain would occur. They could also absorb other beings in order to improve their gene pool. This evolutionary ability was very terrifying.

The Universal Scanner’s results advised Zhao Hai to acquire these bugs at all costs. The Space can extract these bugs’ evolutionary might and then add it to the Space’s creatures. This way, the Space’s creatures could evolve further, improving the Space’s combat capabilities!

Zhao Hai was shocked about the result of the analysis. He didn’t expect the Space to have this strong of an appraisal towards the Bug Race. However, he changed his thoughts and began to relax. If the Bug Race didn’t have this ability, then the Cultivators should have long destroyed them. But now, Fabio Planet remained to be the Bug Race’s territory. Human activity on this planet was at an extreme minimum. One could see how formidable the bugs were from this point. The Cultivation realm had destroyed numerous planets, but they had yet to take Fabio Planet. Now, Zhao Hai couldn’t wait to introduce the bugs to the Space!

Chapter 1219: Suddenly Closing Up

The next morning, Dongfang Yu got up and sat in the courtyard. He kept looking at Zhao Hai’s door. It can be said that he was anxious.

The fire dragon sword had been his solid partner ever since he came to the Machine Field. But at the same time, Dongfang Yu knew that the fire dragon sword that he had been using wasn’t the true fire dragon sword. Nobody told him about this, he just felt it.

In fact the Yan family couldn’t tell him about this. This was because the Yan Family didn’t know much about the fire dragon sword. The sword was inadvertently obtained by the Yan Family, so it had always been in the External Hall for ascenders to use. Every time the master of the sword died, they would retrieve the sword and then pass it on to another person. This generation, the sword landed in Dongfang Yu’s hands. Nobody knew how many owners it had before him.

Dongfang Yu didn’t know if he shared this feeling with the previous owners of the fire dragon sword. But this feeling was real, and it was very unusual.

Dongfang Yu gave Zhao Hai his fire dragon sword because Zhao Hai was his close friend. Also, it was because Zhao Hai had this mysterious feeling about him.

Zhao Hai had too many secrets. He was able to reforge Xiong Li and Li Kuangren’s weapons. There were also the formation sets he gave Sun Fei. All of these made Zhao hai even more mysterious in Dongfang Yu’s eyes.

It was because of this that Dongfang Yu handed over the fire dragon sword to Zhao Hai. He hopes that Zhao Hai would help him unlock the secret of the fire dragon sword. He doesn’t want to unravel the sword’s secret because he wanted to be stronger. Instead, it was because the fire dragon sword was his most important partner.

At this time, the door to Zhao Hai’s room suddenly opened. Zhao Hai appeared and then beckoned Dongfang Yu. Dongfang Yu immediately ran towards Zhao Hai’s room.

Upon seeing Dongfang Yu’s appearance, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “What happened Second Brother, you didn’t have a good rest last night?” Dongfang Yu, embarrassed, nodded as he replied, “Yeah, I can’t sleep. Ever since I got my hands on the fire dragon sword, I always wanted to find out about its secrets. Unfortunately, I haven’t been successful. I believed that you would succeed, so I couldn’t sleep last night.”

Zhao Hai gave an understanding nod. Then he smiled faintly and then moved his hand. He took the fire dragon sword out and then held it out towards Dongfang Yu.

Dongfang Yu was totally dumbfounded, he was totally absorbed by the changes to the fire dragon sword. He was moved deep inside. At this moment, the fire dragon sword in Zhao Hai’s hand shook, then it flew out from Zhao Hais’ hand and then went towards Dongfang Yu. The next moment, the fire dragon sword acted like a naughty child that was spinning around Dongfang Yu. The scene looked like a child being excited by the sight of its parent.

Dongfang Yu could feel the fire dragon sword’s happiness. He couldn’t help but reach out towards the sword. The sword also acted like a bird going back to nest as it flew directly to Dongfang Yu’s hand.

Just as Dongfang Yu gripped the fire dragon sword, the sword suddenly emitted a red light that wrapped his body. Dongfang Yu stood in place as he closed his eyes, looking as though he fell asleep.

Upon seeing this, Zhao Hai knew that the fire dragon sword was communicating with Dongfang Yu. He immediately left the room and then gently closed the door before guarding it.

Before long, Xiong Li and the others had gone out of their rooms. When they saw Zhao Hai outside his own room, they couldn’t help but get confused. In the past, it was them who would wait outside Zhao Hai’s room, but now Zhao Hai was the one doing it. What changed?

Xiong Li and the others immediately walked over, looking confused at Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai smiled faintly before pointing towards his room and saying, “Second Brother’s fire dragon sword has been unsealed. It is now communicating with him. I don’t want his communication to be cut short so I guarded the room.”

Xiong Li and the others just nodded and didn’t say anything more. The group proceeded to sit down outside Zhao Hai’s room and then chatted in hushed voices. Zhao Hai looked at Sun Fei and said, “Little Fei, how is your research in formation sets doing?” Sun Fei happily nodded and said, “I have learned all of the sets. I can now use them all. They only differ by how proficient I am. Also, Fourth Brother’s formations are easier to learn than the ones I had before. It also consumes less spiritual force, and has more power. It is magnificent.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Practice well. Be more familiar with those formations sets first. When your spiritual force is strong enough, then I’ll teach you more formation sets. Also, if we have the time, I’ll let you experience weapon shattering. What do you think?” Sun Fei excitedly agreed.

At this time, Ma Rulong walked out of his room. When he saw Zhao Hai and the others together, he came over and asked, “Why are you here? Is something wrong?”

Zhao Hai and the others immediately stood up and then gave Ma Rulong a salute. Then Zhao Hai said, “I thank team leader Ma for the concern. Nothing is wrong. Brother Dongfang just had a sudden breakthrough, so he is currently closing up inside my room. But I believe it wouldn’t take a long time for him to come out. We don’t want anyone to disturb him, so we’re guarding here.”

Ma Rulong looked at Zhao Hai’s room and said, “Alright. I hope he wakes up soon. I planned to take you all out today to see the bugs outside. However, I reckon the bugs that attacked yesterday are still in the vicinity. So let’s just take today as a rest day. We’ll take a look at the situation tomorrow.”

Zhao Hai and the others nodded. Ma Rulong waved his hand before turning away. Zhao Hai looked at the door of his room and said, “I hope Second Brother can wake up soon so that he can participate in the elimination round. Otherwise, he wouldn’t be able to face the Yan Family.” Xiong Li and the others nodded. Although they were prepared to separate from their families and be independent, there was a premise. And this premise was that they would gain great achievements in the competition. Only then would they have any qualifications to negotiate with their families. Any other outcome would just be empty talk, their families would never let them go.

Although Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid of the families of the Machine Field, he also doesn’t want to annoy them. The Machine Field had existed for several thousand years. Its foundation was adequately solid. Annoying them wouldn’t be a wise decision.

Zhao Hai doesn’t like the trouble that comes with annoying people. It was just unnecessary trouble. Therefore, Zhao Hai hoped Dongfang Yu can wake up before the start of the elimination round. Otherwise, things would be troublesome.

Due to the recent attack, people from Base Number 5 were all very tense. Once in a while, Zhao Hai and the others could see Cultivators flying in the sky, back and forth in a hurry.

However, there wasn’t any appearance of bugs inside the base, which made them feel relieved. A day passed by quickly. Zhao Hai and the others were still outside the door, but Dongfang Yu remained silent.

In the evening, Zhao Hai and the others drank a few more glasses. However, they were only doing tastings. They weren’t alcoholics, they wouldn’t get drunk every day.

It was already late when the group finished drinking. Zhao Hai had Xiong Li and the others rest. Meanwhile, he stayed outside his door and meditated in place.

Since Ma Rulong had sent word in advance, nobody came to disturb Zhao Hai. People were curious about why Dongfang Yu suddenly closed up after going to Zhao Hai’s room. What secrets did the two of them share? There were a lot of evil-minded people that were speculating with negative thoughts.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t care about these people. He continued to defend outside of his door. To be exact, he was guarding against Streep.

Zhao Hai couldn’t forget the killing gaze that Streep looked at him with. He was afraid that Streep would do something to Dongfang Yu. Although it can be said that he could just use the Space to stop streep, then this was the same as going public with his enmity with Streep. Zhao Hai didn’t want to do this. And if Streep died, then people would be suspicious about him. He doesn’t want to attract such suspicions.

Time slowly passed by. Zhao Hai was still sitting cross-legged outside his room, looking asleep. Then suddenly, Zhao Hai’s eyes opened up. He quickly stood up and then rushed towards the door to Ma Rulong’s room.

Although it seems like Zhao Hai was asleep, he was actually using his spiritual force to pay attention to the changes happening around him. He was also paying attention to the situation outside Base Number 5. He remembers Ma Rulong saying that the silverback gold-winged bug was vengeful. So he was afraid that the bug would attack the base once more. Just now, Zhao Hai sensed a large number of bugs outside Base Number 5. These bugs had yet to enter the trap region of the base. However, every single one of them were looking very aggressive. It was clear that they were preparing to rush the base.

Upon seeing this situation, Zhao Hai knew that he needed to look for Ma Rulong. This way, Ma Rulong could call everyone and have them prepare for battle.

As soon as Zhao Hai arrived outside Ma Rulong’s door, Ma Rulong’s voice was heard, “Who?!”

Zhao Hai quickly said, “Team leader, the bugs is going to attack Base Number 5. Call everyone and have them prepare.”

The door was opened, Ma Rulong still looked at bit shaggy. He looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Are you sure?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I am. They’re going to begin soon.’ Ma Rulong quickly went out of his room before shouting, “Everyone, gather!” His voice spread out like thunder in a silent night. Even deaf people would be able to hear him, not to mention experts who were still on edge.

It didn’t take long before the courtyard sprung with activity. Everyone went out of their own room. And when they saw Ma Rulong’s serious expression, their internal alert levels couldn’t help but rise up.

Ma Rulong looked at everyone and said, “Bugs are about to attack Base Number 5. Everyone, prepare.” Everyone stared, then they looked confusedly at Ma Rulong. Naturally, they had a hard time believing Ma Rulong. If bugs were really going to attack Base Number 5, then the base’s alarms should have already sounded out.

But just as people were thinking about this, the alarms sounded out. This caused everyone’s expression to change.

Chapter 1220: Zhao Hai, Becoming Bigger

Along with the blaring alarms, the entire base moved with activity. One by one, Cultivators stepped on their swords and flew up. Some were also stepping on clouds and other treasures. Each one of them showed their techniques as they flew towards the walls.

When he saw this, Ma Rulong’s expression changed as he cursed inside. He wanted to call everyone over and then lead them towards the transmission formation. He hoped that they could leave the base as soon as possible before the bugs attacked. But now it seems like this was impossible.

It wasn’t like someone would block them if they decided to leave. But as long as the base was in a state of alarm, the transmission formations could only allow entry to the base, not exit. In this case, there was no way for them to leave.

As Ma Rulong was cursing inside, he turned his head to everyone and said, “Everyone prepare to fight. Remember to stick together at all times. Nobody is allowed to go on their own.”

Meanwhile, Zhao Hai looked at his own room. Dongfang Yu had yet to come out. Zhao Hai turned his head to Xiong Li and the others and said, “Boss Xiong, stay here for a while. I’ll go to the wall and check the situation. If the city walls are breached, I will return as quickly as possible.”

As the group was talking, Ma Rulong turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, did Dongfang Yu come out?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “He didn’t. Team Leader, I want Xiong Li and the others to remain here. I’ll follow everyone else to go to the wall.”

Ma Rulong looked at Xiong Li and the others, then he turned to Zhao Hai and then nodded and said, “Alright, have the three of them stay behind. You follow us to the wall.”

Zhao Hai looked at Xiong Li and said, “Boss Xiong, I will leave this place to you. Please protect Second Brother.” Then after he said that, he followed everyone else to leave.

As the group left the courtyard, they saw large quantities of Cultivators flying towards the wall. These people were all flying in the sky, nobody was walking on the ground. Moreover, each one of them were fast.

Ma Rulong looked at this situation as he said, “We should fly as well. Remember to keep the formation intact. Nobody is allowed to fall behind.” After saying that, he flew up first with everyone else following behind. But since Ma Rulong wanted to maintain the formation, they weren’t advancing quickly.

Only when they flew up did they see that the city walls were already as bright as daylight. The Cultivators were already dealing with the bugs. Magical weapons were flying all over the sky. The roars of both bugs and humans filled the entire base.

Ma Rulong led everyone to the wall. In any case, they wouldn’t be able to leave the base so they should just help with the fight. If the base gets taken down, then everyone else would follow along with it.

They were the last group to reach the wall. At this time, the wall had been turned into a huge meat grinder. From time to time, bodies belonging to both humans and bugs were falling from the sky.

The walls were full of Cultivators. There were also a lot of Cultivators at the back. It seems like the Cultivators learned that in order to deal with such an offense, they would need reserve troops to replenish the line.

As Ma Rulong and the others were flying over, Zheng Li’s group suddenly got close. Zheng Li looked at Ma Rulong’s group as a flash of disdain couldn’t help but go through his eyes. Then he said, “Everyone, thanks for coming over to help. Please take a rest below. We don’t know when this wave of bugs would end. You’ll be coming in on the second round.”

Naturally, Ma Rulong was able to see Zheng Li’s expression. But he didn’t say anything as he just nodded and said, “Since we came here to help, we will follow your orders. You can rest assured.” then he led Zhao Hai and the others to land on the ground.

Zheng Li also landed on the ground. He looked at Zhao Hai and the others and said, “Is everyone from the Machine Field here?”

Ma Rulong shook his head and said, “We’ve left four behind. One of them is closing up while the rest are guarding him. Besides those four, everyone is here.”

Zheng Li nodded, then he looked at the city wall, his expression was quite heavy as he said, “I don’t know what happened to the bugs this time. They suddenly attacked us in a frenzy. It’s difficult to keep the wall. I think there’s going to be a battle on the streets again.”

Ma Rulong’s expression turned heavy as well. He opened his mouth and said, “Mister Zheng. Our Machine Field’s Mages are very suitable for wide-scale attacks. How about you let us try and help?”

Zheng Li stared, then he gently knit his brows as he said, “Forget it Mister Ma. I thank your intentions, but the people on the walls are currently in great coordination with each other. If you suddenly join, then you might disrupt their rhythm. It’s not a good time, maybe later.”

Ma Rulong didn’t say anything. He looked at the other Cultivators who were sitting cross-legged on the ground before turning to everyone else and said, “Sit down and rest.” Zhao Hai and the others didn’t delay and immediately sat down.

Zheng Li saw this and then turned to Ma Rulong and said, “Mister Ma, I’ll be going to the frontlines to take a look. Farewell.” Then his figure quickly disappeared.

Just as Zheng Li left, Zhao Hai suddenly heard discussions happening behind him. One of them said, “Look at his impatient appearance, he really thinks he’s great.” Another said, “Right, these Cultivators are all arrogant. They always think that they’re far better than us.” These words caused Zhao Hai to gently knit his brows.

Zhao Hai glanced at these people and couldn’t help but sigh deep inside. These geniuses from the Machine Field couldn’t fully understand the gap between them and the Cultivators. Although they were speaking in hushed tones, the Cultivators nearby could still hear it. Once they go into battle, they would go together with the Cultivators. If these Cultivators wanted to deal with them, then they would have no choice but to die.

Naturally, Ma Rulong had the same thought. He stood up and said, “Everyone be quiet. At this time, it’s better if you adjust yourselves and keep your best state. Don’t chew your tongues there like a talkative woman.”

Ma Rulong’s voice was very effective, the group immediately turned peaceful. These people weren’t afraid of offending the Cultivators. In their opinion, as long as they attend the competition and then return home, they would never meet these people again. If they offended them, then that’s it. However, they were afraid of Ma Rulong. Ma Rulong’s position in the Machine Field was quite prestigious. If they offended him, then even if they return to the Machine Field, Ma Rulong could still deal with them.

After seeing everyone turn quiet, Ma Rulong turned to look at Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai was sat there with his eyes closed, just like a Cultivator meditating. Ma Rulong couldn’t help but nod. His appreciation for Zhao Hai increased once more. Zhao Hai understood what needs to be done and knew what to do at what situation. Such talent only needed time in order to become a true expert.

However, Ma Rulong didn’t say anything as he just stood still and looked at the direction of the wall. The fighting was very fierce. Besides Cultivators, the walls also had magic cannons installed. But a few of them were in operation, a lot had already been damaged.

When he saw this, Ma Rulong couldn’t help but feel heavy. These cannons were certainly destroyed during the previous bug attack. The base didn’t have enough time to repair them all.

If these magic cannons were operational, then its possible for the bugs to be held back. Without these cannons and just relying on Cultivators, Base Number 5 is truly in danger.

Upon thinking about this, Ma Rulong couldn’t help but curse inside. He really couldn’t understand why his luck was this bad. As soon as they arrived at Base Number 5, it was attacked. And then there was this.

The fight on the city wall continued. Moreover, it got more and more intense. The Cultivators had already suffered heavy losses. It was time to replenish the defenders.

Seeing the Cultivators around them getting fewer and fewer, the Machine Field’s people couldn’t help but turn anxious. They began to whisper to each other with expressions of fear.

At this time, Zheng Li arrived. Ma Rulong quickly greeted him. Zheng Li looked at the people from the Machine Field and said, “Mister Ma, please lead your people to support the eastern wall immediately. I’m afraid it would collapse soon.”

Ma Rulong nodded, “Alright, Mister Zheng. Please guide us.” Zheng Li nodded, then he turned around and flew. Ma Rulong followed closely behind as they flew towards the eastern wall.

Seeing the situation in the eastern wall, Ma Rulong couldn’t help but suck in cold air. The eastern wall was in dire straits. Some bugs had already climbed up the wall. The Cultivator casualties were more than normal.

Ma Rulong couldn’t blank out now, so he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, use wide-scale magic to clear an area for us to land.”

Although Zhao Hai paused for a moment, he still nodded and then waved his hand. A magic staff appeared before Zhao Hai waved it and sent his ten thousand fiery arrows towards the eastern wall.

Even if Zhao Hai didn’t use astral qi, he still integrated weapon shattering to this formation. One could easily imagine the might of this ten thousand fiery arrows. Arrows rained nonstop towards the bugs. Loud explosions followed closely behind as well as splashes of flesh and blood. Zhao Hai’s explosive formation set caused the bug advance to slow down.

Right after this, Ma Rulong loudly said, “Alright, Warriors, head out. Deal with the bugs on the wall as soon as possible. Mages, use your magic to block the bugs outside the wall. Don’t allow any of them to approach.” Then after he said that, Ma Rulong took out his ghosthead broadsword and then threw himself towards the wall. Under the leadership of the other team leaders, the Mages proceeded to launch magic towards the outside of the city.

However, the magic attacks of these people weren’t much. Even level 5 Mages dealt less damage than Zhao Hai’s magic. Naturally, this disparity was very clear in the eyes of the nearby Zheng Li.

Zheng Li noticed Zhao Hai because his magic was very powerful. It even compares to large-scale magics used by Cultivators. In his mind, if everyone from the Machine Field was like Zhao Hai, then it would be too terrifying!

Chapter 1221: Immensely Powerful Aura

But after seeing the spells that others launched, Zheng Li understood what was going on. He couldn’t help but pay more attention towards Zhao Hai. He discovered that Zhao Hai wasn’t a team leader. This meant that he was a participant. A participant being stronger than a team leader, this was too astonishing.

However, he couldn’t observe for too long. After giving Zhao Hai a glance, Zheng Li left and entered the battle. The fight outside had become very violent. The bugs seem to be endless.

Zhao Hai continually sent out hundred layer formations. The bugs outside slowed down. This doesn’t mean that the bugs stopped attacking. It was just that Zhao Hai had already killed the fastest bugs outside the wall.

Upon seeing this situation, Zhao Hai relaxed. Although using hundred layer formations couldn’t tire him out, doing so would attract attention towards him. If he continues his attacks, everyone would pay attention to him soon. He doesn’t want that to happen. He was already eye-catching enough.

Zhao Hai stopped firing magic, he closed his eyes, and then drank a bottle of potion. It looked as if he was recovering his energy. This made Zheng Li, who was paying attention to Zhao Hai, feel relieved.

Zheng Li was counting, and Zhao Hai had fired a total of eight 100-layer formation spells. These eight spells weren’t the same, which meant that these spells weren’t dependent on Zhao Hai’s staff but instead in Zhao Hai’s spiritual force. Even if his staff was a treasure, only a formidable spiritual force could allow him to fire off eight 100-layer formations. This was an astonishing feat. Even average level 5 Mages couldn’t achieve this.

It was good that Zhao Hai was now catching up his breath. Otherwise, Zheng Li would have to reevaluate how he sees Zhao Hai. In fact, it wasn’t just Zheng Li, other people were also looking at Zhao Hai in surprise. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be so fierce. Sending out eight 100-layer formations almost instantaneously, how much spiritual force does this require? They were astonished when they thought about it.

Taking advantage of the bugs slowing down, the Cultivators as well as Ma Rulong and the others dealt with the bugs on the walls. However, they didn’t celebrate, they knew that another wave of offense was coming soon.

Although the other Mages of the Machine Field were also firing spells towards the bugs, their effects weren’t very good. Their power wasn’t as great as Zhao Hai. As long as Zhao Hai’s attacks reach the bugs, they would be heavily injured if not killed. On the other hand, the other Mages could only give wounds to the bugs, they couldn’t kill them.

The life force of these bugs was very strong. As long as they weren’t hit in a vital part, they could still continue to fight for a long time. Because of this, the other Mages weren’t able to deal with the bugs effectively.

Ma Rulong also noticed this point. He knew that the spells of the others weren’t necessarily bad. They were using wide-scale magic so their attacking power was naturally dispersed. It was natural that they weren’t able to kill the bugs.

This also allowed Ma Rulong to see the difference between Zhao Hai’s spells and the spells of other people.

Upon thinking about this, Ma Rulong couldn’t help but shake his head. Then he loudly commanded, “Everyone, change to single-target attacks. There’s no need to use wide-scale attacks.” Upon hearing Ma Rulong, the Mages couldn’t help but feel their faces redden. They knew that they lost face this time. They couldn’t help but get embarrassed. Then they changed to single-target attacks and achieved better effects.

Not only the Mages, even the Cultivators were also using single-target attacks. However, their attacks were coming from magic treasures, different to the Mages and Warriors that use Magic and Sword Qi.

Since the bugs that had climbed up into the wall had already been killed, the Cultivators found that it was now easier to deal with the bugs. Ma Rulong paid attention and saw that even if the Cultivators were using different treasures to make numerous attacks, their effects were still much better compared to magic spells and sword qi attacks.

The Machine Field’s spells and sword qi seemed like bullets fired from a gun. Once the bullet has been fired, they could no longer be controlled. If it was shot down, then it would be impossible for it to injure the enemy. After all, bullets could not make a turn mid-flight.

The Cultivators’ weapons were different. Once their weapons were released, they could still be controlled. It was like a missile that can be remotely controlled to chase the target. With more control over their attacks, the Cultivators were able to deal more damage.

Although the people on the walls were able to block the bug attack, Zhao Hai wasn’t optimistic. It seems like the bugs were endless. Moreover, only low-level bugs were attacking. If a higher level bug appears, then what would happen?

Whether it be Cultivators, Mages, or Warriors, none of them would be able to stay in peak condition for a very long time. If no reinforcements came, then Base Number 5 would be in deep danger.

As he was thinking about this, the transmission formation of the base flashed. Then a large number of Cultivators emerged. These Cultivators immediately flew towards the city walls. Naturally, this flash couldn’t be hidden from the defenders. A cheer erupted as the attacks became faster.

Upon seeing this situation, Zhao Hai relaxed. He closed his eyes and continued to pretend to be recovering. Just like him, there were also several Cultivators, Mages, and Warriors recovering their energy. The reinforcements had already reached the walls. At this moment, there was no longer and division between Cultivators and people from the Machine Field. The situation was now purely humans versus bugs.

Seeing that the walls had been well-defended, Zhao Hai thoroughly felt relieved. Meanwhile, even if he was still closing his eyes, he was actually paying attention to the cultivators. He wanted to take a look at their offensive strength.

One has to say that the Cultivators were indeed very strong. Although they had numerous strange and unusual magical artifacts, once these artifacts were used properly, their lethality couldn’t be underestimated. The attacks made by these artifacts were much more powerful than Mage spells.

Moreover, Zhao Hai discovered that the attacks made by these Cultivators were much stronger than Li Chuchen’s. Li Chuchen might have a lot of attacks that were swift and fierce, but these Cultivators from Base Number 5 were on a different level. They were unforgiving in their attacks, all of it were meant to kill. Each action they do were all done with an intent to eliminate the enemy. Zhao Hai knew that this can only come forth through innumerable combat situations. In summary, the experiences they gained were kill, kill, kill!

Zhao Hai was aware that it was these kinds of people that were dangerous. People like Li Chuchen might be undefeatable, but you can still retreat when faced against them. But as for Base Number 5’s Cultivators, if you weren’t dead, then you would be severely injured.

Just as Zhao Hai was paying attention to the artifacts that these Cultivators were using, a powerful imposing aura was suddenly felt from outside the city. This was the most powerful imposing aura that Zhao Hai had ever felt in his life.

Zhao Hai felt his heart turn tighter. This imposing aura certainly wasn’t coming from a person. This aura was as firm as a mountain, but was as wild as a savage beast. Even savage people couldn’t let out this kind of aura. This was certainly coming from the Bug Race.

It wasn’t only Zhao Hai who felt this imposing aura, the others did as well. Everyone’s faces changed color immediately. None of these people were ignorant, they all knew what this aura represented.

It was a powerful bug, a very hard to deal with creature. If the bug race did indeed send a powerful bug to attack the base, then the base was truly in danger.

While everyone was thinking about this, the danger had already arrived. The bugs that had just slowed down seem to have turned crazy. All of them frantically rushed to the base. It didn’t take long before all of the walls were in a dangerous situation.

Zhao Hai looked at the situation and couldn’t help but sigh. He had a feeling that Base Number 5 could no longer be defended. He immediately sent forth several hundred-layer formations. Then he moved towards Ma Rulong and then whispered, “Team leader, we couldn’t defend this place anymore. Make everyone prepare to evacuate, just in case.”

Ma Rulong looked at the situation around them, then he sighed and said, “I also want to retreat, but we cannot fall back now. If we do, the battle will be taken to the streets. We have less advantage there. Let’s defend here for a while, then afterwards…..”

Just as Ma Rulong said that, the imposing aura sped up towards the base. Everyone’s expression turned dark. They knew that the powerful bug has come!

Zhao Hai looked at the base before turning his head to Ma Rulong and said, “Team Leader, I’ll head back first to check on my brothers.”

Ma Rulong looked at Zhao Hai and then sighed before nodding. He was beginning to feel despair at this point. Outside the base was an inexhaustible sea of bugs. And now there was a very powerful bug approaching the base. With only them here, it was impossible to defend the base. The only thing they could do now was to do their best to hold on for several minutes.

The other Cultivators were also thinking the same way. To be honest, these Cultivators cherish their lives more than ordinary people. They worked hard and even robbed in order to become immortals. Even if it was clear that there was no hope, they would still not give up knowing that they can live for a few more minutes.

Zhao Hai didn’t think about the situation so much. He knew that he wouldn’t die. But he was in a dilemma. He was now deciding whether he should take Xiong Li and the others with him and leave, or to show his power and deal with the bugs. If he uses his strength to deal with the bugs, then the base would surely be saved. However, he could no longer act low-key in the future.

On the other hand, if he took Xiong Li and the others to leave, then they would be able to discover the Space. This was his biggest secret. If this goes known, then he would have no place in the World of Cultivation. Whether it be in the Machine Field or wherever else, people would want to catch him.

Of course, Zhao Hai wouldn’t be caught. However, it would be very hard for him to gain a foothold in the World of Cultivation. This was the reason why Zhao Hai was in a dilemma.

Although it wasn’t a big deal if Zhao Hai reveals his power, one shouldn’t forget that it had been less than a year since he had ascended. If he showed outstanding prowess, then wouldn’t people be suspicious?

But when he thought about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smack his own head. He suddenly remembered something. It wouldn’t be a problem if his strength suddenly increased. This was because the Ashley Family told him that if worse comes to worst, then he could use Liquid Silver. Liquid Silver was a weapon of legends. It should be able to keep attention off of him for a while.

Also, after the Six Realm Beginner Competition, people would be aware of his strength. Even if people wanted to deal with him, the scale wouldn’t be as bad.

With this thought in mind, Zhao Hai began to relax. He also understood that being too low-key wouldn’t be good. As long as you have enough strength, then you would be able to call the wind and summon the rain. Even if people wanted to covet your treasure, nobody would dare make a move. On the other hand, if you don’t have the strength, then even if you don’t have anything, people would still catch you and turn you into a slave. This was the case with non-practitioners in the Cultivation Realm.

At this time, Zhao Hai arrived at the courtyard where they were staying in. Xiong Li and the others were eagerly defending the place. Dongfang Yu was still silent. Zhao Hai used his spiritual force to scan the room only to be repelled. This caused him to be startled. He immediately asked Cai’er to look into what’s happening in the room.

Before long, Cai’er reported what was happening. Dongfang Yu can currently cross-legged on the ground. His entire body was red, probably at a crucial point in his cultivation.

Upon hearing Cai’er, Zhao Hai’s facial color changed. He knew that they could no longer leave. This was the most important moment in Dongfang Yu’s cultivation. If Dongfang Yu was interrupted, then he might be heavily injured.

At this moment, Xiong Li and the others also saw Zhao Hai. They quickly flew towards him. Then Xiong Li worriedly asked, “Little Hai, how is the wall doing? Where did that powerful aura come from? Can we hold on?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “I’m afraid we couldn’t hold on. And even worse, we cannot disturb Second Brother now, otherwise his cultivation would be severely damaged. It seems like we really have to go all out this time.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the color in Xiong Li and the others’ faces changed. Xiong Li immediately said, “Alright, let’s head to the wall. We need to block off those bugs.”

However, Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “You going there is useless. You might as well continue defending this place. If a bug comes, kill them all. Leave the walls to me.” Then his body disappeared as he quickly returned to the wall.

Chapter 1222: Silverback Gold-winged Bug

Zhao Hai calmly returned to the city. He looked at the distance and felt the powerful aura closing in fast. It wouldn’t take long before it would arrive. The expressions on everyone on the walls weren’t good. They knew that when the immensely powerful bug gets close to the base, then that would be their end.

The insects outside were still coming in. Everyone was doing their best to resist. However, it can be seen that they were doing their final struggles.

Ma Rulong saw Zhao Hai, but he wasn’t in the mood to manage him right now. Although he didn’t stop attacking, the color of his face was already pale. This was partly because he was tired, and partly because he was worried.

Ma Rulong brought the elites of the Machine Field in the past five years with him. And some were even the strongest people in the last decade. If all of them were lost here, then he would have no face left to show the higher ups of the Machine Field.

But now he can’t leave, and would only wait for his death in this place. This feeling was really bad, he doesn’t have any means to deal with it.

Ma Rulong felt that his heart was on its last embers. He scolded himself again and again. Why must they come here early? If they came later, then they would have evaded the tragedy. Coming here was just charging to their deaths. Not only that, he was ruining the Machine Field’s hope!

At this time, Ma Rulong suddenly felt a powerful aura that seem to soar through the heavens. This aura wasn’t any less than the aura being emitted by the bug, it was even more powerful.

Ma Rulong was startled, then he quickly turned his head around. He saw Zhao Hai calmly standing there, his imposing aura was very strong. Even the powerful bug outside couldn’t overwhelm him.

Ma Rulong stared at Zhao Hai. He didn’t know what to say. He felt that Zhao Hai was somewhat strange, that Zhao Hai wasn’t the person he knew him to be.

Not only Ma Rulong, everyone in the base was looking at Zhao Hai. They were struck dumb by his powerful aura. This was especially true for Cultivators. These Cultivators knew that only Nascent Soul Sect Masters would have an aura as strong as this.

The Nascent Soul stage, people on this level can be regarded as experts in the Cultivation Realm. They were known as grandmasters. This meant that they could already establish their own sects. Besides the major sects, there were a lot of minor sects that were created by these Nascent Soul experts.

And it wasn’t only those in the base that were dumbfounded, the bugs that were attacking the base couldn’t help but pause. Although they weren’t afraid of death, their instincts could still stop them in their tracks.

Animal instinct was much keener than a human’s. Although the level of intelligence of these insects weren’t high, they could clearly feel Zhao Hai’s imposing aura. Zhao Hai managed to put pressure on them that they couldn’t help but slow down.

As for the powerful bug , it naturally sensed Zhao Hai’s aura. In turn, it intensified its aura. The bug’s aura exploded with intensity, it was like a tide that suddenly welled up.

Zhao Hai’s aura slowly increased. It was like an ordinary rock in the sea, steadfast against all currents!

Both the base and the insects couldn’t help but stop. This was no longer a fight they could participate in. For weak beings like them, the only thing they could do was wait for the outcome.

The bug’s imposing aura was quickly approaching. Before long, Zhao Hai could already feel the bug with his spiritual force. He didn’t really expect the bug’s aura to be this strong. This caused a huge impact towards the entire base.

As soon as he saw the bug, Zhao Hai immediately noticed its differences compared to the other bugs. This bug was a huge version of a rhinoceros beetle. It’s back was akin to black iron. A silvery white stripe streaked through its entire body. It’s back was opened as a pair of golden wings provided it with flight. It had six blade-like feet that added to its menacing look. In front and behind the head of the bug were two sharp horns. One could see the offensive capability of this bug.

Silverback Gold-winged Bug, Zhao Hai immediately thought of this name. He was certain that this was the silverback gold-winged bug. The name alone described what this bug looked like.

Zhao Hai’s body slowly flew up, then he proceeded to fly forward. When he was a kilometer away from the base, he stopped.

Before long, the bug flew up until he was a kilometer away from Zhao Hai. The bug’s blood-red eyes were looking at Zhao Hai. There was even a hint of confusion in its gaze.

Zhao Hai looked at the insect, then he smiled faintly and said, “What clever fellows. You actually had the idea to lure the tiger out of the mountain. Now that you lured the Nascent Soul Experts out, you attacked the city once more. Interesting. I didn’t expect you bugs to be this smart.”

The rhinoceros beetle-like bug had a glimmer of pride in its eyes. It roared twice as if to show off to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai looked at the rhinoceros beetle, then he smiled faintly and said, “But now that I’m here, you can no longer attack the base. Go back now, I don’t want to injure you.” The bug seems to understand Zhao Hai’s words. It’s eyes flashed with anger before he charged towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then waved his hand. A 100-layer formation appeared, forming a big shield that blocked the attack coming in front.

Since this bug was like a rhinoceros beetle, its main attack was ramming with its huge horn. Zhao Hai braced for the impact. A huge bang was heard before Zhao Hai’s shield was shattered. However, the bug didn’t slow down at all, it still continued to charge towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai held up his staff and then used it to block. ‘Dang’, a loud sound was heard as the rhinoceros horn slammed into Zhao Hai’s staff. However, the staff didn’t move. Not only was the staff unfazed, Zhao Hai was also unaffected by the attack. He was able to completely block the bug’s attack.

A burst of energy erupted from where the staff and the horn intersected. A wave of energy spread out. The bugs around them were hit by this wave of energy. The bugs that were hit were immediately turned into green dust.

The strength of the collision caused those in the base to be startled. Whether they be from the Cultivation Realm or the Machine FIeld, even those with weak spiritual force, all of them could easily see the situation a kilometer outside the base. Not to mention the fact that it was now bright as daylight, it was very easy to see the fight. The Cultivators in the base were taken aback by the strength of the impact.

When the bug discovered that it failed to damage Zhao Hai, it quickly retreated. Then it reorganized itself before attacking once more. One could feel the aura of an ancient general coming from the bug. It had exquisite combat skills. All of its actions were well executed and used a bit of martial arts.

The silverback gold-winged bug was small. All in all, it was six feet tall. It had two pointed horns that can be used as weapons. And with its thick armor, it was like a knight holding a lance and a shield. Moreover, it had six blade-like feet that can also be used for attack. Ordinary people wouldn’t be able to deal with this bug.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t an ordinary person. His body moved as he began to send spells one after the other. The staff in his hand was also used as a weapon. He wasn’t in any disadvantage in a melee against the bug.

People in the base now knew that Zhao Hai was both a Mage and a Warrior. Moreover, his skill in both professions was formidable. The people from the Cultivation Realm were quickly able to accept this. Meanwhile, those from the Machine Field had mixed feelings about it.

There were a lot of participants who had met Zhao Hai in the competition. Before this, they were not convinced of their loss. But after seeing Zhao Hai, those who were unwilling to accept their loss couldn’t help but be convinced. They knew that Zhao Hai was still holding back when he fought them. If Zhao Hai did indeed use his true ability, then they would have been injured to near death. They thought that they might only be warm-up for Zhao Hai.

With this thought in mind, people couldn’t help but get embarrassed. Naturally, some people felt envy and hate. One of these people was Streep. He already envied and hated ZHao Hai before this, but he just didn’t have the opportunity to act. After seeing Zhao Hai fighting evenly with the silverback gold-winged bug, Streep became aware of how naive he really was. At the same time, he felt that he was lucky. If he had acted against Zhao Hai, then he would have died. He thought that Zhao Hai was just a strong level 4 Mage.

When he thought of this, Streep’s face turned red with anger. He didn’t know why Zhao Hai suddenly showed his strength, which was unbecoming of Zhao Hai. But no matter what, Zhao Hai had already displayed his immense strength. This only meant that Streep would have to make another plan to deal with him.

Amongst everyone present, only Ma Rulong knew why Zhao Hai suddenly showed off his strength. Ma Rulong knew about Zhao Hai’s relationship with Xiong Li and the others. Zhao Hai went back and saw that Dongfang Yu couldn’t be disturbed. Those who were in seclusion shouldn’t be disturbed. If the base was broken through, then Dongfang Yu would certainly be attacked. This might be the reason why Zhao Hai made his move.

Ma Rulong wasn’t angry that Zhao Hai wasn’t going all out before. On the contrary, he felt that Zhao Hai did the right thing. Those from the Cultivation Realm weren’t easy to deal with. If they discover that Zhao Hai was this strong, then they would be able to prepare. When the time comes, Zhao Hai would have more trouble when trying to defeat them.

When he thought of this, Ma Rulong couldn’t help but feel his heart going hot. He knew that with Zhao Hai’s current strength, he could definitely achieve great results in the Six Realm Beginner Competition. As long as Zhao Hai gets great results, then the Machine Field would get benefits. Then as a team leader, Ma Rulong would also get benefits.

What Ma Rulong didn’t know was that at this time, Xiong Li and the others were also looking at the direction where Zhao Hai and the beetle fought. Tears were actually in their eyes. If they still had any doubts about Zhao Hai’s feelings for them, then all of these doubts were now gone!

Chapter 1223: Drinking a Forbidden Potion

Xiong Li and the others became friends with Zhao Hai because of various reasons: his temperament, his friendliness, and many more. However, they were all from the lower realms, their hearts were as hard as iron. It was impossible for them to leave their lives to other people just because of friendship.

Xiong Li and the others regarded themselves and Zhao Hai as friends. But although they call themselves brothers, their relationship wasn’t that deep. But faced with Zhao Hai’s sacrifice of facing the silverback gold-winged bug alone, Xiong Li and the others’ hearts melted. They now regarded him as a brother for a lifetime.

Zhao Hai continued to fight the silverback gold-winged bug. Moreover, they went farther and farther from the base. They fought until the bugs and the base were far away. Surprisingly, the bugs didn’t use this opportunity to attack. Instead, they slowly retreated.

Seeing the bugs retreating, the people in the base cheered. The Bug Race’s retreat was really important for the base. Now that the bugs had left, this meant that the base was safe.

At this moment, the base’s transmission formation flashed with white light. Walking out of this formation was a group of Cultivators. The quality of this group of cultivators was clearly higher than those before. Each one of them had threatening auras. Moreover, some of them were experts of the Nascent Soul Stage.

Upon seeing the Nascent Soul experts, everyone in the base began to relax. Zheng Li immediately welcomed the reinforcements. At this point, Ma Rulong became aware of Zheng Li’s identity. Zheng Li’s Five Element Team was the entire garrison of Base Number 5. This meant that the captain was the manager of the entire base. As for the Nascent Soul defenders, they really didn’t care about positions.

Zheng Li arrived in front of the five Nascent Soul experts and then gave them a salute, “I have seen the five grandmasters.”

One of the five was a red-faced old man, he nodded and said, “Alright, did the bugs retreat?” Zheng Li nodded and said, “Yes, they retreated.” The red-faced old man nodded and said, “Tell me what happened.”

Zheng Li nodded, then he said, “Yes. Masters, please take a rest at the main hall first. Allow me to give you a comprehensive report.” The five Nascent Soul experts didn’t say anything and just nodded. Then they all flew towards Base Number 5’s main hall.

These Nascent Soul Experts knew that a small captain like Zheng Li still had quite the power in Fabio Planet. Although Zheng Li couldn’t control them, these Nascent Soul Experts still needed to give Zheng Li face.

After the group arrived in the main hall, Zheng Li immediately gave an account of the situation to the five experts. Upon hearing the details, the five couldn’t help but be stunned. When Zheng Li finished, the red-faced old man immediately said, “You mean the bug attack was blocked by someone from the Machine Field? Are you sure?”

Zheng Li quickly replied, “I won’t dare lie in front of the grandmasters. That is indeed the case. Zhao Hai is a participant of the Six Realm Beginner Competition. His initial strength is only slightly stronger than a level 4 Mage. However, when the silverback gold-winged bug attacked, he suddenly exploded with strength.”

The red-faced old man knit his brows and said, “He’s participating in the Six Realm Beginner Competition? When did such a powerful figure appear in the Machine Field. Hmmm, I seem to have heard of this Zhao Hai. He gained first place in the Machine Field’s qualifiers. He also blocked three attacks from that kid Li Chuchen from Extreme Cold City. But is he really that strong?”

The others nodded. Meanwhile, Zheng Li just stood there without saying anything. Ordinary electronic products wouldn’t function in Fabio Planet. Besides places that can be reached by short distance teleportation, the planet had no news coming from the outside. Therefore, those in the planet weren’t well-informed about Zhao Hai and the others.

The red-faced old man and the others just came from the Cultivation Realm, so they knew about Zhao Hai, albeit not too detailed. But because of this, all of them couldn’t help but wonder. Can a Machine Field rookie really contend against a silverback gold-winged bug? This sounds like something from fantasy.

Silverback gold-winged bugs were high-level beings in Fabio Planet. A fully grown silverback gold-winged bug could never be defeated by an ordinary Nascent Soul Expert. It would need multiple Nascent Soul Experts to defeat a single adult silverback gold-winged bug. And it wasn’t certain that they could kill it, only injure. Since this was the case, hearing that a rookie from the Machine Field managed to fight one silverback gold-winged insect alone was something that only very few people could believe.

The red-faced old man as well as the others stayed silent for some time. Zheng Li didn’t dare to make a noise as he just respectfully stood there. After staying in Fabio Planet for some time, he knew when to speak and when to stay silent.

At this time, a frail and scholarly looking expert said, “Did Zhao Hai do anything special before fighting the Silverback Gold-winged bug?”

Zheng Li stared for a moment, he didn’t quite understand what this person was asking about. However, he didn’t dare speak his mind. Although this scholarly man looked frail, Zheng Li knew that he was the strongest and most ruthless among the five.

Therefore, he quickly responded, “He didn’t do anything special. But when he was fighting ordinary bugs, he drank a bottle of potion to recover. And before fighting against the silverback gold-winged bug, he returned to the base to check in on his friends. This is because one of them is still in seclusion. “

The scholar nodded and said, “Zhao Hai’s strength shouldn’t be so high. He must have used a secret potion that burns his potential in order to increase his strength. If he really used that, then there’s no need to worry about him. If Zhao Hai didn’t use this kind of potion, then he would be terrifying.” The others in the room nodded. They also agreed to the scholar’s point of view. Zhao Hai must have taken a secret potion. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have become that strong.

Meanwhile, Ma Rulong was unaware of this conversation. He was currently leading his people back to their courtyard. Xiong Li and the others were still there, they didn’t leave even for a single step. Moreover, there was no need for them to step forward. The arrival of the Nascent Soul Experts meant that Base Number 5 was already safe.

After Ma Rulong had the others take a rest, he directly went to see Xiong Li and the others. Xiong Li and the others had already calmed down. They knew that Zhao Hai’s action of revealing his strength would put him in great danger. They accepted this outcome but they buried the sentiment deep inside their hearts.

Ma Rulong looked at Xiong Li and the others, he sighed and then patted Xiong Li’s shoulder as he said, “Zhao Hai will be safe, don’t worry.”

Xiong Li smiled faintly and said, “Team leader, rest assured, we know that Little Hai will come back. That bug couldn’t take his life. Also, he needs to return for the Six Realm Beginner Competition.” Ma Rulong nodded, then he suddenly laughed and said, “I didn’t expect that kid to conceal that much strength. It seems like the Machine Field will win big in the competition.” Li Kuangren and the others laughed as well. They were confident in Zhao Hai. They believed that he would come back, he certainly will.

At this time, Zhao Hai and the silverback gold-winged bug were already far from Base Number 5. They were currently on a mountain in Fabio Planet. Although massive insects inhabit the planet, its environment was actually very good. There were giant trees everywhere and its mountains were covered in forests. Taking a broad view of the planet, one could see a sea of green.

Upon feeling that there was truly nobody around them, Zhao Hai waved his hand and sent forth a 1000-layer formation. After beating the silverback gold-wing insect back, Zhao Hai waved his staff as the formation formed into a huge net.

The rhinoceros beetle stepped back from the net and then spewed a lightning bolt out of its mouth towards Zhao Hai. This lightning was as thick as a bucket. One could see how powerful it was.

Zhao hai didn’t expect this rhinoceros beetle to have a lightning attack. However, he didn’t stop as he sent another 1000-layer formation to block the lightning.

Upon seeing the flexible maneuvers of the silverback gold-winged bug, Zhao Hai knew that it would be impossible for him alone to deal with it. So he waved his hand and released an army of Undead that immediately charged towards the beetle.

The rhinoceros beetle looked at this situation and couldn’t help but pause. Then it angrily roared as it attacked the Undead. It must be said that the beetle was very strong. When it came it contact with the Undead, it was able to kill them in large numbers.

The Undead weren’t true immortals, and with the powerful attack of the beetle, these Undead were smashed into pieces. It was impossible for them to continue living.

Zhao Hai calmly looked at the battle between the beetle and the Undead. He didn’t do anything as he waited for an opportunity. He knew that the beetle was still keeping an eye on him. If he moved now, then the beetle would definitely run away.

After fighting with the bug for so long, Zhao Hai learned to never underestimate it. He knew too little of Fabio Planet, so he didn’t know if the beetle had any other means. He didn’t want it to go all out.

The beetle and the Undead continued to fight for an hour. Zhao Hai lost several thousand Undead. In the end the opportunity finally arrived. Zhao Hai moved and then used the Space to teleport himself on top of the beetle. Then Liquid Silver turned into a large net. With such a sudden action, even the Undead that the bug was fighting were caught. The other Undead immediately helped as they pushed the net towards the Space.

As the silverback gold-winged bug entered the Space, a prompt was immediately heard, “New type of bug lifeform detected. It has an aggressive attitude towards the Space. Subduing, subjugation successful. The bug is a genetically modified bug with strong offensive strength. The host can now buy it inside the Space.”

Chapter 1224: Reaction From All Parties

When Zhao Hai heard this prompt, he couldn’t help but knit his brows. He wasn’t satisfied with the result. The reason he captured the rhinoceros beetle wasn’t because he wanted it to help him fight. What he wanted was the Bug Race’s evolutionary ability. The prompt didn’t mention anything of that sort. It was clear that this silverback gold-winged bug had evolved. This caused Zhao Hai to be confused.

Zhao Hai immediately said, “Cai’er, use the scanner to do an analysis. See what’s going on. Why does this bug not have any evolutionary ability?” Caier immediately used the scanner. By this point, the scanner had already reached an advanced level. It can’t only analyze objects, it could also make readings about situations.

Not long after the scanner was used, a prompt was heard, “The bug is only a gene improved member of the Bug Race. It doesn’t have any capabilities that its parent had, therefore it doesn’t have the ability of rapid evolution. From the analysis, there should be a type of bug queen in Fabio Planet. This queen can grasp changes in the environment and conduct gene improvements on the larvae to suit the Bug Race’s needs. Since there is too little data, this is just a possibility. Host needs to provide more material.”

When he heard the prompt, Zhao Hai stared. Then he nodded once he understood what the scanner meant.

In other words, a Bug Race Queen Nest was in Fabio Planet. This nest must be the key to the Bug Race’s ability to evolve rapidly. Bugs like the silverback gold-winged bug didn’t have the ability to evolve on their own.

Although the scanner said that this was just a possibility, and can only be used for reference, Zhao Hai knew that it was likely to be true.

Zhao Hai was happy. One, because he knew that there might be a queen nest. And two, because he discovered that the scanner was beginning to sound more natural. Moreover, its ability to analyze had gotten stronger and stronger. This was a very good thing, especially to him, it was very good.

At this time, Laura and the others took a look at the silverback gold-winged bug. To be honest, this bug was basically just an enlarged version of a rhinoceros beetle. Despite its overwhelmingly powerful strength, it actually looked pretty good.

Laura and the others touched the bug as though they had forgotten that it was an insect. It seems like the black sheen on the bug’s armor caught their fancy.

Zhao Hai didn’t disturb them as he stood on the side and enjoyed the sight. In any case, the bug has already been subdued by the Space. There was no danger for Laura and the others.

Quite some time after inspecting the bug, Laura turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, let’s head inside. Cultivators in Base Number 5 are talking about you.”

Zhao Hai stared, he raised his eyebrows and said, “Really? What did they say?”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “They said that you took a forbidden potion to become strong. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai stared, then he chuckled and said, “Isn’t that great? Then I’ll go into seclusion later when I go back. This will make them think that I really took a potion.” Laura and the others chuckled as well.

Zhao Hai didn’t immediately return to Base Number 5. Instead, he stayed inside the Space for some time before returning.

……………….

The place where Zhao Hai came out from wasn’t far from Base Number 5. It didn’t take long before he arrived at the base. The Cultivators in the base were still anxious. There were quite a lot of patrols on the wall, obviously on guard against any bug attack.

As Zhao Hai flew forward, a voice was suddenly heard, “Who’s that? Halt!” Zhao Hai turned his head to see a Cultivator stepping on his flying sword. Zhao Hai didn’t stop as he coldly snorted and continued flying towards the base.

When the Cultivator saw that Zhao Hai ignored him, his expression changed as he said, “Alright, Little Mage. You’re quite arrogant. Stop!” Just before the Cultivator finished his statement, a hand suddenly covered his mouth. The owner of the hand quickly looked at Zhao Hai and respectfully said, “I apologize, Mister Zhao Hai. He’s new here. Please come in. Everyone from the Machine Field has already returned to the courtyard to rest. You can go there directly.” Zhao Hai nodded and then proceeded to fly forward. He didn’t mind the two people, he didn’t even speak a word. However, the Cultivator didn’t have any dissatisfaction on his face.

Once Zhao Hai was no longer in the wall, the second Cultivator let go of the first one. The first Cultivator immediately said, “Third Senior Brother, why did you do that? It’s just a Mage from the Machine Field. He dared to be rampant, aren’t I supposed to teach him a lesson? We should let him know that he shouldn’t be arrogant in the Cultivation Realm.”

The Third Senior Brother looked at the man and said, “Stop talking. If I didn’t cover your mouth, then you would have already been killed. Do you know who that person is? That’s Zhao Hai, he fought off the silverback gold-winged insect alone. If you continued to shout at him, then you will have died in vain.” Then he ignored the man and flew away.

The Cultivator stared, then he turned to look at Zhao Hai’s direction and muttered, “So he’s Zhao Hai. No wonder his aura was so overwhelming. He’s that strong.”

The Cultivation Realm was a very realistic place. If you were strong, then you can kill all the weaklings you want. But if you’re weak, then you can only prostrate yourself to the strong. People might not kill you in public, but there would certainly be someone plotting against you in the shadows. This was the Cultivation Realm.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about the man as he directly flew towards the courtyard. Just after he entered, he was immediately discovered by Xiong Li and the others. They surrounded Zhao Hai as Xiong Li worriedly asked, “Little Hai, are you alright?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’m fine. I just need to close up. Help me inform team leader Ma.”

When Xiong Li heard this, he immediately said, “Alright, go. I’ll tell team leader Ma.” Zhao Hai nodded before quickly going inside Dongfang Yu’s room.

Just as Zhao Hai closed the door, Ma Rulong came out of his room. When he saw that Zhao Hai wasn’t there, he turned to Xiong Li and the others and said, “Where’s Little Hai?”

Xiong Li immediately answered, “Team leader, Little Hai said that he would close up for some time.”

Ma Rulong’s expression changed. Then he said, “Alright, if Little Hai needs anything, tell me immediately. I’ll try to help as much as I can.”

Xiong Li and the others nodded. Then Ma Rulong entered his room and immediately sent information back to the Machine Field. Passing on information from here to the Machine Field wasn’t easy. Since Fabio Planet had a lot of interference, signals going in and out were being heavily affected. It was great that the Cultivation Realm had devised a way to send signals to other planets through a transmission formation. Then this signal would use the satellites on those planets in order to pass the information.

But in the base, one would need to spend money in order to use this method. Ma Rulong had to pay a hefty price to send information back to the Machine Field.

Ma Rulong was sent on behalf of the realm, so he wasn’t worried about these charges. Keeping the Machine Field informed about the situation in Fabio Planet was of utmost importance.

Actually, it wasn’t only the Cultivators who suspected Zhao Hai of drinking a special potion. In Ma Rulong’s mind, it was the only explanation for Zhao Hai’s sudden increase in strength. Anything else was abnormal.

Zhao Hai had just ascended less than a year ago. He learned magic theory in that time frame and now he was as strong as a Nascent Soul Expert? Nobody would be able to believe it.

Meanwhile, the Machine Field and the Cultivation Realm had methods that could make a person stronger in exchange for their potential. These things were quite common. Therefore, people were more inclined to believe that Zhao Hai drank a forbidden potion than Zhao Hai being this innately strong.

Whether it be in the Machine Field or the Cultivation Realm, these kinds of drugs were very overbearing. The side effects would sometimes manifest itself right after the effects wear off. It’s even common for a person to just dry up and die. And if they survive, the drug would have a tremendous effect on later cultivations. Because of this, Ma Rulong worriedly passed information back to the Machine Field.

The Machine Field counts on Zhao Hai to gain a good position in the Six Realm Beginner Competition. Now that Zhao Hai was possibly crippled, the matter needed to be reported.

This information wasn’t only relevant to Ma Rulong. When Zheng Li heard that Zhao Hai secluded himself right after returning, it affirmed their suspicion that Zhao Hai took something. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have been that strong. Zheng Li immediately reported this situation. Whether it be the Machine Field and the Cultivation Realm, they both discussed someone, and it was Zhao Hai!

Zhao Hai was currently inside the Space. He was currently observing Ma Rulong and Zheng Li’s response. Ma Rulong still felt good about Zhao Hai. After he reported the situation, the higher ups of the Machine Field told him to give up on Zhao Hai. However, Ma Rulong didn’t agree with it. In the end, the Machine Field had to agree with Ma Rulong’s arrangement. After all, Ma Rulong was the one in the field, and nobody could influence his actions.

Zhao Hai also expected the response of the Machine Field’s higher-ups. It doesn’t matter if it was in the Cultivation Realm or the Machine Field, these places were practical in their approach towards useless people. They wouldn’t waste any investment in those that wouldn’t benefit them.

What Zhao Hai cared the most was the Ashley Family’s response. If the Ashley Family and the Machine Field had the same response, then Zhao Hai would be really disappointed.

But much to Zhao Hai’s surprise, the Ashley Family didn’t give up on him. Thunder didn’t tell Margaret to leave Zhao Hai as well. This caused people to wonder about this situation.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect this. Thunder was a practical person, so how could have this attitude towards a useless person?

After monitoring Thunder, Zhao Hai began to understand. The Ashley Family needed to send a message, and this message was in Zhao Hai.

The Ashley Family obtained first place in the realm qualifiers because of Zhao Hai. They obtained a lot of benefits and even gained several allies. Funding their development was definitely not a problem.

For the family to develop, they would need all kinds of talents. Thunder knew very well that Zhao Hai might already be crippled. Yet he still gave him the best treatment and even gave him his daughter. This would give bystanders the message, “Look, see how we treat those who contributed to the family. Even if he is crippled, he would still get everything he deserves!” The Ashley Family could use this to attract talents to the Ashley Family. This way, the family could develop as soon as possible.

After looking into Thunder Ashley’s actions, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but recognize that the Patriarch wasn’t a simple man. He could actually achieve something like this.

But no matter what reason, at least they didn’t ruthlessly cut him off. Zhao Hai decided to treat the Ahsley Family better in the future. After all, it was also Margaret’s family.

At this moment, the Cultivation Realm became relieved about Zhao Hai. They weren’t as concerned about him as before. After all, Zhao Hai blocked three swords from Li Chuchen and also killed Gongsun Zheng. There were a lot of people that liked Zhao Hai to perish since he had the capability to undermine their plans.

But now, nobody cared about Zhao Hai. Disabled people weren’t worth their attention.

Zhao Hai thought that trouble would come looking for him once he revealed his strength. But instead, the opposite happened. Not only did he avoid trouble, there would no longer be anyone that would come looking for him. This caused somewhat of a surprise to Zhao Hai. However, he took this matter off his mind. Even if people came looking for him, with his present strength, there was no need to be afraid. Whether it be in the Cultivation Realm or the Machine Field, he could already carve his own place.

Not to mention the Machine Field, even the Cultivation Realm had sects being set up by Nascent Soul Experts. These Nascent Soul Experts being called grandmaster wasn’t a joke.

After seeing everyone’s response, Zhao Hai began paying attention to Dongfang Yu’s state. Dongfang Yu had closed up for several days and had yet to come out. Moreover, the last time Zhao Hai saw his second brother, Dongfang Yu was at a critical point in his cultivation. Therefore, Zhao Hai wanted to see how he was doing right now.

Seeing Dongfang Yu’s situation through the Space, Zhao Hai began to feel relieved. In the past, Dongfang Yu’s face was red and his expression was exhausted. But now, Dongfang Yu had a calm expression. The fire dragon sword had already disappeared from sight. Dongfang Yu’s whole person was sitting down and meditating. Upon seeing this, Zhao Hai knew that Dongfang Yu would soon come out.

Since Zhao Hai took the silverback gold-winged bug to the Space and with the presence of Nascent Soul Experts in the base, the bugs stopped their attack. However, the elimination round for the Six Realm Beginner Competition had been pushed back 10 days. This was also within Zhao Hai’s expectation, it was normal given what happened.

Chapter 1225: Fire Dragon Daoist

Dongfang Yu slowly opened his eyes. His eyes had a hint of shine one them. At the same time, his aura was very different from before. He really didn’t expect the fire dragon sword to be this mystical.

Dongfang Yu looked around him and discovered that he was in Zhao Hai’s room. Remembering that Zhao Hai had nowhere to stay in, he immediately got up. He didn’t know how long he had been in seclusion or whether he had missed the competition.

Upon thinking about this, Dongfang Yu immediately opened the door and left the room. When he got outside, he saw Xiong Li and the others chatting, but Zhao Hai wasn’t there.

Xiong Li and the others heard the sound of a door opening. When they turned their heads, they quickly saw Dongfang Yu. They immediately surrounded him as Xiong Li said, “Dongfang, how are you? Did you benefit greatly from your seclusion?”

Dongfang Yu nodded and said, “I gained a lot. Where’s Little Hai?” Xiong Li’s expression turned difficult as he looked at Dongfang Yu’s room, then he said, “Let’s head inside first.” Then he pulled Dongfang Yu towards Zhao Hai’s room.

When he saw Xiong Li’s response, Dongfang Yu knew that something must have happened. Upon entering the room, Dongfang Yu immediately asked, “What happened? Did Little Hai have an accident?”

Xiong Li looked at Dongfang Yu and said, “Tell us about what happened to you first.”

Dongfang Yu nodded and said, “I closed up because Little Hai helped me unseal the fire dragon sword. I didn’t expect that unsealing the fire dragon sword would result to this. As it turns out, the fire dragon sword was the life source weapon of the almighty Fire Dragon Daoist. Fire Dragon Daoist died from a severe injury he gained during a fight. He sent a wisp of his consciousness into the fire dragon sword before sealing it. When Little Hai removed this seal, I received that consciousness from the Fire Dragon Daoist. It included a cultivation method known as the Divine Fire Dragon Art. There is also a set of fire dragon sword techniques. Besides that, the Fire Dragon Daoist also imbued the sword with a fraction of his strength. I managed to assimilate the Fire Dragon Daoist’s energy and made it my own. At this point, I no longer have battle qi inside me, all of it has been transformed into fire dragon true qi. It can be said that I’m already practicing the Cultivation Realm’s methods. I’m also much stronger than before.”

When they heard this, Xiong Li and the others let out cold breaths. Then Sun Fei murmured, “That’s good, at least Brother Hai’s efforts weren’t wasted.”

Dongfang Yu heard this and couldn’t help but knit his brows as he said, “What’s happening? Little Hai had an accident? Tell me!”

Xiong Li sighed and said, “The night you suddenly closed up, a massive army of bugs attacked the base. Little Hai made us defend here while he went to the wall to help alongside the others. The bug attack was very fierce, the base was having trouble defending. Then afterwards, a silverback gold-winged bug attacked. It’s a bug that’s equivalent to a Nascent Soul Expert of the Cultivation Realm. However, the base’s Nascent Soul Experts were not present. They were still chasing the silverback gold-winged insect that attacked before. Little Hai wanted to escape, but you were still closing up and cannot be moved. Little Hai went back again and repelled the powerful bug. This was originally a good thing. But after thinking about it for two days, Little Hai couldn’t be that strong. It’s possible that he drank a forbidden potion in order to repel the bugs. After he came back from fighting the bug, he immediately secluded himself. This confirmed our suspicion that Little Hai burned his potential to gain temporary strength. We know that Little Hai’s strength will be affected because of this. We just don’t know how much damage he suffered.”

When Xiong Li finished speaking, Dongfang Yu stood up, tears were already in his eyes. Then he said, “Little Hai, you silly brother. How can you do this? This favor, Elder Brother will certainly remember!”

Xiong Li and the others were also low-spirited. After staring at the ground for some time, Dongfang Yu solemnly said, “Now that I have become stronger, and have practiced a Cultivation Realm’s method, I can now formally join a sect. Perhaps the Cultivation Realm has a pill that can cure Little Hai.”

When they heard Dongfang Yu, Xiong Li and the others stared. People from the Machine Field could only look up to the Cultivation Sects. This was because the requirements to join one were too high. Those who joined a sect were shackled to the sect for their entire lives. Paying obeisance to a sect wasn’t something that an average person could bear.

Xiong Li looked at Dongfang Yu and said, “Are you sure?” Dongfang Yu stopped for a moment before he nodded and said ,”I’ve decided. After this competition ends, I will enter a Cultivation Sect. I’ll find a way for Little Hai to cure his condition.”

Xiong Li and the others didn’t stop him and just nodded. But at this time, a voice was heard, “If you leave and join a sect, then what would happen to our plan to establish a base?”

Xiong Li and the other stared, then they turned their head and saw Zhao Hai smiling at them. They were stunned. Dongfang Yu looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, is that you? Why are you out? Are you fine?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’m fine, Second Brother, rest assured.”

Xiong Li and the others quickly surrounded him and inspected his body. Seeing everyone acting concerned, Zhao Hai said, “I’m really fine. I didn’t drink any strange medicine. Relax.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others relaxed. Xiong Li then looked at Zhao Hai in confusion and said, “That’s not right. You didn’t drink anything? Then how can you be strong enough to repel a silverback gold-winged bug? Don’t tell me you’re really that strong?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said ,”Boss Xiong is correct. I’m that strong. Actually, it’s not purely my own. My weapon is also very powerful.” Then as he said that, Zhao Hai turned his hand and took out Liquid Silver.

Xiong Li and the others proceeded to inspect Liquid Silver, but they couldn’t find anything special about it. Zhao Hai saw their expressions and couldn’t help but smile. Then under Xiong Li and the others’ gaze, Liquid Silver transformed and turned into a shield.

Xiong Li and the others stared as Zhao Hai transformed Liquid Silver into 18 different weapons before turning back into a staff. It took a while before Zhao Hai’s brothers were able to recover. Looking at the staff in Zhao Hai’s hand, Xiong Li’s eyes shone as he said, “Little Hai, what is that thing? How can it transform?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Can you remember a legend back in the Machine Field? The one about a certain weapon that was left unfinished?”

When they heard Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others gawked. If it was mentioned that there was an unfinished weapon in the Machine Field, people would immediately think about Liquid Silver. It’s quite a famous legend.

Xiong Li and the others looked at Zhao Hai in shock. Sun Fei said, “Brother Hai, you mean that this is the unfinished weapon that Leng Wuyeng left behind?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he nodded and said, “Correct. This is the weapon that Senior Leng Wuyeng failed to complete. I managed to finish it and gave it the name Liquid Silver. What do you think? Pretty good right?”

Dongfang Yu’s head was in disarray, he looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “How is that possible? Didn’t people say that nobody can complete that weapon? How did you do it?”

Zhao Hai chuckled and said, “I used a clever method…” then Zhao Hai told them about numerous methods that Liquid Silver could be completed. While listening to Zhao Hai, Dongfang Yu had no choice but to believe him. The brothers couldn’t help but shift their gazes towards the staff in Zhao Hai’s hand.

They had heard about this weapon. It was said that Leng Wuyeng made this weapon in order to combat the Cultivation Realm. Its might was supposed to be peerless, but it was left unfinished. Now that it had been completed, it allowed Zhao Hai to repel a silverback gold-winged bug. Wasn’t it too strong?

Zhao Hai looked at his brothers and said, “It’s because of this staff that I managed to defeat the silverback gold-winged bug. Liquid Silver is most suitable to those who are both Mages and Warriors. I happen to practice both professions, so I managed to display its powerful might.”

Xiong Li and the others nodded, they couldn’t help but look at Zhao Hai in envy. Seeing their expressions, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “There’s no need to feel envious. I’m currently looking for a way to make replicas of Liquid Silver. Although it wouldn’t be as strong, it would still be stronger than most staff and weapons. If I managed to do it, I’ll definitely give you one.”

Hearing Zhao Hai say this, Xiong Li and the others’ eyes lit up. Sun Fei said, “Elder Brother Hai, are you telling the truth? I heard that Liquid Silver requires a lot of materials. Moreover, most of it has been depleted. Can you still make replicas of it?”

Xiong Li and the others stared at Zhao Hai, afraid that Zhao Hai would tell them that he couldn’t do it. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t worry, some materials can be substituted. However, this will make the replicas weaker. But I can assure you that its ability to transform will be retained.”

When Zhao Hai said this, the brothers cheered. This was excellent news for them. A transforming weapon, whether to a Mage or a Warrior, was a very good item to have.

It took some time before Xiong Li and the others calmed down. At this time, Li Kuangren looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Right, Little Hai, since you’re fine, why did you close up? You made us worried for nothing.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I closed up, but does that mean that I have taken a forbidden potion? Hehe. If they want to think like that, then let them. When the time comes, I’ll clean them up in the competition. As long as we make good achievements, we no longer need to care about them. We’ll establish our own base and be independent.”

Dongfang Yu nodded and said, “Right, we can be independent. Also, after we’re done here, I’ll teach you the Divine Fire Dragon Art. When that time comes, we brothers can run rampant in the battlefield.”

The group laughed. They were looking forward to their glorious future!

Chapter 1226: The True Goal Of The Elimination Round

The reason Zhao Hai revealed Liquid Silver was because he was preparing for the future. He clearly didn’t take a forbidden potion. Although everyone was thinking that he did, they would certainly know the truth once the competition began. When that time comes, Zhao Hai would need a reason for his immense strength.

Liquid Silver was the best reason. It already had a great reputation not only in the Machine Field but also in the Cultivation Realm. If Zhao Hai puts forth that this was the reason for his strength, then it’s highly probable that people would be convinced.

The group chatted for a while before Zhao Hai looked at everyone and said, “I’ll stay closed up in the next few days. You act the same as before, don’t let anyone have any ideas. Also, you should be careful of Streep. That guy hates me to the bones. I might not be able to do anything to him at this time, but don’t worry. When the elimination round comes, I will kill him. Just look out for him before that time comes.”

Dongfang Yu raised his brows and said, “Streep dares to plot? I don’t like that guy either. Let’s not wait for the elimination round. If I see the opportunity, I’ll clean him up.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t bother with it. He can’t do anything at this time. Let him live a few more days. Brothers, I’ll head back first. Act as you did before.” Then he disappeared back into the room.

Xiong Li looked at the spot where Zhao Hai vanished from and then sighed as he said, “No wonder Little Hai is so strong. I heard before that during a battle against the Zhang Family, the Ashley Family became stranded in the Rainbow Meteorite Field. Little Hai managed to save them by using space magic and teleporting everyone back to Ashley family’s planet. I found it hard to believe before, but now, it seems like Liquid Silver made Little Hai formidable.”

Dongfang Yu smiled faintly and said, “We can’t just put all merit to Liquid Silver. Little Hai is also quite strong himself. Otherwise, he wouldn’t be able to use liquid silver. I’m relieved now. Right, Boss Xiong, you said that we’ll be independent in the future, wouldn’t our families stop us?”

Xiong Li coldly snorted and said, “Of course they’ll stop us. But we only need to get good results in the competition. Especially you and Little Hai. As long as your results are good, then even if the rest of us want to be independent, nobody would be able to stop us. After all, keeping us from each other is basically offending all of us.”

Dongfang Yu nodded, then he said, “When we have the time, I’ll teach you the Divine Fire Dragon Art. Let’s see if those fellows from the Machine Field would still dare to offend us.”

Xiong Li sighed and said, “The Divine Fire Dragon Art should be alright for Little Fei. But for the rest of us, we wouldn’t be able to practice. And even if we could, it’s just not compatible for us.”

Dongfang Yu nodded, “Alright, then let’s just kill Cultivators in the elimination round and snatch their cultivation methods. If Little Hai can unseal the Fire Dragon Sword, then he could definitely unseal those jade slips.”

Xiong Li nodded and said, “I’m fine with that. Alright, let’s head out. Don’t let those fellows suspect anything. Act serious.” The others nodded with a chuckle. Then they immediately put on their solemn faces.

Time passed by little but little. At this point, almost everyone believed that Zhao Hai consumed a forbidden potion. Looking at the solemn expressions that Xiong Li and the others wore, this belief was further cemented. There were all kinds of rumors saying that Zhao Hai has died or was going to. In any case, nobody was saying good words about Zhao Hai.

Xiong Li and the others didn’t stop these rumors. Rumors were like this, the faster you want it to stop, the further it would spread. However, Xiong Li and the others weren’t idling either. They were also investigating who started these rumors.

After several days of investigation, Xiong Li and the others finally traced the origin of the rumor. It seems like Streep was the one propagating fake news about Zhao Hai. With this discovery, Xiong Li and the others quickly thought back to Zhao Hai’s words. Streep does indeed want to deal with them.

Dongfang Yu almost couldn’t stop himself from killing Streep. In the end, he was calmed down by Xiong Li. Without anyone knowing, Dongfang Yu’s temperament became more and more explosive since he practiced the Divine Fire Dragon Art. He was even more explosive than Li Kuangren. This caused Xiong Li and the others to be worried.

Days passed and the date for the elimination round was getting closer. The participants from the other realms had also arrived at Fabio Planet. They didn’t come ahead of time thus they weren’t caught by the recent battle. They suffered no losses and their numbers were healthy.

It was now three days before the elimination round begins. All participants had arrived. In addition to surviving for seven days in Fabio Planet, they must also hunt bugs and then bring back their useful parts. The more you take back, the more points you would gain. By the end of the elimination round, those who get the top 100 points would proceed to formal matches.

The past elimination rounds wouldn’t have this high rate of elimination. Sometimes they would even conduct several rounds in order to select the top 100. This was the first time where the formal competition would immediately happen after the elimination round.

Upon hearing this information, Zhao Hai was happy. He was confident that his group would be able to reach the top 100. When that time comes, the Machine Field would obtain more benefits while their position in the competition would be higher.

Moreover, Zhao Hai knew from the Space the reason why the Cultivation Realm had the elimination round happen in Fabio Planet. This was because they wanted to cull the bug population!

The Cultivation Realm had no method to deal with the bugs in Fabio Planet. The stronger experts they send, the stronger the newest generation bugs would be. This caused the Cultivation Realm to be afraid. If they sent experts that were too powerful, then the bugs might gain the ability to get out of Fabio Planet. And with the Bug Race’s reproductive ability, this would definitely be a great disaster for the Cultivation Realm.

Because of this, the Cultivation Realm needed another method to trim the bug race’s population. This method was very simple, it was to send less powerful people and clean up the weaker members of the bug race. Although this wouldn’t cause the bugs to be exterminated, at least it reduced its population. This method has been quite effective in controlling the bug race’s development.

And as it turns out, it was time to trim the bug population once more. Because of this, it was decided that Fabio Planet would be the place for the competition’s elimination round. This would serve two purposes, to conduct the competition, and to trim the bug population. It was killing two birds with one stone.

The Cultivation Realm also had another purpose. Through this competition, they would be able to eliminate the upcoming experts from the other realms. This way, the Cultivation Realm would stay on top of the six realms.

Cultivators could easily survive in Fabio Planet. Moreover, the Cultivation Realm had conducted multiple operations against the bug race. Because of this, the Cultivators were more experienced in dealing with the bugs compared to the other realms. This elimination round was heavily favored towards the Cultivation Realm.

The Cultivators had been culling the bug race’s population multiple times now. And every operation would incur huge casualties. Now that the elimination round was going to be in Fabio Planet, they would kill the bugs while also weakening the other realms. The Cultivation Realm was using this competition as an opportunity to kill any future enemies to the realm.

After knowing about the Cultivation Realm’s plans, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh. The Cultivation Realm’s plan was very good. Even if other realms knew about it, they still wouldn’t be able to do anything.

Seeing that it was almost time, Zhao Hai decided to head out. He didn’t want Ma Rulong to be too anxious. He said his goodbye to Laura and the others before he left the Space.

Just as he went out of Dongfang Yu’s room, Xiong Li and the others immediately surrounded him. They knew that Zhao Hai was fine, but they needed to act in order to fool others. Therefore everyone was looking at Zhao Hai with worry.

The others also discovered that Zhao Hai had gone out. But this time, their gaze towards him was different. In the past, they always looked at him with fear. But now, their expressions were clearly showing schadenfreude.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about them and just greeted Xiong Li and the others. At this time, Ma Rulong came out. He just heard that Zhao Hai had shown himself. So he went out and immediately asked, “Little Hai, you’re out? How are you doing? Are you alright?”

Of course, Zhao Hai knew everything that Ma Rulong did for him. He greatly respected the team leader. So he stood up and then bowed to Ma Rulong before answering, “Team leader, I’m alright.”

Ma Rulong went to Zhao Hai and then inspected him. Then he said, “Are you really alright? If there’s anything you need, just tell me. I still have some influence in the Machine Field.”

Zhao Hai knew what Ma Rulong meant. In the past few days, Ma Rulong had been constantly inquiring about medicine that can cure Zhao Hai’s problem. It seems like the team leader was truly concerned about him. And now that he was out, Zhao Hai needed to tell Ma Rulong to calm down. So Zhao Hai told Ma Rulong, “Team Leader, rest assured. I’m really fine. You don’t need to worry.”

Seeing that Zhao Hai doesn’t look injured, Ma Rulong nodded and said, “Alright. It’s fine if you don’t want to participate in the elimination round. Don’t overwork yourself.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Team Leader, I’m truly fine. I’ll participate in the elimination round. Moreover, I’ll ensure that my brothers can enter the main tournament.” Zhao Hai’s voice was very low, only Ma Rulong and those very close by heard it.

Hearing these words from Zhao Hai, Ma Rulong’s eyes couldn’t help but shine. He looked at Zhao Hai and was met with an affirmative nod. Ma Rulong quickly turned ecstatic. He patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said, “Alright. Then I’ll keep my eye on you. You don’t have to care about others. As long as you can accomplish what you said, you have already achieved the highest merit for the Machine Field.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Team Leader, don’t worry.” Ma Rulong nodded before he left.

Xiong Li looked at Ma Rulong and then looked at Zhao Hai. Confused, he asked, “Little Hai, why did you say those things to the team leader? Moreover, it seems like you give him a lot of respect.”

Chapter 1227: Clever Bugs

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s because the team leader deserves my respect. Everyone thought that I took a forbidden potion, even the team leader. However, he didn’t give up on me even though the Machine Field’s higher-ups wanted to. Now, tell me, does he deserve my respect?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others nodded with understanding. Everyone looked at Ma Rulong’s back, their faces showing their respect.

Now that Xiong Li and the others had completely seen Zhao Hai as a brother for life, everyone Zhao Hai deemed to be good would earn their respect. And those that Zhao Hai deemed evil were also their personal enemies.

But at this moment, Dongfang Yu remembered something. He looked at Zhao Hai and said, “So the news that you had taken a forbidden potion, everyone in the Machine Field knows about it? Does the Ashley Family know? How did they react? How is Margaret?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Second Brother, there’s no need to worry about it. Margaret will have no problems. As for the Ashley Family, they’re taking it well. The Ashley Family needs talent, and if they want to win talents over, then they need to treat me well. Therefore, there’s no need for you to worry about my position.”

Li Kuangren looked at Zhao Hai in confusion as he asked, “Little Hai, do you have close contact back there? Why do I feel like you know everything?”

Zhao Hai just gave a smile along with his answer, “Of course I know everything. Margaret’s been telling me the news. Don’t worry about it, nothing will happen. As long as we win this elimination round, all voices of doubt will disappear.”

Li Kuangren and the others didn’t ask any further. They already knew that Zhao Hai had a lot of methods. Moreover, Zhao Hai had already gained their absolute trust.

At this time, Streep walked in from outside. His face still held that eternal smiling expression, he looked like a good Young Master. After Xiong Li and the others saw Streep, their expressions couldn’t help but sink.

Streep acted like he didn’t see Xiong Li and the others’ change in expression. He continued smiling as he said, “Hello Mister Zhao Hai. I have shown you my shameful side during our previous battle. I just realized that I don’t know the immensity of the heavens and the earth. This time, since Mister Zhao Hai has entered seclusion, I’m sure that your strength has increased once more.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Mister Streep is too polite. But I really did gain some benefits in my recent seclusion. If time permits, then I would like to spar with Mister Streep once more.” Streep gave a polite nod and said, “Very well, I will certainly spar with Mister after the elimination round.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Then see you at the formal matches.”

Streep also nodded, “See you at the formal matches.” Then he turned around and left.

The dialogue between the two was very polite. One couldn’t smell even a whiff of gunpowder in the air. If someone had no idea, then they would think that the two were good old friends. Nobody would suspect that both parties wanted to kill the other.

When Streep left, Xiong Li couldn’t help but snort as he said, “Little Hai, why the need to be polite to that guy? If it was me, I would have already dealt with him. That will wipe that smile off his face.”

Zhao Hai slightly smiled and said, “He wants to joke with me with hidden intentions, so I joked with him with my own hidden intentions. He looks like he wants to test me, but I think he’s showing off. He thinks that I’m already dead. But isn’t that better? Let’s see him smile after we deal with him in the elimination round.”

Dongfang Yu let out a long breath and said, “It seems like even if we don’t look for him in the elimination round, he’ll be the one looking for us. Streep has won over a lot of people lately. I’m afraid these people would join him in attacking us.”

Zhao Hai replied, “Me becoming the champion of the realm qualifiers offended a lot of people. Now that I have fallen, they would take the opportunity and take my place. I won’t blame them for it, but I just hope that they don’t regret their decision.”

Li Kuangren coldly snorted and said, “Of course they’ll regret it. They’ll regret ever stepping foot on this planet.”

Sun Fei sneered as well, “Those idiots. Even if I’m all alone, I still won’t side with Streep. That guy is obviously a villain at first glance. Those who get convinced by Streep won’t even know how they will die. They always think about benefits, now look where it got them.”

Zhao Hai chuckled, “They’d better not follow Streep in attacking me. Otherwise, I wouldn’t be able to stop myself from adding them into my Undead Army.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Sun Fei was curious. Sun Fei got closer to Zhao Hai and said, “Elder Brother Hai, I’ve been hearing about your Undead army for some time now. How many Undead do you have? 1000? 2000? 10,000?” Xiong Li and the others were also very curious. They heard that Zhao Hai had raised an impressive number of Undead creatures. However, they had never seen Zhao Hai use any Undead.

Zhao Hai looked at Sun Fei and said, “I’ll let you see them when the elimination round starts. I assure you that I have more Undead than you can imagine.”

Xiong Li and the others stared at Zhao Hai, not convinced at all. Li Kuangren held Zhao Hai’s shoulders and said, “Kid, you better tell us now. Or else, things will get ugly.”

Zhao Hai just laughed it off and said, “Don’t worry about it. How about we go and have a drink? I haven’t drunk in the last few days. I’m feeling thirsty.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Li Kuangren who was also a drunkard himself, immediately let go of Zhao Hai and said, “Alright, let’s drink! Drink!”

Xiong Li and the others looked at Li Kuangren’s abrupt change in attitude and laughed. However, none of them dallied as they quickly sat on the nearest available table.

The other people in the courtyard watched the group. But this time, instead of envy and jealousy, they felt a bit of joy and happiness. In their eyes, Zhao Hai was saying his last goodbyes.

Three days went by quickly and the elimination round was about to start. Zhao Hai didn’t feel anything. This time, he was certain to pass the elimination round. There was no need to be anxious.

Zhao Hai wasn’t anxious, but this doesn’t mean that others felt the same. Xiong Li and the others were a bit nervous. After all, they would have to face the bugs that they fought last time. Not only that, they would also face the participants from the other realms. Those people weren’t easy to deal with either.

……..

The day of the elimination round.

Zhao Hai walked out of his room and saw Xiong Li and the others already waiting for him. Everyone’s faces looked serious. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but chuckle as he looked at them and said, “What’s wrong? Didn’t have enough sleep?”

Xiong Li sighed and said, “I can’t sleep. Damn. I have been waiting for this day for a long time. But now it’s here, I suddenly don’t know what to do.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Don’t be nervous about it. Especially now that we don’t have to be on our own. Just relax.” Then as he said that, Ma Rulong came out of his room. Everyone else was also out in the courtyard. Everyone had nervous looks on their faces.

Nobody could blame them for being nervous. After all, today they will not only face the Bug Race, they will also go against the various geniuses from the other realms. Among the participants in the competition, the Machine Field had the worst when it came to raw strength. In almost every competition, the Machine Field would populate the bottom 100.

Ma Rulong looked at the participants in the courtyard and saw that everyone was divided into three groups. The first group was led by Streep. It was the largest group with more than 30 people. The next group was headed by Zhu Chen with members numbering more or less 20. The last and smallest group was Zhao Hai’s with only five members. As for the rest, they had perished in the last two battles against the bugs.

Ma Rulong looked at their nervous eyes as he lightly sighed and said, “Let’s go.” Then he led the other team leaders to leave the courtyard.

Their target was the transmission formation. People from the other realms didn’t go to Base Number 5 since only the Machine Field were assigned to the base. People from the other realms went to other bases in order to participate in the elimination round. And each realm would enter a different transmission formation at a different base.

Zhao Hai and the others already knew that the location for the elimination round would be the underground of Fabio Planet. The underground of Fabio Planet was the world of the Bug Race. Countless bugs constantly dug tunnels to the point where nobody knew where the beginning was nor the end.

These underground transmission formations were also established by the Cultivators, albeit at a high price. This was in order for the bugs underground to be regularly cleaned up.

When Zhao Hai and the others arrived at the transmission formation, they saw Zheng Li already there. As soon as he saw the Machine Field’s people, Zheng Li quickly walked forward and then gave Ma Rulong his greetings, “Team Leader Ma, everything is ready.”

Ma Rulong nodded, then he waved his hand. This was a signal for Zhao Hai and the other participants to enter the transmission formation. When Zheng Li saw Zhao Hai, he quickly stepped forward. Then after giving a salute, he said, “Zhao Hai, I’ll have to thank you. No matter the reason, you still saved Base Number 5. Thank you very much.”

Zhao Hai hastily returned the salute. Then he smiled faintly and said, “There’s no need to be polite. It wouldn’t be proper for me to not move while being inside the Base. Otherwise, my friend would be involved. This is a fight between humans and bugs, this has nothing to do with realms.”

Zheng Li nodded. Then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, you’re an unlikely friend that I gained. I wish you luck. I hope you live and return.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Then I’ll take advantage of your good wishes. Rest assured, I will certainly live and return!” Zheng Li nodded. Then he waved to a person nearby who started the transmission formation. It didn’t take long before Zhao Hai and the others vanished.

Zhao Hai felt a flash of white light before he felt a bit dizzy. But as the light slowly faded away, Zhao Hai suddenly felt a dangerous intent coming straight towards him. He immediately shouted, “Be alert! The bugs are here!”

As he shouted, Zhao Hai erected a 50-layer formation shield that protected his group. Xiong Li and the others also took their weapons out.

As soon as the others heard Zhao Hai’s shout, they knew that they couldn’t treat this matter lightly. Zhao Hai had reminded them several times before, and each warning was real. At this point, all of them believed in Zhao Hai’s words.

Sure enough, as the light vanished, the Machine Field’s participants saw themselves stunned. The cave was several hundred meters high and spanned nearly ten thousand square meters. Naturally, the size of this cave wasn’t the surprising aspect. The cave was full of bugs. One of those bugs were the eight-legged bugs they had fought before. The sight caused everyone present to feel their hairs go up.

While the Machine Field’s participants were dumbfounded, the insects quickly threw themselves towards the transmission formation. Even Zhao Hai was feeling cold as he saw the amount of bugs present.

Zhao Hai quickly said, “Let’s go!” Then he waved his hand causing Xiong LI and the others to disappear from the transmission formation.

Others weren’t as lucky. Upon seeing the approaching bugs, everyone else from the Machine Field immediately turned frantic. Spells and sword qi were sent forth with no abandon. A lot of those present took out their secret items and used them.

Mages repeatedly used their staff as they sent 100-layer formations to both attack and defend.

Warriors were doing the same. They waved their weapons non-stop as they sent sword qi. Some warriors also took out some bombs from their spatial equipment. The battle quickly turned vicious. But as this was happening, Zhao Hai and the others had appeared in another cave with no insects inside.

As soon as they reappeared, Zhao Hai let out a breath of relief. He found this place through the Space’s monitor. But when he recalled the scene just now, he couldn’t help but feel cold.

Xiong Li and the others also let out long breathes. Sun Fei wiped a cold sweat as he said, “That was terrifying. How many bugs were there? 10 thousand? 20 thousand? 50 thousand? 100 thousand? There’s too many to count.”

As he breathed out, Dongfang Yu added, “Why do I feel that the bugs knew that we would appear there. Were they waiting for us?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I feel the same way. It seems like the bugs were not fools. Conversely, they seem to be very clever. It’s possible that they knew about the transmission formation a long time ago. Therefore, they waited there. Upon seeing us appear, they immediately attacked. I didn’t expect them to be this intelligent.”

Li Kuangren nodded and said, “Right, I didn’t expect those insects to be intelligent. Little Hai, didn’t you say that you’ll fight the bugs using your Undead? How about now?”

Xiong Li and the others turned to look at Zhao Hai. Dongafang Yu nodded and said, “Right, Little Hai. I really want to see how many Undead you have.”

Zhao Hai looked at the others and couldn’t help but laugh. Then he said, “Alright, since you want to see my Undead Army, here it is!” Then he waved his hand and sent out a batch of Undead from the Space.

Chapter 1228: Undead vs Bugs

The cave that Zhao Hai and the others were in wasn’t very big. It was about 200 meters in height and more than 300 meters wide in all directions. When Zhao Hai waved his hand, this entire cave was filled with Undead.

Each Undead was wearing bone armor and exuded formidable might. The Undead were also arranged in a square formation. All of them were in front of Zhao Hai.

Xiong Li and the others stared at these Undead. Although they knew that Zhao Hai had a lot, they didn’t expect this much. They were too shocked to talk, wasn’t this too much?

Zhao Hai looked at his brothers and smiled as he said, “How is it, is it a lot? These are just a part of my entire Undead army.”

Xiong Li and the others recovered. Xiong Li looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Part? These Undead, they are just a part of your entire army?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It’s a fraction of my entire army. Alright, let’s move on. Everyone, let’s go and kill some bugs.”

Xiong Li and the others were in a daze. At first they didn’t know who Zhao Hai was speaking to. But after a short pause, they finally understood.

Just as Zhao Hai’s voice fell, the Undead immediately began to walk line by line outward. Their actions were fast but their formation stayed organized.

Xiong Li and the others stared at the Undead. After some time, Xiong Li breathed out and said, “Little Hai, these Undead are as organized as an army. How did you do it?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I refined these Undead using a special method, so they’re all very intelligent. I also selected a few Undead to lead the others. This way, things can stay organized. And after some training, it led to this.”

Xiong Li and the others nodded. Although they haven’t heard of Zhao Hai’s method before, it sounded believable. Therefore, they didn’t have any suspicions.

Zhao Hai looked at everyone and said, “Let’s go. The Undead are about to clash with the bugs.” Xiong Li and the others didn’t decline. The group immediately went out of the cave.

Naturally, these Undead were controlled by Laura and the others. They treated battles like these as games. Zhao Hai also liked to give them this job so that they wouldn’t be so bored inside the Space.

Zhao Hai and the others slowly proceeded. Before long, roars were heard in the distance. Zhao Hai didn’t stop and instead flew forward. After a few turns, they finally saw the battle between the Undead and the bugs.

It was in a small cave. The Undead lined up in neat formation as they fought the bugs. The Undead were uniformly armed. Those in front held up their shields and their blades. The Undead behind them were using spears to attack. And on the very back were Undead archers. It was ordered and perfect. This caused them to become a meat grinder for the attacking bugs.

Xiong Li and the others looked at this fight and discovered that the Undead’s individual strength was also extraordinary. They had had least level 3 strength. Most importantly, they don’t fear death nor do they feel tired.

What made Xiong Li and the others even more shocked were the Undead Cavalry. These Undead rode on top of bone beasts and had lances as weapons. They would conduct charges towards the bugs, causing massive casualties to the enemy.

Additionally, there were also Mages among the Undead army. Although these Mages didn’t use Magic Theory and only used lower realm spells, their lethality wasn’t weak.

The Undead Archers were armed with explosive arrows. Each explosion would kill groups of bugs. Even if the bugs were well-armored, they unexpectedly fell after being hit with these explosions.

What Xiong Li and the others didn’t know was that these Undead were shooting arrows that came with blood lightning beads. Now that the Space had leveled up, the blood lightning beads had also increased in strength. Its might have become at least three times stronger compared to before. Because of this, the blood lightning beads were able to kill the bugs.

The bugs also couldn’t be underestimated. Xiong Li and the others saw the advantages of the bugs when it comes to fighting in caves. The bugs could crawl on the walls in order to attack in more favorable angles. They could crawl to the ceilings and jump down to attack their enemies. Because of this, even if you flew in the air, you still weren’t safe from being attacked.

At this time, there were a lot of insects that had crawled up the cave walls. However, not even waiting for these bugs to fall down, the Archers and Mages were already beginning to shoot them down. And if some survived the fall, the Undead on the ground would end them soon after.

The Undead began to start changing their tactics. They gradually reformed the square formation and then formed a circle. This circle rotated as it slowly advanced.

With this change in form, the speed in which the bugs were killed had increased. Meanwhile, all the bug corpses were being separated by the Undead in the back, waiting for Zhao Hai and the others to collect them.

Seeing this situation, Sun Fei muttered, “I’m suddenly regretting why I didn’t choose to be a Dark Mage. If I had this much Undead, I could also kill the bugs with ease.”

Xiong Li and the others recovered from their daze upon hearing this. They began to nod in agreement. Then they turned to Zhao Hai with envy. Dongfang Yu sighed and said ,”It seems like Zhao Hai wasn’t joking when he said that he’ll make us enter the top 100 smoothly. WIth this much Undead, it would be difficult for us to be eliminated.”

Zhao Hai just smiled. To be honest, if not for the elimination round’s rules, then he might have already turned these bugs into Undead. But since the elimination round required these bugs to gain points, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh. This was such a waste of material.

However, since he needed to progress in the competition, he can only endure. In any case, Fabio Planet had already been mapped into the Space. He could come here at any time later.

With this thought in mind, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown. In the past few days, he sent out silver needles to map the entire Fabio Planet. This way, he could see the terrain and find a queen nest. This way, he could send it to the Space and then gain the bug race’s incredible evolutionary ability.

However, before Zhao Hai could celebrate, something unexpected came up. These silver needles were easily discovered by the bugs. Everywhere these needles went, the bugs would immediately attack it. This caused Zhao Hai to be confused. He didn’t know how the bugs were able to discover the needles.

Only after communicating with the silverback gold-winged bug did Zhao Hai know the reason. The bugs were more sensitive than humans. Humans use their spiritual force to feel their surroundings while bugs were born with it through instinct. This intuition was very formidable. As soon as they feel a small change, the bugs will immediately look into it using their own spiritual force. Naturally, they would be able to find the silver needles.

This was especially true to the bug race. Even if the change was at a size of a grain of sand, the bugs would sense it. And the closer it was to the nest, the more on guard the bugs would be. Using silver needles to get close to the nest was almost impossible.

Zhao Hai originally wanted the needles to go Underground, but it was evident that it wouldn’t work. No matter where in Fabio Planet, he would be blocked by the bugs. In the end, he could only give up on this plan.

After putting plan to use silver needles aside, Zhao Hai asked the silverback gold-winged bug if it could approach the nest. However, the beetle said that it’s impossible. The bugs didn’t rely on appearance for identification. Instead, they relied on smell and spiritual imprints. Although the beetle hasn’t changed, the bugs would immediately discover that it no longer belonged to the race. When that time comes, the other bugs would certainly attack it. Moreover, the beetle told Zhao Hai that silverback gold-winged bugs weren’t placed high up in the bug race hierarchy. This meant that it didn’t have any qualifications to approach the queen nest. If it was divided according to human classification, silverback gold-winged bugs were regarded as local officials. They manage their territory and wouldn’t have any qualifications to see the central government.

To be honest, Zhao Hai was very surprised upon hearing this information. He never expected it to be like this. Zhao Hai could remember the threat that the beetle imposed on Base Number 5. Even he took some time before he could capture it. But now, such an existence was actually a low-level official in the bug race, it wasn’t the strongest being. One could see from this point how strong the bug race really was.

However, this also made Zhao Hai feel strange. If the bug race was this strong, then how could the Humans establish their bases on the planet. Moreover, how could the bug race allow Humans to perform regular killing of their lower-level brethren?

Zhao Hai asked the beetle about this issue. But the beetle didn’t have any answer to it. It was only a low-level official, so it doesn’t know what the higher-ups were planning.

Upon knowing this situation, Zhao Hai could only shake his head. He can only take one step at a time and make a few trips to Fabio Planet to collect more bugs for the Space. Then he would slowly find a way to deal with this issue.

At this moment, the Undead were continuing their advance. The cave was becoming more and more spacious. Then in the distance, they could hear the sound of fighting.

Chapter 1229: Confusing Right and Wrong

Boom! Boom! Boom! Boom!

Fierce explosive sounds were heard around the transmission formation. Each explosion claimed the lives of several bugs.

These explosions didn’t only come from the Undead Army’s arrows, these also came from the bombs that theMachine Field’s participants used. The might of these bombs weren’t much, but its power was much stronger compared to ordinary level 4s.

The participants from the Machine Field relied on these bombs in order to maintain their defensive line. This allowed them to not be destroyed by the bugs in one go.

Streep’s expression was currently ugly to behold as he kept sending spells. He didn’t expect to enter a cave that was surrounded by bugs. If the current situation continues, then it would be impossible for them to break out.

When he thought of this, Streep’s face became uglier. He thought of using the caves to deal with Zhao Hai, but now it seems like there’s no chance. Zhao Hai ran away.

He heard that Zhao Hai was capable of space magic before. However, he hadn’t seen Zhao Hai use spatial spells so he assumed that these talks were nonsense. But now, he could only believe, albeit already too late.

Seeing everyone around him putting up a last-ditch effort, Streep couldn’t help but feel depressed. He didn’t think that he who was hailed as a genius in the lower realms would die alongside these people in the hands of bugs. He was unwilling!

At this time, large explosions were heard. Streep stared. He was a very sensitive person. He heard that these explosions were different and didn’t belong to the Machine Field’s bombs. Moreover, these explosions seem to come from a distance.

Upon hearing this, Streep couldn’t help but get hopeful. This only meant that someone was coming to rescue them. Streep looked around and found that another group was fighting the bugs in the cave. And it seemed like it was a large group of people.

Upon seeing this, Streep’s spirits were elevated. He loudly said, “Brothers, people are coming to help us. You need to endure!”

Hearing Streep’s voice, the others from the Machine Field stared. They were already desperate, but they didn’t expect someone to come in their moment of despair. They quickly looked around and saw the Undead Army fighting the bugs. They couldn’t help but cheer for a moment as a burst of strength filled their bodies.

Actually, there weren’t a lot of bugs in this cave. The reason they looked like so was because they had filled up the cave.

Zhao Hai discovered this but didn’t say anything. The reason he dealt with the bugs was to collect bug parts and also to rescue the others. No matter what, these people were lower realm ascenders as well as people from the Machine Field. Also, most of these people didn’t have any grievances with him. SInce he could lend a hand, then he would do it this one time.

But after this event, they would have to go at it alone. Zhao Hai would no longer help them. It can be said that Zhao Hai only helped them this time because he wanted to give them a chance at least.

The battle continued. These bugs simply didn’t know fear. The only thing they knew was to attack, attack, and attack. However, the Undead were the same. They also didn’t know fear. The Undead followed instructions and fought. The battle between these two groups would certainly be vicious.

As the bugs were getting extinguished, casualties began to appear among the Undead. This was inevitable. Zhao Hai was already numbed to these losses. He had seen this scene multiple times before.

Zhao Hai was still flying behind the Undead Army. As he was observing the fight, he would also take one or two useful parts of the bugs and send it to the Space. Naturally, Zhao Hai couldn’t receive these things personally. So it was the Undead who did this job for him.

Xiong Li and the others were also witnessing the battle. However, they weren’t as calm as Zhao Hai. They had been frightened by the battle happening below. It was too vicious!

What kind of battle would occur when two sides didn’t know fear nor the word retreat? Xiong Li and the others hadn’t thought of this question before. There was only one way to end such a battle, and that was through one side being totally annihilated.

Although it was the Undead and the Bugs that were fighting, their fighting was brutal enough to move Xiong Li and the others. They couldn’t help but ask themselves. If those Undead attacked them, will they have any chance to escape? They certainly wouldn’t dare think that they would win. They just wondered if they could escape.

But the answer only made them somewhat depressed. They knew that they didn’t have any hope of escaping. It’s more probable for them to be besieged by the Undead until they die.

The battle slowly continued as the Bugs were getting fewer and fewer. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai’s Undead suffered much less casualties. Xiong Li and the others might credit this to the Undead’s coordination, but Zhao Hai knew that it was because the Undead were very strong. Unless it had been attacked by a bug several times, the Undead wouldn’t fall.

Seeing that the battle was about to end, Zhao Hai began putting away some of the Undead, leaving only a small part of them behind. Seeing Zhao Hai’s action, Xiong Li and the others couldn’t help but stare. But they quickly understood why he did this. Zhao Hai had too many Undead. Their combat power was very strong. If this kind of fighting strength came out, then the entire Machine Field would be shaken. Therefore, Zhao Hai didn’t want the Undead to look threatening.

Upon receiving most of the army, Zhao Hai was left with about 1000 Undead. At the same time, Xiong Li and the others began making their move. Zhao Hai used a 50-layer formation spell, Xiong Li and Li Kuangren sent forth their sword qi, Sun Fei also released a magic spell. As for Dongfang Yu, his attack was somewhat different compared to before. He was still using his fire dragon sword, but his attack wasn’t the same. When he released his sword qi, it actually formed into a fire dragon.

But Zhao Hai knew that this wasn’t Dongfang Yu’s real strength. Since Dongfang Yu can now be classified as a cultivator, he definitely had flying sword techniques. The only reason he released sword qi now was because he was preserving his strength.

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything. It wasn’t only Dongfang Yu who was saving energy, he was doing so too. One should forget that there’s still a potential enemy ahead, and that was Streep.

As the battle went on, Dongfang Yu turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, do we take this chance to deal with Streep? Keeping him alive isn’t good.” Xiong Li nodded and said, “This is a good chance to kill Streep. Nobody would say anything. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t worry about it. I still want to see what kind of tricks Streep would use. And we also need to get evidence, it’s still too early to deal with him. Otherwise, the Water Temple would definitely look for trouble. Streep is their hope to gain benefits. I always thought that he’s very strange. Therefore, let’s take our time. In any case, he wouldn’t be able to escape my palm. If he really wants to kill me, then I can just turn the tables on him.”

Zhao Hai had the qualifications to say such things. This was because he still had that silver needle on Streep’s head. This needle had followed Streep for a long time without being discovered. At any time, Zhao Hai can use this needle to strike Streep right in the brain, killing him immediately. But at this time, Zhao Hai wanted to see how Streep would try to kill him. If Streep used other people to deal with him, then Zhao Hai would gain another enemy to kill.

With the brothers acting in addition to the Undead, the bugs were quickly cleaned up. Zhao Hai made the Undead clean the bugs under the gazes of the others from the Machine Field.

These Machine Field participants were staring at Zhao Hai and the others. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be the one to rescue them.

Zhao Hai didn’t clean up all of the bugs, only a portion. He left the majority for the other Machine Field’s participants. No matter what, they were all on the same side. Zhao Hai didn’t want to take everything for himself.

After cleaning up some of the bugs, Zhao Hai looked at the stunned crowd and said, “Everyone, the bugs have been cleaned up. This is where we part ways. Goodbye.”

Just as Zhao Hai was about to leave, Streep’s voice was suddenly heard, “Mister Zhao Hai wait a moment. This one has something to say.”

Zhao Hai turned to Streep and said, “And what does Mister Streep want to say?”

Streep looked at Zhao Hai and then his expression sank as he said, “Mister Zhao Hai, why don’t you explain why you fled and gave up on us earlier? And now, you seem to come back as a savior. Why is this?”

Streep’s words caused Zhao Hai and the others to stare. Not only Zhao Hai’s group, everyone from the Machine Field paused. They didn’t expect Streep to ask that question. Wasn’t this a stupid question?

Zhao Hai burst out laughing and said, “Streep, you’re saying funny things. I gave up on you? What relationship do I have with you? Did you form a team with me? We aren’t in a group, we aren’t even friends. So why do I have to care about you? To be honest, I came back because I’m giving face to the Machine Field. I can choose to just leave all of you here to be besieged by the bugs until you die.”

Streep coldly snorted and said, “You didn’t come back to save us, but to kill the bugs. You want to snatch our prize? Since you left, those bugs are ours. You just came back to steal our spoils. You better leave them behind, otherwise you can’t blame us for being impolite.”

Upon hearing Streep, Zhao Hai as well as the others from the Machine Field understood what he meant. All of a sudden, everyone from the Machine Field were stunned!

Chapter 1230: Seeing Li Chuchen

Greed!

From ancient times to today, countless people succumbed to this sin. Even countries and dynasties were wiped out because of this word.

However, one has to recognize that people were innately born with greed. They may be greedy for a small profit or greedy to live forever, but all were greed nevertheless.

Streep was obviously a person who knows people’s hearts well. Everything he said was naturally fart. Its true purpose was to move the greed of the others from the Machine Field. This way, they would move together and deal with Zhao Hai.

Seeing the crowd’s greed being aroused, Zhao Hai laughed and said, “It seems like you all think the same thing? Alright then, I’ll give you all a chance. Those who don’t want to be enemies with me can stand aside. Those who agree with Streep and want to deal with me, then go stand behind him. Everyone, please choose wisely.”

As soon as Zhao Hai’s words were heard, the people in the Machine Field became a hub of voices. Then one of them loudly said, “Don’t listen to him. He just wants to divide us. We’ve fought hard and he just wants to take advantage of our efforts. We need him to account for his wrongs.”

Another person added, “Right, give us our harvest back!” The others followed shouting. When Xiong Li and the others heard this, their faces paled. They couldn’t help but tightly grab onto their weapons. They looked at Zhao Hai and waited to see what he would do.

Seeing everyone like this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. He just wanted to see if there were other people who weren’t greedy like Streep.

Seeing nobody from the crowd move after some time, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be disappointed. But then, a person’s figure was seen walking out from the crowd. This person was wearing full-body armor and had a long dagger-axe in his hand. He looked like an ancient warrior that walked the battlefield.

However, when Zhao Hai saw this man, his eyes shone. This was because this person was Army Breaker Lu Dingtian, one of the top ten beginners of the Machine Field.

Zhao Hai had a good impression of Lu Dingtian. Although he was quiet, this person had formidable strength. Moreover, if he lost, he lost, and if he won, won. He accepted things for what they were. Seeing Lu Dingtian walk out of the crowd, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but increase his impression of him.

After walking out of the crowd, Lu Dingtian stood aside and didn’t speak. Streep looked at Lu Dingtian and couldn’t help but get angry, then he sneered and said, “Lu Dingtian, is this what you want?”

Lu Dingtian looked at Streep and then coldly snorted as he said, “This Lu Dingtian is an honorable man. I disdain being on the same side as a villain. Streep, you’re unqualified to teach me.”

As soon as Streep heard Lu Dingtian, he angrily said, “Alright. Good, Lu Dingtian, you will certainly regret this.”

Lu Dingtian coldly snorted and didn’t say anything. He wasn’t a talkative man, and with how much disdain he had for Streep, he didn’t bother talking.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about Streep, instead he looked at the others and said, “Nobody else? So everyone else agrees for me to leave everything behind?”

The people behind Streep moved around for a while. However, none of them exited the group and just stood in place.

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Alright, very good. I don’t know if I’m being ungrateful to Mister Lu Dingtian, but how about we team up together, what do you think?”

Lu Dingtian heistated before he finally nodded and then walked towards Zhao Hai. Although Lu Dingtian preferred to keep silent, he wasn’t stupid. In fact he was a smart individual. Otherwise, it would’ve been impossible for him to ascend. He clearly knew that if he only depended on himself in this elimination round, then he wouldn’t be able to reach far. It was also because of this reason that he joined the majority of people in grouping up with Streep. With greater numbers, the possibility to live longer would be higher.

However, he couldn’t stand Streep’s actions. Moreover, Lu Dingtian knew that if Streep was trying to deal with Zhao Hai because of benefits, then there’s no stopping Streep from doing the same to him when the time comes. Therefore, from the present situation, Lu Dingtain knew that staying together with Streep was no longer safe.

On the other hand, things were different when it came to Zhao Hai’s group. Although Zhao Hai hadn’t known Xiong Li and the others for a long time, they were close to each other and their friendship caused even Lu Dingtian to be envious. And from what Lu Dingtian saw in the past few days, Zhao Hai’s strength seemed to be much more than what he had shown. This strength revealed itself from the fact that Zhao Hai was able to kill so many bugs.

Lu DIngtian knew that the others were idiots that had been blinded by greed. They haven’t even thought that since Zhao Hai could kill all those bugs, then he could also kill all of them.

Due to all of these considerations, Lu Dingtian decided to leave Streep and move to Zhao Hai’s side. At the same time, Lu Dingtian was also betting on Zhao Hai to win and that his action this time would make him Zhao Hai’s friend.

And his bet was right! Seeing Lu Dingtian going to his side, Zhao Hai gave him a nod. Lu Dingtian didn’t speak and just held his dagger-axe as he stood beside Zhao Hai. He was prepared to fight at any time.

Seeing Lu Dingtian’s actions, Streep’s eyes could almost spit fire. Lu Dingtian’s actions were no doubt a slap to Streep’s face, so how could he not hate him? But now his biggest enemy was Zhao Hai. Streep believed that as long as he dealt with Zhao Hai, then everything will be alright.

As soon as he discovered that it was Zhao Hai that had rescued them, Streep took out a jade charm from his spatial equipment and then crushed it. All of these talking were merely a means to delay for time.

Therefore, even if Li Dingtian moved to Zhao Hai’s side and Zhao Hai was ignoring him, Streep didn’t immediately move. Instead, he breathed in air to calm his mood. Then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, I know that you’re strong. But aren’t you aware of who everyone here represents? They’re representing the strongest powers of the Machine Field. Do you want to be enemies with everyone?”

Streep was a smart and clever man. Lu Dingtian’s move caused the people behind him to be confused. Although it seems like there were a lot of people on his side, these people were very unstable. If they fought with Zhao Hai, then even a single touch would burst this supposed unity they had. When this happens, then it would be impossible to constrain Zhao Hai. Therefore, he gave those behind him a hint that they shouldn’t be afraid because of their backgrounds. They weren’t just fighting alone, their families were with them. Zhao Hai wouldn’t dare to offend any of them.

Sure enough, as soon as they heard Streep, everyone became calmer. They agreed to Streep’s idea. Even Zhao Hai wouldn’t dare offend so many powers.

Hearing Streep, Zhao Hai’s expression changed as well. Then he said, “Streep, don’t make excuses for your greed. We saved you, but you want to snatch out rewards. This is the only truth.”

When Streep heard Zhao Hai’s response, he couldn’t help but be pleased. He heard the hesitation in Zhao Hai’s words. As long as Zhao Hai was hesitating, then it would be easier to drag out time. This would allow him to squeeze everything out of Zhao Hai.

Seeing Zhao Hai go soft, Streep immediately pushed, he shouted, “Zhao Hai, I’m giving you the last opportunity to return everything. We will let you go. Otherwise, you can’t blame us for being impolite.”

When Streep said this, Zhao Hai suddenly laughed. Not only Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others laughed as well.

At the sight of Zhao Hai’s laughter, Streep couldn’t help but get startled. He found that he had misunderstood Zhao Hai. At this moment, Zhao Hai stopped laughing and said, “Streep, you’re really naive. To be honest, when I felt your killing intent back in Base Number 5, I wanted to kill you. But since I had to give team leader Ma some face, I didn’t make a move. I intend to just leave you to die to the bugs here. I didn’t expect you to court death this early. You’ve been delaying for time aren’t you? As soon as you saw me, you immediately crushed a jade charm to send someone a signal. If I guess right, then someone asked you to inform them when the elimination starts. That person wants to kill me. And this person should be Li Chuchen, correct?”

The more he listened to Zhao Hai’s words, Streep’s face turned uglier. He didn’t expect that his plans would actually be seen through by Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai looked at Streep and said, “Back in Machine Field planet, I managed to block Li Chuchen’s three swords. This matter has become huge in both the Machine Field and the Cultivation Realm. Li Chuchen lost a lot of face, so how could he just let it go? So before he left the Machine Field, he sent you a letter with the jade charm that can tell him where I am when you crush it. He should be rushing over here to kill me right now.”

Streep looked at Zhao Hai with a pale color on his face, because everything Zhao Hai said was correct. Once he crushed the jade charm that Li Chuchen gave him, Li Chuchen would immediately come over to kill Zhao Hai. Streep didn’t expect that everything he has done until now was discovered by Zhao Hai.

Despite his pale face, Streep coldly snorted and didn’t say anything. Zhao Hai didn’t wait for Streep to reply as he continued, “Because of what I did, Li Chuchen wants to kill me. But since he wants to kill me, then I would have to kill him. Keeping a person like that alive in this world is really dangerous.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Streep suddenly laughed and said, “Extremely arrogant. Zhao Hai, you look too highly on yourself. I can recognize that you’re strong, but do you really think that you can compete with Li Chuchen? Especially now. You drank a forbidden potion that burned your potential. You should be much weaker compared to before. You think you can injure Li Chuchen with your Undead? Aren’t you too naive?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Mister Li Chuchen, since you’re here, why don’t you come out? Isn’t it beneath you to be hiding?”

As soon as Zhao Hai’s voice fell, another voice was heard, “You think I’m hiding from you? I didn’t expect you to be naive. You think I’ll let you go since you blocked my three swords?” Along with this voice, a person flew in from a distance. This person was stepping on a blue sword. Naturally, it was Li Chuchen.

Zhao Hai looked at Li Chuchen, and with a faint smile he said, “Mister has become more elegant since the last time. However, it seems like I don’t have any inexcusable feud with mister. Why must you cause trouble?”

Li Chuchen snorted coldly and said, “Who said that there’s no enmity between us? You got famous at the expense of my reputation. This is the biggest enmity. Since you got famous by taking advantage of me, then you should be waiting for my retaliation. Are you prepared to settle your debt?”

Zhao Hai looked at Li Chuchen and then shook his head as he said, “I don’t really want to kill you. After all, you’re from Extreme Cold City. Killing you would cause a lot of trouble for me. But since you want to kill me, then I could only be impolite. Even if Extreme Cold City is hard to deal with, my life is still more important. I just didn’t expect that the second Cultivator I would kill would be you.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Lu Chuchen couldn’t help but sneer, “Zhao Hai, I really don’t know where you get your confidence. Do you really think that you can defeat me?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Of course I could defeat you. However, your opponent wouldn’t be me, he should be fine.” Then as he said that, Zhao Hai pointed towards Dongfang Yu.

Naturally, Dongfang Yu didn’t expect this. He didn’t think that Zhao Hai would make him enter the stage. He looked at Zhao Hai in confusion, waiting for an explanation. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Second Brother, you just learned the fire dragon sword’s methods. Don’t you want someone to test your new strength? Since Li Chuchen is here, then why don’t you clash swords? Don’t worry about anything else, I’m here.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Dongfang Yu’s eyes shone. He nodded and said, “Alright, good. He should be alright to test my sword with. I can now see how strong my fire dragon sword really is.”

The two didn’t lower their volume, so their conversation was heard by everyone. This annoyed Li Chuchen. Whether it be in the lower realms or the Cultivation Realm, he had always been deemed as a genius. But now, he was reduced to a person who someone tests their sword with. Li Chuchen was incensed, but he didn’t say anything. He just watched Zhao Hai and Dongfang Yu, but his face failed to hide his anger.

Zhao Hai looked at Dongfang Yu as he smiled and said, “Second Brother, let’s chat later. It seems like he’ll be so mad he’ll spit blood.”

Zhao Hai’s remark caused Xiong Li and the others to laugh. And although Lu Dingtian was putting on a serious expression, a smile couldn’t help but bloom on his face.

Chapter 1231: Plum Blossom Sword Technique

Li Chuchen was already pale with anger as he looked at Zhao Hai. He was a Heaven’s Chosen. Normally, people would lose in arguing against him. But now, it seems like he has been put down by Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything. Instead, he chuckled for a few moments as he talked Dongfang Yu into fighting. Dongfang Yu held his fire dragon sword in front of Li Chuchen. Then he sneered towards Li Chuchen and said, “I didn’t expect the Cultivators to have tolerance this low. Losing a battle of three swords actually went to your head. This truly broadened my view.”

Li Chuchen coldly snorted and said, “Yapping is useless. You will all die today!”

Dongfang Yu sneered and said, “You want to kill us? Then you need to prove yourself. Let Grandpa Dongfang test your sword first.”

His words caused Zhao Hai and the others to laugh once more. Zhao Hai loudly said, “Second Brother, Third Brother Li said that those words don’t sound great coming from your mouth. Hahaha”

Li Kuangren and the others also laughed. This caused the faces of Streep and the others to change. Even after seeing Li Chuchen, Zhao Hai still had the capacity to joke freely. There were only two implications for this. First was that they were simply insane. But looking at it, Zhao Hai and the others weren’t crazy. The second reason was because they didn’t treat Li Chuchen seriously. They weren’t afraid of Li Chuchen.

Dongfang Yu waved his hand and released his fire dragon sword. But this time, he used his fire dragon art. The fire dragon sword immediately burned with fire. Then it surrounded Dongfang Yu like a fire dragon.

When Streep saw this, he couldn’t help but shudder. Then his expression changed. Only cultivators had methods that can control swords like this. The Machine Field’s practitioners simply couldn’t do it. This could only mean that Dongfang Yu had learned a cultivation method.

Li Chuchen’s expression changed as well. Then he calmed down as he sneered and said, “You want to fight me just because you managed to learn a flying sword technique? I really don’t know what to say. But let me show you a real flying sword technique.” Then he waved his hand and also used a flying sword technique. Before long, Li Chuchen’s blue skyfrost sword flew straight towards Dongfang Yu.

Although Dongfang Yu was a beginner in using flying swords, the sealed fire dragon sword has given him a lot of information. This information didn’t only include techniques and methods, it also included insights and experiences regarding those techniques. If explained in Buddhist terms, it provided Dongfang Yu with enlightenment.

Because of this, even if Dongfang Yu was a beginner in controlling flying swords, his experience wasn’t very bad. It was only because he hadn’t used such a technique before that he was quite awkward in using it, but he was gradually adapting to the technique. Naturally, he wasn’t fazed by Li Chuchen’s sword.

The fire dragon sword moved and swayed like a real dragon as it welcomed the skyfrost sword. Coldness and heat were two natural enemies, now two swords of the same attributes were going to clash.

Boom! A loud sound was heard. Dongfang Yu and Li Chuchen’s faces both changed. Dongfang Yu suffered a small loss since the time he studied the Divine Fire Dragon Art was too short. His foundation was still shallow.

But at the same time, Li Chuchen didn’t fare well. This was because the skyfrost sword was inferior to the fire dragon sword. In terms of sword quality, Li Chuchen also suffered a loss.

It can be said that the clash was somewhat even. Li Chuchen’s expression turned ugly. He didn’t expect his move to be countered to this extent. This was unacceptable. He coldly snorted and said, “Die!” Then he waved his hand as he commanded his sword to swing towards Dongfang Yu. But at this time, Li Chuchen’s eyes flashed a cold light. All of a sudden,  a disk flew out and went straight towards Dongfang Yu.

The disk was very sharp, its entire body was pitch black. As it rotated, the wailing of ghosts was heard. This caused everyone who heard it to unconsciously shiver.

Dongfang Yu didn’t expect Li Chuchen to use such an attack. And it was now impossible to withdraw the defending fire dragon sword. But at this moment, a hand suddenly appeared and grabbed the disk. Then a voice was heard, “I said that Brother Dongfang needs to try his sword. Sneak attacks aren’t allowed.”

Zhao Hai looked at the disk as though it was an ordinary item then threw it to the Space. In the next moment, he reappeared next to Xiong Li and the others.

Zhao Hai’s action caused everyone to shake, including Li Chuchen. That weapon couldn’t just be easily caught. That disk wasn’t a weapon of Extreme Cold City but was a weapon Li Chuchen gained from killing a Ghost Cultivator. It was known as spinning ghost disk. Its speed was fast and also had elements of a sound attack. Most importantly, this weapon was very sharp. Most weapons wouldn’t be able to block it. Back when Li Chuchen faced the spinning ghost disk, he broke his weapon and was almost injured by the ghost cultivator.

He sneakily took out the spinning ghost disk in order to kill Dongfang Yu. He was very confident in the disk because of its speed and the timing. Dongfang Yu wouldn’t be able to escape even if Zhao Hai wanted to save him.

However, Li Chuchen didn’t expect his plan to be broken by Zhao Hai. Moreover, Zhao Hai dealt with it with ease, he didn’t even treat it seriously.

At the same time, Li Chuchen began to dread Zhao Hai’s strength. Zhao Hai caught the spinning ghost disk empty handed. Even Li Chuchen wasn’t able to do this.

Li Chuchen couldn’t help but complain about his bad luck. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be so strong. He heard about Zhao Hai fighting back against the silverback gold-winged bug alone. Back then, he thought that people were speaking nonsense. And if it was possible, then Zhao Hai should have drunk a forbidden potion. But now it seems like Zhao Hai’s strength was the real deal.

Zhao Hai looked at Li Chuchen, then he smiled and said, “Young Master Li, please be serious in comparing notes with Second Brother Dongfang. Rest assured, after your done, I’ll turn you into one of them. Having you would be very interesting.” While saying that, Zhao Hai gestured towards the Undead standing not far from him.

Whether it be Li Chuchen or Streep, everyone was shocked when they heard Zhao Hai words. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be so ruthless. He even clarified that they wouldn’t be able to survive today.

Li Chuchen’s expression changed, he coldly snorted and said, “Very arrogant. You really think that you can kill me? I’ll let you see my true strength!”

As he said that, Li Chuchen put away his skyfrost sword and then took out another one. Compared to the skyfrost sword, this sword was different. This sword was entirely white. The hilt looked like an ordinary plum blossom. It meandered and seemed to be unsuitable for grasping.

Upon seeing this sword, Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he smiled faintly and said, “I didn’t expect Extreme Cold City to give you a plum blossom sword. It seems like you learned the plum blossom technique as well?”

The location of Extreme Cold City could be said to be a world of white. The scenery around the city could be called a plum forest. And the entire Extreme Cold City was a very huge plum forest. However, this plum forest wasn’t just a simple scenery. This plum forest was a great formation known as the Plum Blossom Bitter Cold Myriad Sword Formation. It was a very famous formation in the Cultivation Realm.

The plum blossom sword technique was a legend in Extreme Cold City. It was a sword technique that was created by the founding ancestor of Extreme Cold City. It was said that the ancestor was watching the plum blossoms in cold snow when they created this technique. Once used, the plum blossom technique wasn’t only powerful, the sword would also bloom like a plum blossom and then scatter snow around like plum petals in the wind. The technique was beyond beautiful once executed.

Although the plum blossom technique was the signature technique of Extreme Cold City, not anybody can use it. Only inner disciples of Extreme Cold City can learn the technique. Moreover, they could only learn the first nine moves. The other nine moves could only be learned by core disciples.

The plum blossom sword was as famous as the plum blossom technique. The plum blossom sword was a signature weapon of the inner disciples of Extreme Cold City. The forging technique of the sword was also created by the founding ancestor. Although the might of the replicas was just 1% of the original plum blossom sword, creating one wasn’t very easy. It was impossible for outer disciples to get one. Zhao Hai didn’t expect Li Chuchen to actually have one.

After hearing Zhao Hai, Li Chuchen couldn’t help but sneer as he said, “I didn’t expect a country bumpkin like you to know about this sword. But in the end, you’re a bumpkin. Today, I’ll let you experience the might of Extreme Cold City’s plum sword technique!”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Extreme Cold City’s plum blossom technique has a huge reputation. So how could this Zhao Hai be ignorant of it? However, you can’t see the true essence of the technique from just a few moves.”

Li Chuchen just coldly snorted. To him, Zhao Hai’s words were satirizing him, so he didn’t listen to it. He waved his hand and released the plum blossom sword. Then he used the technique, causing the sword to tremble and then vanish from sight. White plum petals began falling from the sky and then headed towards Zhao Hai’s group. This plum blossom was very beautiful. However, Zhao Hai knew that these plum blossoms were capable of taking human lives.

Zhao Hai was aware that Dongfang Yu’s experience in battling with the new fire dragon sword was very small. Although he had obtained Fire Dragon Daoist’s inheritance, it wasn’t easy to comprehend and digest battle experience. It seems like Dongfang Yu wouldn’t be able to stop Li Chuchen’s attack.

Zhao Hai coldly snorted as he waved his hand and released a 100-layer formation. This formation exploded and then became a huge inferno. Its might seemed to burn the heavens and the earth. This inferno welcomed the approach of the plum blossoms.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s move, Li Chuchen sneered and said, “Good, it seems like you improved compared to last time. But Zhao Hai, you are destined to die under my plum blossom sword today. I’ll let you suffer the disgrace of being killed by Extreme Cold City’s snow!”

Then as he said that, Li Chuchen’s aura rose. Then at the same time he shouted, “The Plum Blossom born from extreme cold!”

After he said that, the plum blossom sword stabbed straight towards Zhao Hai.

Chapter 1232: Might of the Exterminating Fist

The plum blossom sword goes up, the plum blossom rain falls. The sky was blotted by the plum blossom rain, drenching Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai could even feel himself standing in a plum forest. The petals of the plum blossom looked like simple rain, he could also smell the plum blossom. However, this was what made this rain very terrifying!

The chills seem to go straight for the bottom of a person’s heart. It gave a feeling that it could freeze a person’s mind, a person’s body, and a person’s soul!

The Plum Blossom born from extreme cold. It was a move of freezing coming from the plum blossom. The domain imposed by the sword was truly outstanding. It seems like if one doesn’t have real skill, then nobody would be able to deal with Li Chuchen.

Zhao Hai coldly snorted. He didn’t take something out of his robe, nor did he use any spells. This time, he stood in the air and then stepped forward before punching out!

Nobody had ever imagined Zhao Hai to attack using his fist. Moreover, it looks like a very ordinary punch. Such a stance could be used by anyone in the World of Cultivation. And since this punch was too ordinary, there would be a million ways for the enemy to break it. If it was broken, then it meant that the enemy would have the initiative for attack. In this case, why would Zhao Hai use such a method? It was because of this that everyone was stunned.

Others might be clueless about the might behind Zhao Hai’s fist, but Li Chuchen who was the recipient of the punch knew very well. Li Chuchen’s current state wasn’t so good. He thought that his move ‘the plum blossom born from extreme cold’ couldn’t be blocked by the punch. However, once the fist met with the technique, Li Chuchen finally felt that he was wrong.

The fist was as heavy as the mountain, like a meteor. As soon as Zhao Hai punched out, Li Chuchen felt a huge meteor slamming into himself. The domain imposed by the plum blossom couldn’t compare to the explosive strength of the fist. In almost an instant, the plum blossom domain was destroyed with the fist that could destroy the heavens and the earth. All of it disappeared like smoke!

Li Chuchen was shocked. Zhao Hai’s fist broke his sword technique. And Zhao Hai’s fist didn’t stop. It continued towards Li Chuchen. The pressure seemed to wrap the skies, causing Li Chuchen to feel as though he was a person standing in the meteor’s orbit trying to block it

A mantis trying to stop a chariot! This statement suddenly appeared inside Li Chuchen’s mind. He discovered that his confidence completely vanished. As Zhao Hai’s fist approached him, he actually felt genuine fear!

Li Chuchen was a determined person. He bit his teeth to calm his senses. Then he moved his hand and took out a turtle shell to block in front of him. It was a shield large enough to cover his entire body.

But it was also at this moment that Zhao Hai’s fist arrived. Actually, Zhao Hai just stood in place, it was only the projected qi of his fist that travelled the distance and hit Li Chuchen’s shield. There was a loud noise before the shield shattered. The fist, now unblocked, continued to hit towards Li Chuchen.

Li Chuchen felt the pain on his chest. The fist qi travelled through his internal organs. Li Chuchen felt his five solid organs and six hollow organs being crushed. He vomited blood. His two eyes stubbornly looking at Zhao Hai. He didn’t think his gap with Zhao Hai was this huge. He couldn’t even take Zhao Hai’s fist.[1]

This was also the final thought that crossed through Li Chuchen’s mind before everything went dark. Zhao Hai waved his hand as black gas surrounded Li Chuchen’s body. After the black gas vanished, what remained was Li Chuchen’s skeleton.

Streep and the others stared at the skeleton wearing Li Chuchen’s robes. It was also at this time that people discovered that Li Chuchen was wearing inner armor that was as thin as a cicada’s wing. It was woven with gold threads that looked beautiful. But this time, a hole was in the middle of this armor. The size of this hole was as big as the fist that Zhao Hai just made.

What struck them even more was the plum blossom sword that kept floating beside the skeleton. It was as if the sword didn’t notice that Li Chuchen had already been turned into an Undead.

Zhao Hai coldly snorted, then he turned his head towards Streep and said, “Streep, it’s time to settle our account.”

Everyone was still stunned by what happened. After hearing Zhao Hai’s words, Streep and the others changed their expressions. Then everyone began to feel regret, especially Streep. His face was very pale. But this time, he wasn’t pale with anger, but instead with fear.

Zhao Hai looked at Streep and the others and said, “I didn’t really intend to deal with you just because I want to give face to the Machine Field. However, all of you wanted to deal with me. Especially you, Streep. Do you really think that I don’t know about your ability? You rely on women to collect yin qi. Then you use this yin qi to improve your attacks. If not for the yin qi, you would just be an ordinary level 4 Mage. I can’t blame you for using women like that, but only as long as they do it voluntarily. You can play with as many women as you want, that’s your method. However, you shouldn’t have killed them. You wear a gentle mask but behind it is a ruthless face. I initially wanted to deal with you when the elimination round is about to end. But who would’ve thought that you would find trouble with me first. You even pulled these people’s backgrounds over to deal with me. You really think that I will submit? Streep, you’re too naive. This is Fabio Planet’s underworld. Even if all of you die, the Machine Field still wouldn’t say anything. Now, since you want to deal with me, then be proud of becoming new members of my Undead army!”

After he said that, Zhao Hai waved his hand then Undead began appearing everywhere. These Undead immediately threw themselves towards Streep’s group.

Streep and the others turned frantic. They initially wanted to beg for mercy, but Zhao Hai didn’t give them the opportunity to do so. The Undead attacks were extremely sharp. And since they were in a formation, they were much harder to deal with. The defenses formed by Streep’s group were quickly torn apart by the Undead. After being separated into smaller groups, it didn’t take a long time before they succumbed to the Undead’s attacks.

Xiong Li and the others looked at the scene with cold gazes. They were disappointed with these people so they didn’t stop Zhao Hai. Moreover, they knew that Zhao Hai wasn’t the kind of person that would let this matter go.

The only one surprised was Lu Dingtian. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this ruthless and kill everybody. Seeing the number of Zhao Hai’s Undead, Lu Dingtian began to understand how Zhao Hai was able to deal with so many bugs.

At this time, the Machine Field’s participants were almost wiped out. There were only a few alive, including Streep. Although his cultivation method had yet to be known by Zhao Hai, it has to be said that yin qi was very effective in increasing offensive strength. This was the reason why he was able to survive this long.

Naturally, this was also because the Undead Li Chuchen didn’t join the fight. Otherwise, Streep wouldn’t be able to stop Li Chuchen’s attack.

Streep had deep despair in his eyes. While he was resisting the Undead attacks, he shouted towards Zhao Hai, “Zhao Hai, I’ll do anything as long as you let me go. I ask you to let us off.”

Zhao Hai looked at Streep and said, “I don’t need you to do anything other than dying!”

Streep shouted back, “If you let me go, I’ll tell you my cultivation method. This is a method used by an ancient cultivator. I already destroyed the jade slip containing the method. As long as you let me go, I’ll tell you..”

Zhao Hai sneered and said, “I’m not interested in your cultivation method. And even if I was, I can still find out about it once I turn you into an Undead. I don’t need you to survive, I can just wait until you become an obedient Undead.”

As soon as Streep heard this, his final ray of hope vanished. He could only wildly curse, “Zhao Hai, you’ll die like a dog. You have made so much Undead. Sooner or later, you will pay for everything!”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “You don’t need to worry about this. Now you can die with ease.”

After he said that, Zhao Hai flicked his finger. Then Streep suddenly stopped moving. The spirit in his eyes began to disappear. He was dead, killed by Liquid Silver’s needle.

Actually, Zhao Hai had long wanted to kill him with the silver needle. However, he needed to make Streep suffer for a while. It could be considered revenge for those women that Streep killed.

Streep’s murder of women was unknown to Zhao Hai until a few days ago. When Streep cultivated, he would need a lot of yin from women. Some of these women were provided to him by Ba Dong, while some were enticed by him. However, a large part of these women were forcefully seized. These women suffered intensely as their yin was extracted. And then in the end, they would die. It seems like Streep had a sick hobby of watching women suffer. All of these were saved in his computer, waiting to be viewed.

Streep was still very honest some time ago. However, after he was particularly annoyed by Zhao Hai, he returned to his room and watched those videos. It was only then that Zhao Hai came to know about this matter. These events strengthened Zhao Hai’s determination to kill him.

The reason why Zhao Hai revealed everything to Streep before killing him was because he wanted Streep to know why he was killed. What he did to those women was already enough for Streep to be executed.

Another reason why Zhao Hai decided to use the silver needle to kill Streep was because he discovered that Streep wanted to use a small nuclear bomb. If Streep managed to detonate that bomb, even if Zhao Hai survived, then a lot of Undead would be killed in the process. So before Streep could execute his final plan, Zhao Hai decided to just have the needle strike Streep’s brain.

* * *

The five solid organs of traditional chinese medicine: heart(hsin), liver(gan), spleen(pi), lungs(fei), and kidney(sen). And the six hollow organs of traditional chinese medicine: small intestine(shao chang), gallbladder(tan), stomach(wei), large intestine(ta chang), urinary bladder(pang guang), triple heater(san jiao). The triple heaters were regarded as an organ that has a name but no form..

Chapter 1233: Attacking A Bug Nest

The battle was already over. Everyone from the Machine Field was killed. Moreover, those who died had now become members of Zhao Hai’s Undead army.

After dealing with these people, Zhao Hai made the Undead clean the battlefield. Every bug part was collected and piled up in equal portions on the ground. Then Zhao Hai and the others stored their pile in their spatial equipment, Lu Dingtian did the same.

Lu Dingtian’s actions made Zhao Hai regard him as a friend. Lu Dingtian also didn’t say anything and just collected his own pile. He was also beginning to look at Zhao Hai as a friend. But since he was embarrassed, he wasn’t able to say his thanks to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about it. After taking his own pile, he looked at everyone and said, “Brothers, it’s only us left. Hahaha. I reckon we’re the most insane out of all the six realms. We already butchered our own people just as the competition began.”

Xiong Li and the others couldn’t help but laugh. They didn’t think much about it. This was because they knew that if they weren’t as strong as they were, then the ones who would die would be them. They felt no guilt about this event.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “We should leave this place and look for some bugs to kill. Otherwise, we wouldn’t be able to get to the top 100. That would be troublesome.”

Xiong Li smiled and said, “Killing those bugs is quite easy. It’s not interesting. Right, Little Hai, what do we do if we run into people from other realms?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “What else can we do? If we can defeat them, then we’ll kill them all. If we can’t defeat them, then we can just escape. In any case, they would certainly try to kill us. The Machine Field really has a great reputation.”

Xiong Li and the others laughed. They agreed that the Machine Field has a great reputation. However, this reputation wasn’t a good one, but the reputation that they were soft persimmons.

Xiong Li and the others were confident in Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai was able to kill a top ten ranker of the Cultivation Realm with a single fist. With Zhao Hai’s strength, why would they be afraid of the other realms?

Lu Dingtian looked at the brothers who were laughing and joking with a touch of envy in his eyes. Ever since he ascended, he had always been cautious. He wouldn’t easily believe anyone. This was because he had seen a lot of geniuses that suddenly disappeared into obscurity. It was a world where a friend could become an enemy in the blink of an eye. Because of this, Lu Dingtian was never able to make any friends. He just cultivated and performed tasks given by his family.

Due to his lifestyle, Lu Dingtian was able to become strong. But at the same time, he was envious of people like Zhao Hai and the others who were brothers that cared for each other.

Zhao Hai looked at Lu Dingtain and then smiled as he said, “Old Lu, it seems like you’re stuck with us. Rest assured, now that we’re teammates, we’re also friends. I hope that we can get closer in the future.”

Lu Dingtian nodded but didn’t say anything. Zhao Hai didn’t mind it as he nodded and said, “Let’s go. It’s time to look for bugs to kill.” Then after he said that, he led everyone out of the cave.

While Zhao Hai and the others were in battle, Laura released silver needles in order to inspect the surrounding caves. And not far from the cave that Zhao Hai and the others were in was a large collection of eight-legged bugs.

These eight-legged bugs can be said to be the Bug Race’s most populous species. They were also at the very bottom of the race’s hierarchy, completely made to be cannon fodder. These eight-legged bugs lived inside nests. However, these nests weren’t queen nests of the Bug Race. Instead, these were nests that produced only eight-legged bugs. Nevertheless, the production rate of these nests was very astonishing. In a year, an eight-legged bug nest could produce more than 100 thousand bugs. Such reproductive speed can only be described as completely broken.

It was precisely because of this nest’s reproduction that the Cultivation Realm needed to clean the bugs from Fabio Planet regularly. Although the strength of the eight-legged bugs wasn’t on par with the Cultivators, once their number reached a critical degree, the might they could exhibit would be astonishing. Moreover, their offensive strength wasn’t very weak.

The intelligence of these eight-legged bugs was very low, but their territorial instincts were strong. If other eight-legged bugs were to enter their territory, they would immediately frantically attack. After seeing the eight-legged worm nest, Zhao Hai was almost certain that the bugs that besieged them in the transmission formation were from the same group.

From the research that the Cultivation Realm did on the eight-legged bugs, Zhao Hai knew that these bugs were divided into two groups. The first group was called ‘hunting bugs’, these were bugs that go out and hunt for food. The other group was called ‘guard bugs’, the bugs that defended the nest.

Eight-legged bugs were omnivores. Whether it be other bugs or leaves or grass, they would all consume it. The hunting bugs’ main job was to seek these kinds of food for the nest. The task of the guard bugs was much simpler. Their duty was to protect the bug nest.

The insane reproductive ability of the eight-legged bugs would also cause trouble for themselves. Bug tides would happen all over Fabio Planet due to the bugs being overpopulated. When it’s time for a bug tide, they would target the Cultivation Realm’s bases as well as other bug groups. This wouldn’t only reduce the number of eight-legged bugs, it would also provide food for other bugs.

For the Bug Race, nothing was inedible. As long as it can provide them with energy, then it was food.

Naturally, the bugs that attacked Zhao Hai and the others were hunting bugs. But now that they were heading to the bug nest, they would fight the guard bugs soon.

Zhao Hai was aware of all of these, but the others weren’t. They just followed Zhao Hai and carefully flew forward. Zhao Hai and the others were now quite close to the nest. They would arrive in about half an hour.

Before long, they arrived in the nest’s territory. Zhao Hai waved his hand, causing everyone to stop and look at him. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Wait a moment.” Then he waved his hand and a large number of Undead appeared. Shortly after being summoned, the Undead attacked the bug nest.

The bug nest was divided into multiple layers with countless caves. These caves were connected to each other, forming a vast network of caves that only the bugs could navigate.

The center of the bug nest was a huge cave with a height of more than 400 meters and a floor area that spanned tens of thousands of square meters. There’s a huge organic ball in the middle of the cave that housed the eight-legged bug queen. This was also the structure that the guard bugs protected.

Several circular paths were on the periphery of this huge bug nest. Each passage was about 3-400 meters wide and 200 meters high. Eight-legged bugs patrol these paths regularly. On each passage would be 10 thousand patrolling bugs. It could be estimated that the number of bugs in this nest numbered in the hundreds of thousands.

Zhao Hai and the others were now in the outermost region of the nest. All in all, Zhao Hai released 5000 Undead. They would be the first line against the bugs.

Zhao Hai didn’t release too much Undead since he wants Xiong Li and the others to have a go at the bugs. Although the bugs were dangerous to them, the threat wasn’t that huge. This would also allow Xiong Li and the others to get familiar with their weapons. If they relied on the Undead the entire time, then the purpose of the elimination round would be lost.

Xiong Li and the others were also waiting for an opportunity to raise this issue with Zhao Hai. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be the one to mention it. Naturally, they were glad with this arrangement. They immediately roared and took out their own weapons.

Among those present, only Sun Fei and Lu Dingtian’s weapons weren’t very good. Sun Fei was a Mage, and the Fire Temple had already prepared a lot of good things for him. His magic staff alone provided him with a lot of support. However, this weapon wasn’t manufactured by Zhao Hai, so it didn’t have the weapon shattering property. This caused Sun Fei to feel unsatisfied. But Zhao Hai already made a promise that he would prepare him a staff with weapon shattering once the elimination round was done.

The weapon that Lu Dingtian used was still the dagger-axe. He had used this weapon for several years so he was quite familiar with it. Moreover, after repeated upgrades by the Dong Family, the weapon became very compatible with Lu Dingtian. Since Lu Dingtian wasn’t friends with Zhao Hai before, then it’s a given that his weapon doesn’t have weapon shattering. Actually, Lu Dingtian wasn’t aware that Xiong Li and the others had weapons that had weapon shattering.

As soon as Zhao Hai and the others entered the first perimeter of defense, the bugs immediately found them. One by one, bugs began streaming in. Naturally, the Undead were being commanded by Megan and the others. At the same time, Xiong Li and the others rushed over and began killing bugs with their weapons. Only Zhao Hai stayed still and stood by, watching the battlefield with a keen eye.

With Zhao Hai’s present strength, fighting the bugs would no longer benefit him. What he needed to do now was to make sure that Xiong Li and the others were safe.

Although Xiong Li and the others weren’t weak, these eight-legged bugs didn’t know fear. These bugs were tenacious. If Xiong Li and the others make a mistake, then they would be injured.

Zhao Hai took Xiong Li and the others here so that they could practice. They weren’t here to go all out against these bugs. Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t want them to receive any injury.

This kind of guided trial was something that big sects in the Cultivation Realm only do to their Core Disciples. Most inner and outer sect disciples would never have gotten such attention.

This was also possible because Zhao Hai’s strength has been greatly improved. Otherwise, he wouldn’t be able to do this.

Zhao Hai noticed that the battle had moved to open ground. Two more groups of eight-legged bugs joined the battle. Zhao Hai expected this, so he had more of the Undead participate in the battle.

Xiong Li and the others were now immersed in battle, shouting as they attacked the bugs. However, they weren’t able to kill the bugs faster than the Undead.

The coordination between the Undead was perfect. This allowed them to dispose of the bugs in a very efficient manner. Because of this, it was naturally impossible for Xiong Li and the others to surpass them in killing speed.

Zhao Hai didn’t allow Xiong Li and the others to kill the bugs alongside the Undead. The Undead were being commanded to perfection by Megan and the others. If Xiong Li and the others join in, then the Undead coordination would be destroyed. Therefore, Xiong Li and the others formed their own group and fought the bugs themselves.

It must be said that Xiong Li and the others weren’t that much stronger compared to the Undead. Although they had more powerful weapons, they were still beginners in using it. On the other hand, when the Space leveled up, the bone armor and the golden combat suits were upgraded. The bone armor and the combat suits were no weaker than the Machine Field’s items.

Zhao Hai stood in the air and would often shoot spells to support Xiong Li and the others. Seeing Zhao Hai’s action, Xiong Li and the others didn’t say anything. Instead, they felt relieved as they focused on killing the bugs.

The fight continued for some time. Due to Zhao Hai’s support, Xiong Li and the others were completely fine and were happily attacking the bugs. However, the first one to give up was Sun Fei. Because he has gained new spells from Zhao Hai, Sun Fei was very eager to try them out. He tried each formation and ran out of energy before long. So he took a potion and then went to Zhao Hai’s side to rest.

Zhao Hai didn’t mind Sun Fei as he continued to pay attention to the battle. On the other hand, Sun Fei was observing Zhao Hai’s actions. This was especially true whenever Zhao Hai made a move. Sun Fei discovered that Zhao Hai doesn’t use formidable spells in order to save Xiong Li and the others. Most of the time, Zhao Hai would use ten-layer spells, rarely would he use 100-layer formations. The amount of formation layers he would use was just enough to save Xiong Li and the others. He wouldn’t waste energy.

As time went by, Sun Fei was able to somewhat take note of Zhao Hai’s tactics. He found that Zhao Hai had been in a complete state of control over the entire battlefield. The moves that Xiong LI and the others did as well as the attacks made by the bugs seem to be under Zhao Hai’s influence. Sun Fei noticed several times that Zhao Hai would prepare a spell seconds in advance. This showed how long Zhao Hai had anticipated the development of the battlefield. This ability to control the battle was extremely terrifying.

Sun Fei examined himself and knew that he would be unable to do this. However, he didn’t feel depressed. He continued to observe Zhao Hai in earnest. Although he couldn’t achieve the degree of Zhao Hai’s ability, he can still learn a few things. This experience was important for a Mage. When to use magic was one of the most important things that a Mage needed to learn. Being able to gain this ability would increase a Mage’s battle proficiency by at least three layers.

Time went by and Lu Dingtian was the next person to give up. After all, his weapon was still ordinary. Because of this, the battle qi he used was much greater compared to Xiong Li and the others. He drank a potion of recovery before going to Zhao Hai’s side to rest.

Chapter 1234: Transforming Bug Nest

The eight-legged bugs were still frantically attacking. These bugs survive on instinct, so they didn’t have any fear in them at all. The only thing they knew was attacking and killing their enemies.

Soon after, Xiong Li and Li Kuangren gave up. Although their weapons had been transformed by Zhao Hai, they still weren’t able to fight for a very long time. They took a potion like Lu Dingtian did and then went to Zhao Hai’s side to rest.

The only one left on the field was Dongfang Yu. Although his fight with Li Chuchen ended in almost an instant, it still made Dongfang Yu aware about the strength of the Cultivators in the Cultivator Realm. Without Zhao Hai’s help, he would’ve already died under Li Chuchen’s spinning ghost disk.

However, Dongfang Yu believed that he wasn’t any worse compared to Li Chuchen. HIs only disadvantage was his short time in studying the Divine Fire Dragon Art. Otherwise, he wouldn’t lose that easily against Li Chuchen. Therefore, Dongfang Yu made sure to use the current battle with the bugs to train his Divine Fire Dragon Art as well as his fire dragon sword technique.

It was at this moment that the difference between the Machine Field’s method and the Cultivation Realm’s method appeared. Xiong Li and the others were already tired, their battle qi was consumed, they don’t have any capability to fight. Meanwhile, Dongfang Yu was still fighting. Moreover, he was becoming more and more skilled when it came to using his fire dragon sword. This also allowed him to be more relaxed in battle.

After watching Dongfang Yu, Xiong Li and the others finally knew why he was able to fight for so long. This was due to the difference between flying swords and sword qi.

Flying sword techniques allowed one to control their sword to fly and kill their enemy. Meanwhile, sword qi was akin to arrows being shot out by a bow. Once it was in motion, it could no longer be controlled. It was the same difference between artillery shells and remote missiles.

One must know that enemies that would just stand there to take the hit were very rare. Most of them would just avoid the attack. Even the bugs who lived on instinct knew to avoid sword qi. Even if they couldn’t completely avoid the attack, they would still make sure that their vital organs weren’t hit. In this case, taking someone’s life using sword qi was very hard.

Flying swords were different. Once a flying sword was set in motion, it could still be controlled. Even if the bugs managed to dodge, the sword could still home in on their vital parts. This allowed Dongfang Yu to kill a large amount of bugs while keeping his energy consumption to a minimum.

With this thought in mind, Xiong Li and the others couldn’t help but be envious of Dongfang Yu’s luck in being able to obtain a Cultivation Method.

At this moment, Zhao Hai’s voice was heard, “After this competition, everyone can also practice a Cultivation Method. Look, haven’t we already gained a water-attribute method?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others stared. Then they immediately understood what Zhao Hai was saying. They managed to kill Li Chuchen who practiced a high-level water-attribute cultivation method. Now that Li Chuchen has become Zhao Hai’s Undead, this meant that they could also practice this water-attribute cultivation method.

But after thinking about it, Xiong Li and Li Kuangren weren’t happy. This was because they were both earth-attribute. A water-attribute cultivation method was useless to them. Meanwhile, Sun Fei doesn’t need to wait until the competition to learn Dongfang Yu’s Divine Fire Dragon Art.

However, they still had hope. If they could kill a water-attribute Cultivator today, then what’s stopping them from killing an earth-attribute Cultivator tomorrow? When the time comes, they would have their own cultivation method.

Seeing Dongfang Yu’s sword technique becoming more and more refined, Zhao Hai stopped looking and instead turned to the others and said, “When we get a few more Cultivation Methods, I’ll take a look at them first if they’re good to practice. You should know that I have all the attributes. Right, Old Lu, what attribute do you have?”

Lu Dingtian paused for a moment before replying, “Metal attribute.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he nodded and said, “Metal? That’s good. Then we’ll grab every attribute there is. This way, we can find appropriate ones in the future.”

The fight with the bugs was nearing its end. Xiong Li and the others might not have killed a lot of bugs, but the Undead absolutely did. At this time there weren’t a lot of bugs left in the passage.

Moreover, from what Zhao Hai can see, only the bugs from the first and second perimeter came to fight. The bugs from the third, fourth, and fifth perimeter of defense didn’t move.

Before long, the battle was over and the Undead began clearing the battlefield. Xiong Li and the others looked at the Undead with envy. Xiong Li murmured, “Having these fellows is truly convenient. Especially at this time. Others have to divide the bugs to themselves while we can just sit here and chat.”

Upon hearing Xiong Li, Zhao Hai and the others laughed. Dongfang Yu received his sword at this time, then he looked at Xiong Li and said, “Boss Xiong, how about you ask Little Hai to teach you summoning magic?”

Xiong Li immediately shook his head and said, “Forget it. I still have to learn magic then how to write magic formations. It’s too troublesome.”

The group laughed once more. Zhao Hai wasn’t anxious to continue attacking. Everyone had just finished a battle and they needed to take a good rest. It would be unwise to attack now.

At this time, the Undead were done cleaning up. The bugs were divided evenly and every useful material were taken out.

Zhao Hai and the others didn’t hurry in getting the materials. Instead, they sat down and then chatted. Although there were a lot of bug corpses around them, they were used to such an environment so they didn’t care.

The reason why Zhao Hai was assured in taking a rest here was because he knew that there weren’t any dangers in the surroundings, unless someone from the other realm or an advanced-level bug came. Besides those, no other eight-legged bugs were nearby.

This nest belonged to eight-legged bugs. And since the area belonged to this particular nest of bugs, eight-legged bugs from other nests wouldn’t come near. This was because the territorial consciousness of the eight-legged bugs was very strong.

After resting for two hours, everyone had almost recovered. Zhao Hai gave a nod and said, “Let’s go and continue the attack. I believe that there would be pleasant surprises waiting for us today.”

Xiong Li and the others still weren’t aware that they were inside a bug nest. Moreover, they weren’t able to scout the area ahead of them like Zhao Hai. Also, this cave system restricted the use of spiritual force. This caused Xiong Li and the others to be relatively clueless about their surroundings.

In the past, the Cultivators wanted to map out the cave systems so that they could fight the bugs better. However, they soon discovered that it was useless. This was because the passages transform constantly. These bugs would dig more caves and passages while also burying old ones. This caused any maps made to be scrapped.

After multiple explorations into the cave system, the Cultivators also found out that the bugs secret a type of mucus. This mucus is very potent. As long as it gets mixed in with the earth, it would make the ground as strong as concrete.

Most importantly, this mucus had the ability to restrict spiritual force. But once the bugs were killed, this mucus would quickly dry up, unable to be used. From the Cultivation Realm’s investigations, almost the entire underground system was covered by this mucus. Therefore, whether it be the Cultivators or the people from other realms, when they enter the cave system, their spiritual force would be affected. One could use magic to explore, but spiritual force was impossible.

It can be said that having the elimination round here was giving Zhao Hai a home ground advantage. He can use the silver needles to explore the surroundings first. And since this was on the outer layer of Fabio Planet, advanced-level bugs were very rare. So even if the silver needle was found out, it couldn’t be dealt with easily. Zhao Hai used the silver needle to perfectly grasp the situation inside this bug nest. Naturally, this gave him an advantage in the competition.

Additionally, Zhao Hai had a lot of Undead to help him hunt and kill the bugs. The results of this elimination round would definitely surprise a lot of people.

Although Xiong Li and the others didn’t know about the situation ahead, they already had absolute confidence in Zhao Hai. In their opinion, the only thing they needed to do was follow Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai led Xiong Li and the others towards a passage. While they were flying, Zhao Hai suddenly heard Laura’s voice, “Brother Hai, you need to take care. The fourth and fifth defensive line’s bugs had reinforced the third defensive line’s bugs. The eight-legged bugs that you would face will number 30 thousand.”

Zhao Hai gave a short nod, indicating his understanding. Then he turned to Xiong Li and the others and said ,”Boss Xiong, be prepared. A large number of bugs are ahead. There are more bugs there than we faced before.”

As soon as XIong Li and the others heard Zhao Hai, their expressions turned serious. Then they nodded and couldn’t help but tighten their grip on their weapons.

Zhao Hai wasn’t holding back this time and directly took out 20 thousand Undead to drive back the wave of bugs. Before Zhao Hai and the others entered the third line of defense, the bugs and the Undead were already fighting.

When the group entered the third defensive line, the Undead and the bugs were already killing each other. Xiong Li and the other quickly joined in on the battle. Zhao Hai was still doing the job of a caretaker. Not only was he enhancing the fighting abilities of Xiong Li and the others, he was also making Megan and the others adjust their battle formations in order to get used to the battles of the World of Cultivation.

Chapter 1235: The Straightforward Lu Dingtian

The Undead were very important combat elements in Zhao Hai’s arsenal. Although they weren’t strong right now and were only equal to level 3, their cumulative strength makes up for it. This allowed the Undead to become very powerful in the battlefield.

However, they also have their own issues. Undead needed to be commanded. They could fight on their own, but the difference between having a commander and not was very clear. The ones commanding the Undead this time were Megan, Lizzy, and Margaret.

Laura and Meg don’t usually like to command the Undead, but Margaret actually took a liking to it.

On the other hand, Lizzy and Megan commanded the Undead since the lower realms. However, they found that the battles in the World of Cultivation were much more intense. No matter from which realm, their practitioners were much more formidable. Now, with the elimination round, Zhao Hai allowed them an opportunity to adapt to the rhythm of battles in the World of Cultivation.

Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t make a move against the bugs. In addition to overseeing Xiong Li and the others, Zhao Hai also left the Undead to the ladies.

Lizzy and the others were indeed improving. After several battles with the bugs, they had learned to adjust the Undead’s formation according to the changes in the battlefield. Seeing them adapt faster and faster, Zhao Hai was very satisfied.

What surprised Zhao Hai was Margaret’s interest in commanding Undead. He truly didn’t expect this to happen. Zhao Hai thought that Margaret was only interested in supporting formations. Who would’ve thought that Margaret was also interested in commanding the Undead.

Compared to the last battle, this one progressed slowly since there were a lot more bugs involved. But during the battle, Zhao Hai noticed that Sun Fei’s tactics were beginning to contain something special. In the past, Sun Fei acted like his attribute, hot-headed and straightforward like fire. His attacks were all quite fierce, which caused him to consume more energy than required.

However, his tactics were changing. He was no longer the same as before. Now, instead of pursuing the greatest attacking strength, he was now using efficient attacks.

Attacks with great strength completely differed from attacking with efficiency. It was just like people using a cannon to kill a mosquito. They could indeed kill the mosquito, but the power they used was too much. Although their attack was very powerful, it wasted a lot of energy if it only dealt with a single mosquito.

Using large-scale attacks reduced one’s lethality. Without Zhao Hai’s insane strength, even 100-layer formations wouldn’t be able to kill the bugs.

Sun Fei was using large-scale attacks in the past battle. But now, Sun Fei was using 10-layer formations and even 5-layer formations. His biggest attacks would never exceed 50-layers. But even so, he was now killing more bugs compared to before. Moreover, as he was staying behind XIong Li and the others, Sun Fei was beginning to pay great attention to Xiong Li and the others’ actions. Whenever a great danger appears near the Warriors, Sun Fei would make sure that it would be eliminated.

Naturally, since he wasn’t that strong yet, Sun Fei was unable to keep Xiong Li and the others completely safe. Nevertheless, he was heading in that direction.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but nod at Sun Fei’s learning capability. Sun Fei observed him last battle and was now starting to apply what he learned. Zhao Hai was very satisfied.

Mages were smart people. However, there were Mages that were very stubborn. Once they see a solution to a problem, they would immediately stick to it.

A Mage’s large-scale attack was indeed stronger than a weapon, but it heavily depended on the situation. If there were a lot of enemies, then this kind of attack would be very useful. This would greatly increase the speed in killing enemies.

But if a large-scale attack can’t cause a lot of damage to the enemy, then it was better to help your companions by clearing the dangers around them. This way, they could fight in relative safety.

Doing so wouldn’t only enhance Sun Fei’s ability, this would also increase the efficiency of the Warriors. After all, a Mage’s best weapon in battle wasn’t their magic, but instead their control over the situation. Knowing when to use spells was the most critical ability to have.

This point might seem simple, but it was rare for Mages to achieve this. Even Zhao Hai wouldn’t be able to achieve this if he didn’t have the Space’s help. In a fast battle, a simple mistake may develop into a fatal loss. If you cannot grasp the situation of the battle, then you would already be three points closer to a loss.

Grasping the changes of the enemy was also a type of control. It was impossible for a Mage to only use one kind of spell. And choosing a suitable spell for a specific situation wasn’t easy. Mages weren’t like Warriors who had a set of stances. If these stances were practiced to the extreme, then the Warrior would be able to use them at any time. However, a Mage’s magic arsenal wasn’t fixed. Even if one practices all spells, then they still couldn’t guarantee that they would be peerless in the battlefield.

When the enemy changes their actions and you weren’t able to grasp it, then your effectiveness would be reduced. Therefore, the most important thing for a Mage is control, control of the situation and the entire battlefield.

This ability of control couldn’t be gained by simple training. Only through grounded actual combat could one gain this ability.

Although Zhao Hai was satisfied with Sun Fei’s progress, Sun Fei was still beginning to train. Therefore, he still fell short in some areas. The one in full control of the situation was still Zhao Hai.

This fight ended up quicker compared to the last. First was because Zhao Hai released more Undead. And Second, because Lizzy and the others were beginning to adapt themselves to fighting the bugs and were now more able to coordinate themselves.

When Xiong Li and the others felt that they were about to run out of energy, their battle had abruptly ended. They weren’t able to foresee this, so as they killed bugs, they suddenly found out that there were no bugs to kill. They were stunned for a moment before they recovered when they saw that the Undead were already cleaning the battlefield.

When Xiong Li found out about this, he turned his head to Zhao Hai and gave a dissatisfied glare as he said, “Little Hai, can’t you make your Undead slow down? I haven’t killed enough bugs yet, and now they’re all gone.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Boss Xiong, you’re too complacent. You already look like you’re going to die, but you still want to fight. But if you really have some energy left, you can head further in. There’s a bug nest ahead with tens of thousands of bugs left to kill. Moreover, since its the interior of the nest, those bugs would be more frantic. I’m sure you can fight properly there.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Xiong Li waved his hand and said, “Forget it. I’m not that greedy. Let’s just use the extra time to relax.”

Dongfang Yu laughed and said, “Boss Xiong, you should go. Not only can I assure you that you can fight properly, you would also end up being bug poop. Hahaha. “ Li Kuangren and the others laughed as well. Xiong Li didn’t care and just laughed alongside them. They were brothers for life and death, these kinds of jokes were harmless for them.

While the Undead were cleaning the battlefield, Zhao Hai led the group back to a clean cave nearby. After they settled themselves down, Zhao Hai took out some dishes and said, “Let’s take a rest here and wait until we fully recover. I estimate there to be about 60 thousand bugs in the bug nest. Since we’re in the nest, those bugs would certainly go all out. Even if there are 10 thousand more bugs, we’re still going to be fine. So we can relax here with no worries.”

The group nodded. Since they trusted Zhao Hai, they didn’t doubt his words. They took Zhao Hai’s words as is.

Everyone took out their own bottle of wine and then opened it as they said, “Drink!” Then they all took a sip. Zhao Hai took out his finest liquor at this time. It’s flavor was very pure, the taste was neat, and drinking it was satisfying.

After putting his bottle down, Zhao Hai looked at Lu Dingtian and said, “Old Lu, we brothers are going to establish our own base when we go back to the Machine Field. We’ll be going on our own. Although we would still perform tasks, we would act independently. Are you interested in going with us?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Lu Dingtian’s eyes shone. Then he nodded and said, “Alright.”

Zhao Hai didn’t expect Lu Dingtian’s answer. Most people from external halls wouldn’t prefer working alone. Although being independent seems like the smart move, this also meant that you would lose the family’s support. This was the same as leaving the family. Since you can no longer benefit the family, then there’s no reason to support you. There would no longer be potions, weapons, armor, and other things. You would now need money in order to purchase them. These weren’t easy things to aquire, one would need to complete multiple tasks in order to afford them.

But undergoing too many tasks would hamper one’s cultivation. Therefore, not a lot of people would choose to leave. Although there was no freedom in the family, everyone knew about the saying ‘leaning on a tree to enjoy the breeze’. Leaving the family meant leaving the tree and undertaking the difficulties outside this zone of comfort. Not everyone would have the courage to do this. However, Lu Dingtian didn’t even hesitate. This truly was out of Zhao Hai’s expectations.

Chapter 1236: Attacking The Main Bug Nest

Not only Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others were also surprised. They looked at Lu Dingtian in puzzlement. They had known Zhao Hai for a long time, even long before the elimination round. On the other hand, Lu Dingtian had just recently joined their group. Agreeing to Zhao Hai’s proposal that easily caused the others to feel that it was strange.

Xiong Li was a person who wouldn’t withhold words, so he looked at Lu Dingtian and asked, “Old Lu, why did you accept Little Hai’s proposal that easily?”

Li Dingtian gave a succinct answer, “I believe him.” He always talked simply, as if saying one more word would cause him to waste a lot of energy.

However, when the others heard Lu Dingtian’s words, their eyes couldn’t help but brighten, then they all laughed. They raised the bottles and then took a huge drink.

After placing his bottle down, Zhao Hai looked at Xiong Li and the others and said, “Brothers, it has been some time since we’ve known each other. We’re also used to each other’s temperament. And since we’re going together after the competition, I was thinking that we might as well become sworn brothers with different surnames.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others stared, then their expressions lit up. Xiong Li loudly agreed “Alright, then it’s settled. What do you all think?”

“I agree!” “I agree!” “I agree!” “I agree!”

Seeing that everyone agrees, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh, then he said, “Alright, then there’s no need to wait. Let’s do it right now.” He waved his hand and an additional table appeared in the cave. Zhao Hai waved once more,  causing three bug legs to appear.

Zhao Hai looked at Xiong Li and the others and said, “Although I always bring food and drinks, I don’t have the habit of bringing incense. Brothers, let’s use these bug legs as incense. Is it fine if we use it to swear our brotherhood?”

Xiong Li laughed and said, “Of course its fine. The important thing is our conviction. Even if we use soil and leaves, we can still swear on our brotherhood. Let’s do it.”

Everyone knelt down before loudly expressing their oath, “With heaven as the witness, we brothers are willing to swear on each other. We shall be brothers of different surnames. We shall share sorrows and joys. We might not be born on the same day and year, but we swear to die together. With the heavens as the witness, we swear!”

After saying the oath, everyone kowtowed towards the table and then stood up. Everyone proceeded to assign names to each other. Xiong Li would be known as First Brother. Lu Dingtian will be Second Brother, Dongfang Yu will be Third Brother, Li Kuangren will be Fourth Brother, Zhao Hai will be Fifth Brother, and Sun Fei will be Sixth Brother.

Becoming sworn brothers made their relationship a layer closer. Zhao Hai received the table and then everyone ate and drank heavily. It was as if they weren’t inside a dangerous cave system.

However, Zhao Hai and the others were modest people.. After drinking two bottles of liquor, they began to eat and chat for a while. Then they proceeded to take a rest. They had undergone two battles in a day, so Xiong Li and the others were very tired. When they lied down, they immediately snored loudly.

The reason why Xiong Li and the others dared to sleep like this was because they believed that Zhao Hai would take care of everything. Additionally, there were Undead guarding outside. This made them assured that they can sleep.

Zhao Hai also closed his eyes. He wasn’t worried at all. The eight-legged bugs and the bug nest were under the Space’s surveillance. It was impossible for them to be caught off-guard.

The eight-legged bug nest seemed to feel that it was in danger. The queen nest was desperately laying eggs. More and more eight-legged bugs were born. And just like Zhao Hai said, ten thousand bugs were born in one day. However, this would also damage the vitality of the nest. At this point, the queen could no longer give birth to so many bugs.

Zhao Hai and the others slept for about six hours. When they got up, they ate once more and then took a short break. At this time, Xiong Li said, “Little Hai, what do we do now? Are we going to attack the bug nest that you talked about?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Of course we will. After we deal with this bug nest, we can proceed to explore other areas. But at that time, we won’t be hunting bugs, but people from the other realms.”

When Xiong Li and the others heard this, they quickly knew what Zhao Hai wanted to do. Once they deal with the bug nest, then it’s time to plunder other realms for their cultivation methods, especially the Cultivation Realm. They couldn’t help but laugh loudly, as though the upcoming battles weren’t a big deal.

Of course they weren’t worried, Zhao Hai’s Undead were too powerful. Moreover, the nest they would be attacking wasn’t an advanced level nest. As long as Zhao Hai was willing, then he wouldn’t need any help in dealing with the bugs. Therefore, Xiong Li and the others had nothing to worry about.

Zhao Hai also doesn’t need to consider a lot of things in this attack. After two battles, Xiong Li and the others were able to adapt to their weapons. They wouldn’t need to participate in the following battles.

When the time to attack the nest was close, Zhao Hai looked at Xiong Li and said, “Boss Xiong, are you still interested in fighting? If you’re not, then I’ll just clean them all up.”

Xiong Li shook his head and said, “It’s fine, we won’t participate. In any case, I have already adapted to my new weapon. Also, fighting bugs is very boring, it’s a waste of time. Right, Little Hai, when we have free time, you should refine Second Brother Lu’s dagger-axe.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “After dealing with the nest, we’ll take a day off so that I can refine his weapon.”

Then after he said that, Zhao Hai waved his hand, releasing Undead to attack the nest. Xiong Li and the others were no longer surprised with the number of Zhao Hai’s Undead. They were also no longer interested to find out the exact amount of Undead. They were afraid that they would be depressed when they do.

Zhao Hai wasn’t polite and directly released 100 thousand Undead to attack the eight-legged bugs. These Undead were added to the Undead already summoned before. This large number of Undead advanced towards the bug nest. He wanted to settle this matter as soon as possible.

However, just as the battle began, Zhao Hai was stunned. This wasn’t because the eight-legged bugs had gotten stronger. These bugs were still insignificant in his eyes. What surprised him was the nest of the eight-legged bugs.

The nest of the eight-legged bugs was a giant organic ball about 20 meters in diameter. This ball had two tubes extending below. These two tubes were arranged so that it would excrete masses that would slowly form into eight-legged bugs after several minutes. These two tubes that usually pointed to the ground were now raised. When the bugs and the Undead began to clash, these tubes suddenly fired two clumps of meat moistened by some mucus.

When these two clumps of meat hit the Undead army, they suddenly exploded. The power of the explosion wasn’t weak. Each explosion killed nearly a hundred Undead.

Seeing this happen, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. The bug nest had just developed defensive turrets. These turrets needed to be removed first, otherwise they would make dealing with the bugs very difficult.

When Xiong Li and the others saw Zhao Hai’s expression change, they knew that something must have happened. Xiong Li immediately asked, “Little Hai, did something happen? Did anybody else arrive?” They were no longer afraid of the bugs. What they were afraid of were people from other realms. Therefore, Xiong Li asked this question.

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “No, I just encountered something tricky with the nest. I’ll take care of it. Don’t follow me, the situation is quite dangerous.” Then Zhao Hai’s figure moved as he entered the cave and then disappeared.

Xiong Li looked at Zhao Hai’s departing back, his expression was ugly as he said, “Shit, I just swore that we would share sorrows. But now when things turn difficult, I can’t do anything. I really hate that I’m weak.”

Dongfang Yu forced a smile and said, “Come on, Boss XIong, this makes me even more embarrassed. I’m now a Cultivator, but I still can’t do anything. Let’s just wait for Little Hai here, I’m sure he can take care of it. When this competition is over, we can work hard so that we can help Little Hai. Otherwise, this would really leave a bad taste in our mouths.”

The others bitterly nodded, nobody said anything else. After swearing on their brotherhood, they were now of the same family. In this case, they can only watch Zhao Hai’s battle. Weirdly enough, this thought made them feel better.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t take in mind what Xiong Li and the others were thinking right now. The metal bombs that the bug nest fired were really powerful. If Xiong Li and the others came, and a bomb finds its way to them, then they won’t have any strength to block it.

To be honest, Zhao Hai didn’t expect the bug nest to have this kind of offensive ability.

Upon appearing in the bug nest, Zhao Hai ignored the eight-legged bugs and immediately flew towards the nest itself. Upon discovering Zhao Hai, the nest immediately readjusted the two tubes and aimed towards him. Then it fired several balls of meat one after another.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and released a 50-layer formation. Several fire dragons emerged and then met the balls of explosive meat.

After several loud explosions, no bombs were able to reach Zhao Hai. Each bomb was detonated by the fire dragons. Zhao Hai used this time to appear above the organic mass that is the core of the nest.

The organic mass probably felt danger as it immediately aimed its tubes to Zhao Hai once more. Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he waved his hand, causing a spatial rift to appear. Then the rift moved downwards, swallowing the organic mass as well as the eight-legged bugs nearby.

Zhao Hai discovered that the eight-legged bug’s queen nest cannot move at all. In addition to birthing eight-legged bugs, its only action was launching those meat bombs. Neither of these methods were able to protect itself from Zhao Hai.

Once the queen nest was taken away by Zhao Hai, the eight-legged bugs lost their final support. However, the bugs continued fighting, but this time there was no longer any threat towards the Undead.

Zhao Hai relaxed and then shifted his attention towards the bug queen nest inside the Space. At this time, the nest was still inside the Space’s storage. With an intention, Zhao Hai caused the nest to appear inside an empty background.

As soon as the queen nest appeared,  a prompt was heard, “Low-level bug queen nest detected. This nest can only produce low-level bugs. It can absorb a small amount of gene material to improve bug’s combat power. However, this improvement is very limited and will still result in low combat power. It is recommended that the host transforms this nest into a meat bug farm. Once the transformation is done, meat bugs will be produced. These bugs have low combat power but they have delicious meat. Will the host transform the nest?”

When he saw the result, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but bitterly smile. He didn’t expect the Space to suggest something like this. Not to mention this suggestion was actually good.

Presently, there were a lot of demand for meat in the Space. Since the reproductive ability of this nest was very good, if he can produce shrimp and crabs from it, then it would definitely be a good choice.

In any case, the nest was low-level and the fighting strength it possesses wasn’t very strong. Moreover, the Space has no need for eight-legged bugs right now. It was much better if it was transformed into a meat farm.

With this thought in mind, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Transform it.” The Space’s prompt was heard, “Host has agreed to transform the nest to a meat bug farm. Transformation will immediately begin. Asking the Host to wait for a moment.”

A beep sounded before white light surrounded the queen nest. After a while, the white light disappeared. The nest reappeared on the ground. When Zhao Hai saw the nest, he couldn’t help but gawk at it. It looked much better and much larger than its previous form. It was now a huge ball about 50 meters in diameter. What surprised him the most was the exterior of the ball. It no longer looked like it was made with organic matter. Instead, the ball had a carapace that flashed with metallic light. It now looked like a huge metal ball.

Below this metal ball were eight tubes. The diameter of these tubes was about a meter. The color and texture of these tubes were the same as the metal ball.

But Zhao Hai knew that even if the ball looked like it was made of metal, it wasn’t metallic in nature-just a resemblance. As Zhao Hai looked at the metal ball, he said, “Cai’er.”

Cai’er whizzed beside Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, what’s the matter?”

Zhao Hai gestured towards the nest and said, “Take a look. This thing is supposed to produce meat bugs. Find out what it needs and also find a way to control the amount of bugs produced. But first, let’s produce a batch and have a taste. It would be useless if it tastes bad.”

Chapter 1237: Sentiment In A Ruthless World Is Stronger

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master, rest assured. Information about this thing is now in my head. It’s nothing more than a machine. It’s like a Universal Processing Machine but instead produces a specific kind of meat. It can be fed with both plants and animals and we can control how much it produces. It needs spiritual qi to function, but it isn’t a problem since the Space is rich with spiritual qi.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Can you produce a batch right now? Don’t make it look disgusting, we don’t like people losing their appetite when they see it.”

Cai’er smiled faintly and said, “Young Master, rest assured. That wouldn’t be a problem, the Space has already considered this issue.” Then after she said that, a meter high egg tumbled out of a tube. The egg rolled to the ground and after a few seconds, the eggshell broke. Then what came out made Zhao Hai stare. He didn’t expect the Space to make the bugs into this form. It’s clearly a crab.

Right, a giant crab hatched out of the egg. When he saw the crab, Zhao Hai chuckled and said, “Alright, it turned out to be a crab. No wonder the Space said that it tastes like crab-meat. That’s good, let’s produce them. Also, how is their fighting strength?”

Cai’er nodded and then said, “They can fight back, but they’re not very strong. They are far weaker than the eight-legged bugs. After all, they’re intended for consumption.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “But if I still want the eight-legged bugs for battle, can I get them?”

Cai’er gave a nod and said, “That bug has been saved in the Space’s shop as well as the eight-legged bug nest. If Young Master wants to use them, you can buy them at any time.”

Zhao Hai replied, “That’s good. Alright, pay attention to how much meat this crab has. And then promote it in the various backgrounds in the Space. In any case, this thing doesn’t need much to be fed. And people also need more variety in their food.”

Cai’er nodded, “Young Master, rest assured. I’ll take care of it.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll trust you with this.” Then he disappeared out from the Space and then got back to the cave.

The battle with the bug nest was basically over. The eight-legged bugs had lost their commander. With the Undead as their opponent, it wouldn’t be long before they would be killed off.

Zhao Hai went out of the battlefield and back to the anxiously waiting Xiong Li and the others.

Seeing Zhao Hai coming back, they immediately relaxed. Xiong Li quickly asked, “Little Hai, how is it?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s basically finished. There’s just a small problem with the nest. But I already dealt with it, there won’t be any more problems.”

Xiong Li and the others relaxed. Then Zhao Hai led them to enter the nest. At this time, eight-legged bug corpses were in piles. Besides the Undead who were cleaning up the remaining bugs, the others Undead began to clean up the battlefield.

Zhao Hai looked around him and said, “Alright, let’s find a clean place to sit down. At the same time, I’ll be refining Second Brother’s dagger-axe.”

Xiong Li and the others nodded. Although they didn’t mind the bug corpses, the sight of them would still make food taste worse. It was much better if they went to a cleaner place.

Fortunately, the bug nest was full of caves. Zhao Hai found a random cave and then went there. Zhao Hai cleaned the place up a bit with magic before everyone sat down. Then Zhao Hai looked at Lu Dingtian and said, “Second Brother, let me have a look at your dagger-axe.”

Lu Dingtian nodded and then took out his dagger-axe and gave it to Zhao Hai. When he was handed the dagger-axe, Zhao Hai found out that it was quite heavy. It was even heavier than Xiong Li’s two hammers.

Moreover, it seems like Lu Dingtian’s weapon was very old. Strictly speaking, this weapon should be a double-ended spear. The head would be the spearhead while the other would be a two-ended dagger-axe. The entire weapon was very long. Its entire body was azure in color, with a bit of copper tint. However, Zhao Hai knew that it was impossible for this weapon to be made out of copper. The material of this weapon should be on par with Xiong Li’s hammers.

Zhao Hai gave a nod and said, “Give me some time. I’ll make sure that the weapon pleases Second Brother. Wait here for me.” Then as soon as he said that, he disappeared.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s vanish, Xiong Li sighed and said, “No wonder we can’t sense anything in his room whenever Little Hai goes into seclusion. It turns out he wasn’t in his room at all.”

Dongfang Yu nods and said, “It seems like this is also the reason why Little Hai is very familiar with the Machine Field’s situation back in Base Number 5. It’s possible that he went back to the Machine Field when he closed up. I reckon it’s Margaret who told Zhao Hai what happened.”

Xiong Li and the other agreed to what Dongfang Yu said. On the other hand, Lu Dingtian didn’t know until now that Zhao Hai can use Space Magic – but he still kept silent. During this period, Zhao Hai had taken great care of him and even allowed him to become sworn brothers with the others. Naturally, he wouldn’t cause Zhao Hai any harm.

It was said that the World of Cultivation was ruthless, everyone was scampering for benefits and cultivation methods, acting like savage beasts. If one doesn’t have any good friends, then they would suffer in this world. And if one relaxed, then they would be destroyed by others sooner or later.

Therefore, if one wanted to reach great places in the World of Cultivation, then one would need dedicated friends. Moreover, because of how ruthless the World of Cultivation was, friendships were more precious. If you become friends with someone and then you betray them, then your reputation would forever be tainted. Nobody would work with you in the future anymore, let alone becoming friends. Therefore, in the World of Cultivation, friendships were seen as a sacred covenant between people.

This turned out to become a strange scene, causing balance in the World of Cultivation. Ruthless people would die out because they were isolated in this ruthless world.

In the World of Cultivation, one would need to be ruthless but also become someone who regarded sentiment heavily. During tumultuous times, love between people was rarely discussed, but at the same time, this love would be thicker. The World of Cultivation was the same. Sentiment wasn’t easily discussed in this world, but the regard for sentiment here was much stronger than any liquor there was!

Xiong Li and the others weren’t fools. They understand clearly what the Machine Field’s natives see ascenders as. They knew that the only way for Ascenders like them to survive in this world was to band together!

Zhao Hai wasn’t aware of what Xiong Li and the others were thinking. In fact, Zhao Hai didn’t think so much when he became friends with Xiong Li and the others. He thought that he had great compatibility with them when it came to temperament. Therefore, he decided to befriend them. Also, Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid of Xiong Li and the others betraying him. He has the Space, so he could never be in grave danger. Therefore, he was very assured when becoming brothers with Xiong Li and the others.

When Zhao Hai returned to the Space, he immediately went to the processing machine and deconstructed Lu Dingtian’s weapon. At the same time, using the vast collection of minerals that the Space has as well as the Universal Scanner, a long dagger-axe with 80 engraved formations was produced in not even half an hour.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t head out immediately. Instead he returned to the villa to chat with Laura and the others. But when he arrived, he saw a massive crab on the ground, menacingly pinching its pincers.

Zhao Hai stared and immediately knew that this was the crab that the nest produced. How did this crab get here? Zhao Hai looked at Laura and the others in confusion and said, “How did this get here? Are you going to eat it?”

Meg nodded and said, “Young Master, we want to see how this thing tastes. We have eaten crabs before, but we haven’t eaten one as large as this.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, let’s taste it. Right, Cai’er, prepare two of them for me. I’ll bring them out for Xiong Li and the others to taste.”

Cai’er nodded. Getting a couple of crabs wasn’t an issue. In fact, the Space has already started to produce crabs. There were several hundred crabs in the Space, two crabs were very small in comparison. She could even take out 200 carbs with no problem.

After getting Zhao Hai’s approval, Meg immediately moved. She cast magic and froze the crab. Then she waved her hand and said, “Cai’er, help me get this thing to the kitchen. We’ll be eating crab today.” Cai’er nodded and then waved her hand as the crab floated. Then she followed Meg to the kitchen.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then turned his head to Laura and said, “How are you all doing?”

Laura smiled and said, “It’s quite tiring. But I think Lizzy and the others are more tired. Brother Hai, the weapons that the Undead use are too low-level. How about we make them more powerful ones? How about engraving them with magic formations? With this, the Undead would be stronger.”

Zhao Hai thought about it and then nodded and said, “Both the bone armors and the combat suits are already good for defense. But their weapons are indeed lacking, causing them to be on the defensive most of the time. We should replace their weapons. You can discuss this with Cai’er.”

Laura nodded. Then at this time Berry said, “Brother Hai, we discovered a good place for a base. Do you want to take a look?”

Chapter 1238: Floating Island

When Zhao Hai heard Berry, he couldn’t help but stare for a moment. Then his expression lit up as he said, “You did? Where is it?”

Berry didn’t say anything as she just smiled faintly and then waved her hand.  A large screen appeared and showed the place. Zhao hai was stunned, it was a beautiful place, beautiful beyond imagination.

It was a small island-looking place. However, this island was floating in the air with a pointed cone shape in the bottom. The entire island was about a thousand kilometers across, it wasn’t very large. It’s environment was also very strange. On one side of the island was a mountain range. The mountain range wasn’t tall, only a few hundred meters high. The mountain range was divided into five peaks. There’s also a river flowing down the mountain range. The volume of water from the river wasn’t much – with the river only 10 meters across. It’s depth wasn’t visible, but its flow wasn’t fast and looked very gentle. This river flowed down the mountains and into a forest. There were all kinds of trees in the forest, but they weren’t tall as well, with the tallest trees barely reaching 20 meters high. The entire mountain looked rich and beautiful.

A plain was under the mountains. It was covered with green grass as well as small shrubberies. It looked like an ordinary grassland.

But what’s strange about this island was its lack of fauna. Besides the plants, there were no other living creatures on the island.

At the same time, the island’s sky wasn’t blue, instead it was bright yellow in color. It wasn’t bright but it also wasn’t dark. There were also several clouds fluttering by the island, adding to its beauty.

Zhao Hai’s eyes were shining as he looked at the island. Then he asked, “Where is this place? So beautiful. But is it safe?”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “Take a guess. It’s an absolutely safe region.”

Zhao Hai stared, then after seeing the cunning smiles on everyone’s face, he immediately had a hunch. So he asked, “It’s in the Quicksand Starfield is it?”

Laura and the others laughed. Then Laura smiled and said, “Brother Hai guessed right. It might seem unbelievable, but do you believe it now? This place is truly in the Quicksand Starfied, moreover it’s at the very center of the huge desert.”

Zhao Hai looked at the floating island on the screen, then he muttered, “This universe is truly vast. Such a place even exists. This place is beautiful. It’s a good place to make a base.”

Laura smiled and said, “That’s why we thought that it would be a good location for a base.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “This is the place. Let’s go and see it.” Then he waved his hand, causing everyone to appear on the island.

As soon as he stepped on the island, Zhao Hai became stunned. The spiritual qi in the island turns out to be adequate. Although it was worse than the Space, it was still stronger than in the Machine Field. It can even be compared to cities in the Cultivation Realm.

Since the spiritual qi was thick, the natural air was also very good. A light breeze caresses you, making the island very comfortable to be in. If an average person came here, then they would definitely be attracted by the beautiful colors of the scenery. However, to Zhao Hai, everything was just average.

After taking a look at the surroundings, Zhao Hai knew that it was impossible for any ores to grow here. Meanwhile, the sky shouldn’t be yellow by itself. What caused it to turn yellow should be the radiance of the desert that surrounded it. However, Zhao Hai couldn’t believe an island like this to exist in the Quicksand Starfield. Just as Laura said, this place was truly safe.

The endless desert of the starfield existed for a very long time. And during that time, even almighty Cultivators didn’t dare enter this place. If this place was unsafe, then nothing in the World of Cultivation was safe.

Zhao Hai believed that if strong Cultivators discovered this place, they would immediately move here. It was because this place was not only secure, it was also well hidden. This was the best place to close up.

Powerful practitioners would still close up from time to time. It was during this time where they tried to comprehend their Cultivation. Powerful beings closing up was a fairly common matter in the World of Cultivation.

However, they would need to find a safe and secret place to close up. There weren’t only one or two powerful beings who were slain during their seclusion.

Zhao Hai was sure that nobody had found out about this place before. This was because there were no traces of people here. It was a completely pure environment.

But it was clear that the vitality of this place was lacking. Although there were plants everywhere, the lack of animals was an issue.

Zhao Hai didn’t mind it as he turned to Laura and the others and said, “You have worked hard. I didn’t expect you to find a place like this. However, I have another favor to ask you. We need a small settlement built here with all the facilities needed. I’ll leave the design to you. What do you think?”

Laura smiled and said, “That’s not a problem. Leave it to us.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Besides building here, continue looking for places for a base. We shouldn’t put all of our eggs in one basket. Find a place close to the Ashley Family. This way, if the Machine Field suffers an accident, we would be able to provide help to the Ashley Family.”

Laura turned her head to Margaret and then nodded as she said, “Rest assured. This is related to Sister Margaret, so we’ll pay extra attention to it.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said ,”Alright, let’s leave. The scenery here isn’t as good as the Space. By the way, if you have time, put some fish and animals here. Make this place more alive.”

Laura smiled and said, “Don’t worry about it. Leave it to us. Let’s head back. Sister Meg should be done with the crabs.” Zhao Hai smiled and then waved his hand, returning everyone to the Space.

When they went back to the Space, everyone took a deep breath, especially Laura and the others. They were already used to being inside the Space. So when they headed out, they weren’t used to the taste of the air.

Just as everyone returned to the Space, Meg walked out from the kitchen and said, “Young Master, the meal is done.” Zhao Hai and the others nodded. Then they went to the dining room together with Meg.

Upon arriving at the dining room, Laura and the others couldn’t help but be wowed. Nothing else was placed on the table other than the giant crab. This huge crab almost occupied the entire table. It looked impressive on top of the dining table.

When Zhao Hai saw this, he laughed and said, “Alright, let’s eat. My mouth is already watering.” Then his hand moved as Liquid Silver appeared. Then he divided the crab and took out the crab meat inside and placed it on the tray. Laura and the others immediately took knives and forks to eat.

Zhao Hai also took some meat and put it in his mouth. A fresh taste immediately went through his taste buds and then to his head before spreading to his entire body. The flavor made his hair stand up, it was too tasty.

The giant crab was consumed by everyone in no time. Looking at the empty crab shell on the table, Zhao Hai sighed and said, “It’s very delicious. I’m thinking about opening a shop after the competition. Then we can serve this crab and get rich off of it.”

Laura’s eyes shone and she said, “That’s a good idea. But Brother Hai, you need to give us an identity. Then we can manage the shop.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Alright. Then I’ll get you a legitimate status once the competition ends. Don’t worry about it.” Zhao Hai also knew that Laura and the others had stayed inside the Space for too long. It’s time for them to head out and play.

The group rested in the Villa for some time before heading to sleep. It was impossible for Zhao Hai to head out this quickly, so he also spent his night inside the Space.

After Zhao Hai woke up, he calculated that it was time to head out. So he took Lu Dingtian’s dagger-axe and then appeared back inside the cave. Xiong Li and the others were currently practicing. They haven’t participated in the last fight, so there’s no need for them to rest. Instead, they used the time to practice.

When they felt that Zhao Hai had come back, everyone opened their eyes at the same time. Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he handed the dagger-axe to Lu Dingtian and said, “Second Brother, try this out. See if it suits you.’

Lu Dingtian nodded and accepted his weapon. After weighing the weapon in his hand, he quickly moved and tried a few moves inside the nest cave. The dagger-axe came to life in Lu Dingtian’s hands. Lu Dingtian’s actions seem to cut wind and rain. Most importantly, Lu Dingtian’s dagger-axe was emitting extremely strong killing aura. Each wave was akin to a terrifying general rampaging through the battlefield.

Lu Dingtian’s actions caused Xiong Li to nod. Then he said, “Old Lu’s dagger-axe technique is very powerful. I’m afraid I wouldn’t be able to defeat him anymore. His technique isn’t complex, instead it is very simple. It matches well with his strong temperament. No wonder he gained the nickname ‘Army Breaker’. He alone could face thousands of soldiers.”

Dongfang Yu nodded and said, “Dagger-axes are also rare weapons. Using a dagger-axe to a degree like Second Brother is very difficult. Second Brother is truly a genius.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly. He didn’t say anything and just waited for Lu Dingtian. After some time, when Lu Dingtian became familiar with his new weapon, he stopped. Then he looked at ZHao Hai and said, “Little Hai, thank you.”

Zhao Hai chuckled as he patted Lu Dingtian’s shoulder and said, “We’re brothers, so save those formalities. Everyone, come and take your pile of bugs. I have something for us to eat.” Nobody held back and took a pile for themselves. Then they returned to the cave they were in before.

After that, Zhao Hai took out the big crabs for everyone to eat. And then everyone took off towards other caves.

Chapter 1239: A Group of Five Cultivators

Zhao Hai’s face was calm as he flew forward – he wasn’t worried at all. In any case, it has only been two days since they entered the caves and there were still several days left. He had also found a target to attack, so he wasn’t anxious.

As they were flying forward, Li Kuangren licked his mouth as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, I want to eat crabs for the next meal. Get me two of them.”

Zhao Hai loudly laughed and said, “Alright, I’ll get two for you. I’ve been thinking about opening a shop once the competition ends. When we find a base, we’ll raise these crabs and then sell them. What do you think?” Xiong Li laughed and said, “Let’s find a base first. That’s the most important.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and didn’t say anything. He couldn’t tell Xiong Li and the others that he had already found a base. This would only welcome a pile of unwanted questions.

Zhao Hai continued to lead Xiong Li and the others forward. They were currently going from cave to cave. Before long, XIong Li and the others became confused as to which was north, east, west, and south – so they just kept on following Zhao Hai. As for where Zhao Hai was bringing them, only Zhao Hai knew. They were also disinclined to ask.

Actually, the party of Cultivators that Zhao Hai wanted to attack was very close. However, the quickest path to them was filled with bug nests. Zhao Hai didn’t want to waste time on fighting bugs, so he chose to circle around and take the safe route. Moreover, if they fought bugs, they would only alert the Cultivators.

Zhao Hai didn’t know which sect these Cultivators belonged to. There were five of them in total. The clothes they wore were different from each other. Zhao Hai chose these five people because their cultivation methods were suitable for his brothers.

Among these five people, two of them were using earth-element cultivation methods, one used a wood element method, and the last two were metal-element cultivators. The earth-element Cultivators defended, the metal-element cultivators attacked, while the wood-element cultivator was in charge of treating wounds and restoring stamina.

This doesn’t mean that the earth-element cultivators couldn’t attack and metal-element cultivators couldn’t defend. Whichever Cultivation method they use, since they were from the Cultivation realm, their fighting prowess was strong. The arrangement was like this because this was the most suitable for their composition.

The grouping of these five could be said to be very good, they even have someone to heal them and aid in recovery. This was also the reason why Zhao Hai targeted them. At the same time, he lacked the cultivation methods from these three attributes.

Zhao Hai currently had two cultivation methods in his hand. The first was Dongfang Yu’s fire-element cultivation method, Divine Fire Dragon Art. The other was Li Chuchen’s water-element cultivation method. Zhao Hai still had no idea what this cultivation method was since he didn’t have the time to ask Li Chuchen about it. But seeing how Li Chuchen fought, Zhao Hai knew that it must have been a highly ranked cultivation method. But since none of his brothers had the water attribute, Zhao Hai wasn’t anxious about getting the cultivation method.

Xiong Li and Li Kuangren were earth attributes, so it was best for them to cultivate an earth-element cultivation method. Lu Dingtian was a metal attribute, so he would need a metal-element cultivation method. As for the wood-element cultivation method, even if it was useless to Zhao Hai, he still wanted to get ahold of it.

Zhao Hai discovered that his Yin-Yang Stellar Transformations Art was an extremely powerful cultivation method. However, this art only has the tempering technique for offense. This kind of attack looked very ordinary. Zhao Hai also wanted to use a flying sword but he would need an extremely powerful technique to match his cultivation method. Therefore, Zhao Hai was planning to get techniques from multiple elements and see if there were aspects that he could copy from them. This way, he can make a useful flying sword technique for himself.

Since Zhao Hai had all attributes, he had the idea of getting multiple flying sword manuals and creating his own flying sword technique.

This might be impossible for other people, but to Zhao Hai, it won’t be much of an issue. This was because he has the scanner. As long as he gets flying sword manuals from five elements, then he can scan them. Zhao Hai believed that with the recent upgrade to the scanner, this matter wouldn’t be very hard to do.

Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to target those five people. As long as he kills those 5, he would be able to obtain their techniques for study. At the same time, this would also be a great help for Xiong Li and the others.

Although there were other people in other caves, they were far from Zhao Hai and the others. If Zhao Hai wanted to deal with them, then he would have to walk farther. Most importantly, these five people had the elements that Zhao Hai needs. If he dealt with people separately, then Zhao Hai would need more time. And Zhao Hai was afraid that he would run out of time.

This time limit wasn’t brought by the end of the elimination round, but something else instead. Laura and the others found out that the bugs were starting a large-scale tide. If the bugs truly start their bug tide, then Zhao Hai and the others would certainly be plunged into battle. When the time comes, he wouldn’t be able to find time to deal with other people. Therefore, Zhao Hai decided to make this party of 5 his target.

These five were from the Cultivation Realm. Moreover, they were quite strong. If these five acted, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t be able to deal with them easily. One must know that the Cultivators had a lot of trump cards. Zhao Hai managed to deal with Li Chuchen because Li Chuchen didn’t take him seriously at first, and was then frightened by Zhao Hai’s strength. At that time, Li Chuchen could only use 80% of his strength at most. Otherwise, Zhao Hai would have had a hard time killing Li Chuchen.

Although the five people that Zhao Hai was targeting weren’t from the same sect, the cooperation between them was quite solid. Zhao Hai saw them easily deal with thousands of bugs, and their cooperation played a vital role in this achievement. Therefore, it wouldn’t be easy for Zhao Hai to deal with them.

And even if Xiong Li and the others were now stronger, they still fall short compared to these five Cultivators. Only Dongfang Yu might be able to stand on his own against them. However, Dongfang Yu was just one person. It would be impossible for him to have a great impact in the battle. In the end, Zhao Hai can only rely on himself.

Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid of those five people, what he was afraid of was the fight taking too long and alerting others from the Cultivation Realm. If other Cultivators see their fight, then it’s highly probable that they would join in.

If it was any other place, the other Cultivators wouldn’t join in if Zhao Hai and the five Cultivators fought. Even if they saw it, they still wouldn’t act. Life and death was common in the Cultivation Realm, so nobody would butt in if someone unrelated to them were to die.

However, this was the elimination round. The top 100 rookies from the six realms compete with each other. If the other Cultivators saw Zhao Hai, then they would immediately attack him, removing the biggest enemy first. Although Zhao Hai has the power to protect himself, he couldn’t allow those people to escape. If they left and told others, then Zhao Hai and the others would be under pursuit from the people in the Cultivation Realm.

Zhao Hai was afraid of attracting the attention of these other Cultivators. But this fear didn’t stem in the fact that they might fight, but instead when they would run away. He didn’t want his strength known since this would give him trouble in the formal matches.

Zhao Hai continued flying forward as he chatted with Xiong Li and the others. However, he would occasionally talk to Laura and the others with his mind regarding the five Cultivators.

The five-man team were currently fighting a group of bugs. The bugs weren’t numerous, only about 1000. However, these bugs weren’t the eight-legged bugs that Zhao Hai and the others faced. Instead, these were the flying mantis bugs that would take heads off.

In addition to their ability to fly, these bugs were offensively strong as well as agile. Because of this, the five were unable to kill them all at once.

Zhao Hai and the others inched closer and closer to the five Cultivators. At the same time, they were making sure to avoid any bugs. This allowed them to have a smooth travel with no bugs interrupting.

After flying for about eight hours, Zhao Hai and the others were already close to the five Cultivators. Although Zhao Hai didn’t feel anything, Xiong Li and the others could still get tired. As they were heading here, they took two breaks and ate one meal.

When they were already near the battlefield, Zhao Hai stopped. Seeing Zhao Hai stop, Xiong Li and the others stopped as well. Everyone looked at Zhao Hai, then Xiong Li whispered, “Little Hai? Did we reach our destination?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Not far away in front is our target. However, they’re currently fighting bugs. Let’s wait for them to finish.”

Xiong Li and the others nodded. They didn’t ask Zhao Hai about what’s ahead or anything. There was no need for such questions, they completely trusted him.

The group entered a cave as Zhao Hai took out some food to eat. While they were eating, Zhao Hai was paying attention to the state of the Cultivators.

These Cultivators were very strong. One of the two earth-element Cultivators was using a huge shield. The shield was massive at about ten meters high. But even if the shield looked unwieldy, the earth-element Cultivator was able to handle it with ease. This caused the bug attacks to be useless against the five.

The weapon used by the other earth-element was unique as well. It was a magical treasure in the form of a bell. This bell could enlarge and shrink itself. At its current form, it was about 5 meters high. In addition to its defensive capability, it also had a sound attack. Not only was it able to protect the party, it also caused casualties towards the bugs.

The two metal-element Cultivators were attacking the bugs in tandem. One of them used a huge scissor-like weapon. The blades of these scissors weren’t straight, instead they were curved like scimitars. The blades were very sharp. No bug survived after being cut.

The other metal-element Cultivator had an ordinary weapon – a sparkling gold sword. However, this sword was different from ordinary swords. It didn’t have a hilt since its entire body was the sword. This meant that both ends of the weapon were sharp. From its looks, one could see how offensively powerful it was.

As for the wood-element Cultivator, he stood behind the group. His weapon was quite special. It was an azure-colored leaf made with unknown material. It didn’t have a sharp edge like a blade. It was currently the vessel in which the group stood on. The leaf’s surface would oftentimes radiate green light that would enter the bodies of the other Cultivators. It seems like this leaf was a treasure that can speed up the recovery of spiritual qi.

With the group’s cooperation, the bugs were getting grinded down. From the initial 1000, the bugs had been reduced to more or less 200.

However, these flying bugs seemed to be different from the eight-legged bugs. Eight-legged bugs would continue fighting to the last bug. On the other hand, these flying bugs seem to be more intelligent. Upon seeing that they were losing, they immediately retreated.

But even if these bugs wanted to retreat, this doesn’t mean that they would be successful. The five Cultivators didn’t allow the bugs to escape. Seeing the bugs retreating, the five immediately separated and surrounded the bugs. Then the five used their weapons to attack them. The shield-bearing Cultivator had also changed his weapon into a seal. It was a square seal that had a dragon turtle’s head carved into it.

The attack of this seal was very simple. When it was used, a mountain like pressure descended into the bugs. All the bugs caught in this pressure were soon turned into paste.

The last 200 bugs didn’t take long to be killed. Once the bugs were cleaned up, the five put away their weapons. The Cultivator who had the bell turned to the Cultivator with the seal and said ,”Dong Tutian, didn’t I tell you to stop attacking? Look at what you did, a lot of bugs had been smashed. You’re decreasing our loot!”

Dong Tutian coldly snorted and said, “I’ve been defending all this time, I’m feeling suffocated. And you’re one to talk, Situ Nan. That bell of yours disintegrated a lot of bugs as well.”

Situ Nan didn’t respond. At this time, the wood-element Cultivator said, “Alright, don’t fight. Let’s clean up the battlefield quickly and then leave. This cave will soon attract other bugs. We need to find a place to recover, we can’t afford another fight.”

Chapter 1240: 1 vs 5

Pa, Pa, Pa

An applause was suddenly heard, causing Situ Nan and the others to change their complexion. Although Cultivators were more durable compared to Mages and Warriors in the Machine Field, their strength was still reduced to 60 percent after fighting all those bugs. If an enemy came at this time, then it would certainly be troublesome.

The other party making themselves known through this matter only meant bad intentions. The five looked at the direction of the clap, then couldn’t help but get stunned.

Several people in mage robes and warrior clothing came out from a passage. The one clapping was a man in black mage robes.

SItu Nan and the others were stunned at the clothing worn by these people. Mage robes and warrior clothing were only worn in the Machine Field. And it was well-known that the folks from the Machine Field were at the bottom of the six realms. This was the first time where people from the Machine Field actually showed themselves and didn’t hide.

Zhao Hai looked at Situ Nan and the others, then he smiled and said, “Cultivators are truly strong. Your fighting strength caused me to be in awe. To be honest, I don’t want to kill you. But it’s a pity that you have the cultivation methods that I want. Therefore, even if I don’t want to, I’ll have to end your lives here.”

Situ Nan’s group of five looked at each other before they burst out laughing. Situ Nan covered his belly as he pointed at Zhao Hai and said, “Kid, are you awake? You want to kill us? You’re from the Machine Field, how can you possibly kill us? Hahahaha. I swear, this is the funniest joke I heard.”

Zhao Hai didn’t care about their reaction. He just looked at his prey with a smile on his face. That’s what people are. If you ridicule the other party and they get angry, then you would find pleasure in it. If the other people scolds you, and you scold them back, but then you turn indifferent, this would make the other party uncomfortable.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s calmly smiling, Situ Nan and the others couldn’t help but be shaken. They stopped laughing. Then Situ Nan looked at Zhao Hai with a cold expression and said, “Kid, I’m amused that you don’t know the immensity of the heavens and the earth. Leave all the bugs you killed, then we’ll let you go. Otherwise, you can go die!”

After he said that, Situ Nan let out an imposing aura towards Zhao Hai. Seeing this aura, Zhao Hai just smiled and released his own, stopping Situ Nan’s aura midway.

Upon seeing this, Situ Nan and the others’ expressions changed. It was at this time that they knew that the other party was truly threatening them.

The group immediately went on-guard. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You’re very weak, but you actually want this Zhao Hai’s life. I just don’t know who doesn’t know the immensity of the heavens and the earth.” As soon as he said that, Zhao Hai released a 100-layer formation in front of him. Then this formation exploded as a fire dragon burst forth and rushed straight towards Situ Nan.

Situ Nan felt the threat of this fire dragon, his expression changed but then he suddenly sneered. He doesn’t believe that a Mage could break his defenses. He moved his hand as his bell appeared before his body.

Dang!

A ringing sound was heard as the fire dragon hit the bell. The bell rocked twice but it managed to block the fire dragon’s blow.

However, this wasn’t the end of the fire dragon. Like a living being, the fire dragon coiled around the bell and then ignited its body.

Others might not know how strong the fire dragon was, but Situ Nan knew clearly. He could feel the waves of attack that the fire dragon was doing. It was akin to ocean waves hitting the bell, causing it to shiver gently. And if this goes on for some time, then the bell would no doubt be shattered by the fire dragon.

Situ Nan’s expression changed. Then he moved his hand to cast his secret art. He mouthed out some words before he whispered, “Nine Tone Method, Shake!” As his incantation completes, the bell sharply rang with a frequency much faster than before. When the bell shook, a buzzing sound was heard. Now that the fire dragon wasn’t in Zhao Hai’s control, it slowly let go of the bell before its flames shrank.

Zhao Hai’s eyes sparkled, then he laughed and said, “Alright, since your bell likes to ring, try this out.” Then he waved his hand and another 100-layer formation appeared. This formation transformed into a giant metallic hammer. Then this hammer swung itself towards the bell.

The hammer was more than ten meters in diameter and had an octagonal shape. Although it was just magic, the hammer had the imposing aura that could shake the world.

In addition the hammer, the fire dragon also charged aggressively towards Situ Nan. Although its size was smaller than before, its threatening aura still couldn’t be underestimated.

Situ Nan’s complexion changed. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai’s magic control to be this powerful. He could actually use two spells at the same time. Situ Nan quickly retreated as he made his bell make another move. The bell sounded out with tones that were uncommon to the ears.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about this change as he continued to command the hammer and fire dragon to hit Situ Nan. But at the same time, he was also paying close attention to the other Cultivators. This was a fight for life, not a fight in an arena. These people wouldn’t just sit still if they saw that Situ Nan is in real danger.

And just like what Zhao Hai thought, seeing the two attacks, the others also changed their expressions. Dong Tutian moved his hand as his dragon turtle seal flew out. Then it increased its size and exerted a mountainous pressure towards Zhao Hai’s hammer.

Zhao Hai coldly snorted, then his hammer changed direction and pounded towards the dragon turtle seal. A bang was heard before the dragon turtle seal was flung in the air. However, this impact also caused Zhao Hai’s hammer to disappear.

Dong Tutian spent a lot of strength to control the dragon turtle seal. Seeing it being thrown away, he quickly told the others, “This is bad, we need to work together!”

The other Cultivators immediately used their magic treasures to attack Zhao Hai. Seeing these attacks heading towards him, Zhao Hai moved and welcomed them. At the same time, his staff appeared in his hand. Upon waving his staff, five 100-layer formations instantly appeared and attacked the five people.

The five Cultivators now knew clearly that they couldn’t underestimate Zhao Hai. They quickly controlled their magic treasures to deal with Zhao Hai’s spells. At this moment, Zhao Hai’s staff turned into a greatsword. Then his figure vanished as he reappeared on Situ Nan’s side, already swinging his sword.

When Situ Nan discovered that Zhao Hai appeared beside him, his complexion drastically changed. Then he moved his hand to make a small shield block Zhao Hai’s strike. As the shield was broken through by Zhao Hai’s sword, Situ Nan used the opportunity to retreat. Then he took out a lot of paper talismans and threw them all towards Zhao Hai.

Just like the sound of paper tearing, Zhao Hai’s sword easily broke through the shield. But at the same time, the paper talismans turned into icicles and fire as they approached Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai waved his hand, discarding the shield that was still stuck in his sword. Then Zhao Hai waved his greatsword, breaking all of the icicles and fire with one fell swoop.

At this time, the other Cultivators also discovered the predicament that Situ Nan was in. They all loudly shouted and then used their own secret arts to deal with Zhao Hai’s magic before attacking Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai coldly snorted, then he waved his sword causing another five 100-layer formations to attack the Cultivators. At the same time, he released sword qi from the sword to attack Situ Nan.

It didn’t take long before the six combatants exchanged several moves. However, Zhao Hai was having the upper hand in a 1 vs 5. Not only did he break Situ Nan’s shield, he also made Situ Nan and the others frustrated.

The Cultivators didn’t have good expressions on their faces. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this formidable. At this time, the wood-element Cultivator loudly shouted, “Draw back to a formation!” Then his figure moved as he retreated. The others retreated as well and then made the same formation as they did when they surrounded the bugs. At the same time, they also brought out their own treasures.

Situ Nan had his bell, Dong Tutian didn’t use his shield but instead his turtle dragon seal. The other people were also using the same weapons they used to deal with the bugs a moment ago. However, they were preparing another weapon as well as talismans to use at any time.

The five-element formation was Situ Nan and the others’ last resort. The five element formation doesn’t require five different elements to be used. In fact, it only needed five Cultivators. However, the effect of the formation would depend on the Cultivators using it.

The five-element formation allowed Situ Nan and the others to fight in their full strength. The more these five cooperated together, the more powerful they were.

Back when they dealt with the flying bugs, everyone only used one weapon and they didn’t take out a second one nor did they use any talismans. But now that they were fighting against Zhao Hai, their second weapon was out and their paper talismans were also being used. Naturally, they had already regarded Zhao Hai’s threat to their lives.

Seeing the five Cultivators like this, Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Alright, good. Gather around, it’s better to deal with you this way. Watch this.” Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as a 1000-layer formation appeared. The formation activated itself and under the five Cultivator’s gaze, a rift opened in the air as a meteorite dropped down. The meteorite’s target was the five Cultivators.

When the wood-element Cultivator saw this, his complexion changed. Then he operated his leaf to retreat. However, what they didn’t expect was the rift following them. Meteorites continued to fall down from the rift, falling down with immense aura. The sight was astonishing.

Seeing this scene, Situ Nan activated his bell. The bell increased its size as it covered everyone.

At the same time Dong Tutian used his dragon turtle seal to increase its size and then meet the meteorites.

The other Cultivators didn’t idle. They knew that all of these meteorites were under Zhao Hai’s control. Therefore, the two metal-element Cultivators took out their weapons and attacked Zhao Hai.

Chapter 1241: Ancestor Appears

As soon as he saw the attackers, Zhao Hai laughed and then waved his greatsword. The sword quickly turned into a huge whip. The whip entangled the scissor as it was used to slam towards the double-ended sword.

Zhao Hai’s approach caused the two metal-element Cultivators to stare. One should know that Zhao Hai was now facing two magic weapons, not just paper talismans. Paper talismans could no longer be controlled once thrown, unlike weapons. As long as Zhao Hai exerts some pressure, then Zhao Hai could change the talisman’s direction with his whip.

Once magic weapons were sent out, they could still be controlled by their master. Magic weapons and flying swords were not much different to Cultivators. But now, Zhao Hai wanted to use another person’s magic weapon to deal with another magic weapon? Was he too arrogant?

The two Cultivators were stunned for a moment before they controlled their weapons with all of their strength. However, what they didn’t expect was that Zhao Hai was just pretending. Naturally, Zhao Hai wasn’t arrogant enough to think that he was able to control other people’s weapons. He just wanted to scare the two Cultivators. One of them immediately enlarged his scissors in order to get out of Zhao Hai’s whip. At the same time, the double-ended sword also attacked Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai laughed as he voluntarily loosened his whip before waving it downward. Then the whip turned into a hammer as it pounded towards the double-ended sword.

Dang! A loud noise was heard as the hammer hit the double-ended sword. The hammer was very strong, causing the owner of the sword to spit blood.

The owner of the double-ended Cultivator didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be his true target. Zhao Hai turned his greatsword into a long whip and then used it to entangle the scissors. After doing that, Zhao Hai tried to drag the scissors towards the double-ended sword. The two metal-element Cultivators thought that Zhao Hai was using the scissors to smash towards the sword. The owner of the scissors naturally stopped his weapon. However, both Cultivators forgot that Zhao Hai’s weapon could transform. Since Zhao Hai used the whip to pull the scissors towards the double-ended sword, then the whip was naturally pointed towards the sword. Once Zhao Hai turned the whip into a hammer, the direction of force wasn’t changed while its impact power was increased. This allowed the owner of the double-ended sword to be caught off-guard.

The Cultivator with the double-ended sword wasn’t prepared. And since Zhao Hai’s attack was very hard, the Cultivation was seriously injured. He even lost control of his double-ended sword.

Zhao Hai immediately captured the double-ended sword and then sent it to the Space. At this time, the Cultivator with the scissor found out that he had been fooled. His expression was ugly as he quickly commanded his scissors to attack Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai laughed, then he transformed his hammer into two tonfas. He blocked the scissors using his two arms. At the same time, Zhao Hai kicked his foot sending forth a pitch black disk. The disk was extremely fast and was releasing the sound of wailing ghosts. This was Li Chuchen’s spinning ghost disk.

This disk wasn’t for the owner of the scissors but instead for the injured metal-element Cultivator. Seeing the spinning ghost disk, the Cultivator quickly extended his hand, sacrificing a magic artifact to defend himself.

This artifact wasn’t offensive like the double-edged sword, but it was instead an earthen bowl. Once it appeared, the artifact enlarged to block the spinning ghost disk.

It was also at this moment that the owner of the scissors discovered what happened. He took back his scissors and then threw paper talismans out. Once the talismans were activated, he resumed his attack.

This exchange happened in almost an instant. The wood-element Cultivator and the two earth-element Cultivators still had their hands full. Zhao Hai’s 1000-layer skyfall magic was still releasing meteorites. They were too preoccupied with dealing with almost 100 meteorites to help the two metal-element Cultivator.

Zhao Hai’s spinning ghost disk hit the earthen bowl that the earth-element Cultivator released. The sound of impact wasn’t loud. Conversely, the sound was very flat compared to previous impacts.

This caused the two metal-element Cultivators to stare. The spinning ghost disk actually broke. The two couldn’t help but get startled. The spinning ghost disk that they knew wasn’t as brittle like this.

They had seen Li Chuchen use this spinning ghost disk before. Therefore, they knew clearly well how formidable this weapon was. Seeing Zhao Hai using the spinning ghost disk, they immediately thought about Li Chuchen. They were afraid that Li Chuchen had met an extremely unfortunate end. So they didn’t dare underestimate the spinning ghost disk.

However, what they didn’t expect was this wasn’t Li Chuchen’s actual spinning ghost disk. Instead, this ghost spinning disk was a replica made by Zhao Hai’s liquid silver staff.

It was because of this that the spinning ghost disk shattered when it met the earthen bowl. However, this didn’t mean that it was broken, the shards turned into small metallic blades that continued to attack.

The Cultivator who used the double-ended sword didn’t expect the spinning ghost disk to have a second attack. Since he was seriously injured, he wasn’t able to react in time. The small spinning blades sliced into his body, killing him instantly.

The spinning blades that hit the metal-element’s body were well-placed. One of them hit him in the heart while the other sliced his throat.

The other spinning blades proceeded to attack the scissor-wielding Cultivator. The Cultivator was surprised when he saw the blades going towards him. He quickly sent out a small shield as he retreated. The shield enlarged itself and blocked the blades.

However, the shield was split apart when it was hit by the blades. Then the spinning blades accelerated, killing the Cultivator in five hits.

There were still spinning blades left, which continued their assault towards the remaining three Cultivators. Although the three were dealing with Zhao Hai’s magic, they still kept some attention towards their two comrades. One of the reasons why they weren’t able to help was Zhao Hai’s spell, while the other reason was because they didn’t expect the two to fall this quickly.

Seeing the two metal-element Cultivators dead and then the spinning blades attacking them, the three remaining Cultivators were startled. But fortunately, their bodies were within the protection of Situ Nan’s bell.

The two metal-element Cultivators were easily killed because they failed to notice Zhao Hai luring them outside the protective range of the bell.

Under the gazes of Situ Nan and the others, the spinning blades hit the bell accompanied with banging sounds. Then the blades shattered into smaller blades which attacked the bell once more. Situ Nan and the others also noticed that the collision that was caused had increased in intensity.

It was now time for Situ Nan to suffer. He needed to pay attention to the meteorites while the spinning ghost blades were continuing to shatter and increase in strength. In no time, he and the other two were stuck about what to do.

Then at this time, the wood-element Cultivator said, “Dong Tutian, do you best to deal with the meteorites. I’ll deal with these spinning blades with Situ Nan.”

The two gave a nod as Situ Nan received his bell. Although the defensive capability of this bell was very good, its range was too big. Moreover, the energy it consumed was large. Having just fought a swarm of bugs, it wouldn’t take long before Situ Nan would run out of energy.

The wood-element Cultivator and the earth-element Cultivator were clear about this. So before Situ Nan put away his bell, they quickly took a few pills.

This recovery pill was specially made to act much faster compared to the Machine Field’s potions. Therefore, these pills were high-quality goods. They were handed these pills because they were joining the Six Realm Beginner Competition, so they were quite reluctant to take it.

Just as the three took their pills, the two dead metal-element Cultivators suddenly stood up and then attacked their former comrades with their weapons.

Situ Nan and Dong Tutian were stunned at the scene so they were quickly killed. However, the wood-element Cultivator was able to react quickly. When the two metal-element Cultivators stood up, he immediately flew back and threw a golden bowl to block the attacks.

At this time, the skyfall spell had ended its duration. Situ Nan and three others were already dead – only the wood-element Cultivator was left. But even if his golden bowl was able to block some attacks, he was still injured. His face was a little pale.

Currently, his leaf-like artifact was blocking in front of him acting as a shield. The wood-element Cultivator was looking at Zhao Hai with hate.

Zhao Hai looked at the wood-element Cultivator, then he smiled faintly and said, “Your response is very good. I didn’t read wrong, it seems like you’re the strongest among the five of you. Unfortunately, you wouldn’t be able to escape today.”

The wood-element Cultivator coldly smiled in response and said, “A country bumpkin is still a country bumpkin. You’re too young to understand the means of the Cultivation Realm. I’ll let you experience how terrifying Cultivators could be!”

As he said that, the wood-element Cultivator took out a piece of jade. Zhao Hai fixed his eyes on the jade and saw runes carved all over its body. It’s actually a jade talisman!

The wood-element Cultivator looked at the jade talisman with regret, then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You forced me to do this. Now die!” He raised the jade talisman and then declared, “Borrowing the power of the heavens, Ancestor, appear!” Then he pinched the jade talisman fiercely.

Bang! An incomparably powerful aura burst out of the jade talisman. This aura went forth and put pressure on Zhao Hai!

Chapter 1242: Beginning of the Bug Tide

When Zhao Hai felt this imposing aura, his expression changed. He knew how formidable this aura was. Even if he used all of his strength, he wouldn’t be able to match it.

Along with the aura was a silhouette of a person appearing in front of the wood-element Cultivator. This person was wearing a daoist robe. His hair as well as eyebrows were white. Also, his eyebrows were very long, just like his silvery beard. He held a wine bottle in his hand. His hair was tied up by a turquoise jade hairpin. He looked very sage-like, it was as though he was one with nature.

When this old daoist appeared, his electric eyes shot towards Zhao Hai as he called out, “Bold evildoer! You dare to hurt my disciple. Die!” Then he waved his hand as a golden palm pressed towards Zhao Hai.

Seeing this attack, Zhao Hai coldly snorted and said, “Just a Nascent Soul. You better give up.” Then he made a fist with his hand and then hit the palm with a punch.

Zhao Hai’s fist caused a huge hole to appear on the golden palm. An explosion was heard, and it actually caused the sturdy cave to shudder. The wood-element Cultivator was killed by the shock of the collision.

Zhao Hai snorted and then waved his hand to collect the bodies of the Cultivators. Then he released Undead to clean up the battlefield. Once the place was cleaned up, Zhao Hai and the others took their own share of bugs. Then they left the cave and flew away.

Not long after Zhao Hai and the others left, other Cultivators arrived at the scene. Upon entering the cave, the Cultivators’ expressions changed. They felt the trace of battle in the cave, especially when Zhao Hai destroyed the Nascent Soul old man’s attack. That clash caused huge fluctuations that it still lingered for the Cultivators to sense.

These Cultivators obviously knew each other but they weren’t friends. One of the Cultivators in black clothing looked at the others and then said, “You guys sensed it too? It seems like a Nascent Soul Expert made a move here.”

A Cultivator in green snorted and said, “Yi Shuihan, you rarely act stupid. We can clearly see that the situation isn’t as crazy as that. Two people were fighting here and one of them used a jade talisman. I just didn’t know what enemy they faced for them to be compelled to use a jade talisman.”

The black clothed Yi Shuihan sneered, he turned his head and said, “Jiang Tian, are you dumb? Can’t you sense other auras here other than that Nascent Soul Grandmaster?”

A person wearing white and has a sword at his back nodded respectfully and said, “It’s just as brother Yi said. Besides that Nascent Soul aura, there seem to be six other fluctuations in this place. Five of them are from our Cultivation Realm. Two metal-element, two-earth element, and a wood element Cultivator. The last one has a very special aura. Forgive me for being unable to know what it is.”

When Jiang Tian heard the polite apology of the white-robed Cultivator, he couldn’t help but gawk. Then he said, “Even Ten Thousand Sword Sect’s Suo Liancheng can’t feel it. This is strange.”

A person wearing red clothing said with a serious expression, “I can feel a weak aura of fire. It seems to be a fire spell. It’s power should be formidable, I just don’t know what kind of spell it is.”

Suo Liancheng frowned slightly and said, “Brother Qin Zhang has already reached major perfection in his fire element art, but even you can’t discern which spell it is? It seems like the enemy that the five met wasn’t weak.”

At this time, a person wearing Daoist Clothes commented, “From the death suffered by the bugs, it seems like the five used the five elements formation. Everyone should remember the five guys from the three mountains alliance.”

Upon hearing this, Suo Liancheng’s expression changed. Then he said, “Brother Yao Gan, do you mean Situ Nan’s group? Those five are very powerful when they work together. Who would dare provoke them? Moreover, from what we can see, Situ Nan’s group didn’t hold back.”

Yi Shuihan coldly said, “Not only did they go all out, it seems like they had been very unfortunate. They were even forced to use a jade talisman. And from the feeling of death that I can sense, if they weren’t dead, then they wouldn’t be able to live for long.”

Upon hearing Yi Shuihan, everyone’s expression changed. They knew that Yi Shuihan was a Ghost Dao Cultivator, so he was very sensitive when it came to death. His insight about this topic should be accurate.

However, this matter made those present wonder. How could a rookie defeat the group of five using the five element formation? They even forced the use of a jade talisman. Who had such strength?

Then at this time, Yao Gan opened his mouth and said, “I don’t know if you have heard about this news. But before we arrived at Fabio Planet, Base Number 5 was attacked by the bugs. When the base was about to fall, a person managed to fight against a silverback gold-winged bug one on one. It was said that this person was also a participant of the competition. It’s the Machine Field’s top newcomer, Zhao Hai. Do you think it’s him?”

Upon hearing Yao Gan, Jiang Tian couldn’t help but laugh as he said, “That’s impossible. I’m more likely to believe that the Machine Field retreated immediately when they saw the bugs.”

…

While these Cultivators were chatting, Zhao Hai was leading Xiong Li and the others away. They were still avoiding as many bugs as possible. The bugs were presently agitated. If they were to come in contact with any bug now, then it’s possible that they might trigger the bug tide ahead of time.

Xiong Li and the others looked at Zhao Hai’s expression and knew that it wasn’t time to tell jokes. Therefore, they just followed Zhao Hai silently as they navigated the labyrinth that was the bug underworld.

Although Xiong Li and the others couldn’t remember their previous route, they could tell that Zhao Hai wasn’t leading them in circles. How can Zhao Hai do this? They might try to guess, but they didn’t say nor ask anything. They just blindly trusted Zhao Hai.

After flying non-stop for seven hours, Zhao Hai finally stopped to rest at a cave. Then he took out food and then shared it with everyone. While they were eating, Li Kuangren looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, are we going back to the transmission formation? And why do I feel like the current situation isn’t right?”

Although Li Kuangren was  clueless about the current situation, the intuition that he sharpened over countless battles was telling him that something was wrong.

In fact, it wasn’t only Li Kuangren who felt this, Xiong Li and the others as well. Hearing Li Kuangren, Xiong Li nodded and said, “I feel it as well. These caves around us seem to be filled with danger.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “Your intuition is correct. The caves are currently filled with danger. In fact, we just avoided a massive bug tide. We should get to a transmission formation in five hours. We don’t have much time left.”

Chapter 1243: The Tide Approaches

Li Kuangren didn’t say anything more and just believed Zhao Hai’s words. In any case, they had been safe all this time while traversing the cave system. If Zhao Hai left them behind, they still wouldn’t be able to find the way out.

At this moment, Zhao Hai’s expression changed. He touched the ground and then immediately stood up as he said, “Leave this area quick!” Then the group quickly flew towards a nearby cave with no hesitation.

Although the others had no idea what was going on, they were still able to feel something from their surroundings. There were currently minute sounds of movement around them.

It sounded like a skitter, but it was a skitter that sounded extremely terrifying.

Zhao Hai looked at the caves and let out a long breath. Then he said, “The bug tide has begun. We need to be more careful. Otherwise, once we get entangled with those bugs, it would be very hard for us to return to the transmission formation.”

Xiong Li’s expression changed, then he said, “Little Hai, if we’re heading back to the transmission formation, wouldn’t it be quicker if you use Space magic?”

When Zhao Hai heard Xiong Li, he couldn’t help but slap his own head. Then he laughed and said, “Boss Xiong, thanks for reminding me. I actually forgot about it. Alright, let’s go.”

Zhao Hai had honestly forgotten about using the Space for this situation. Although the situation was critical, it wasn’t to the point where it was a threat to Zhao Hai’s life. With how much Zhao Hai wanted to protect the secret of the Space, he actually forgot that he already had renown as a space mage. Therefore, he forgot that he could use the Space’s transport to travel quickly.

Now that he had been reminded by Xiong Li, Zhao Hai remembered that he had used this ability before. In any case, Xiong Li and the others would just think that it was a space-attribute spell and wouldn’t suspect anything. Moreover, this would save them some effort of flying along.

Xiong Li and the others looked at Zhao Hai in strange expressions. They haven’t seen Zhao Hai make a mistake before. In their eyes, Zhao Hai was perfect. But a person like him actually made such a simple mistake. They didn’t know how to react.

Zhao Hai looked at their expressions, then he asked, “What happened? Is there something wrong?”

Xiong Li forced a smile and said, “Little Hai, you look very clever all the time, how could you forget something like space magic? Don’t you use it a lot?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Actually, I was absorbed by the feeling of flying through caves. It’s like flying through a mysterious labyrinth.”

His explanation naturally invited the laughter and scolding of the others. But Zhao Hai didn’t take it too seriously and just laughed with them. Then in the next moment he waved his hand and opened a passage towards the transmission formation.

After three days, the bug parts that were left here had started to rot. The smell was enough to make people faint. Naturally, Zhao Hai disliked this smell so he used wind magic to drive it away towards smaller caves. Then he used water magic to clean the cave and then fire magic to roast the place.

Then Zhao Hai used earth magic to close up those small caves. Only two caves were left open for ventilation. This would also reduce the amount of bugs that could detect the place. Zhao Hai knew that if the bugs found them, then they would certainly attack. Those earthen walls would do nothing to stop them.

After dealing with this, Zhao Hai and the others sat inside the transmission formation. The transmission formation was specially made so that it couldn’t be erased. Moreover, Cultivators would perform maintenance on it from time to time. Therefore, there’s nothing wrong about it.

Naturally, Zhao Hai discovered that this wasn’t any special method. Actually, the formation’s real structure was buried underground. It can be said that if that formation wasn’t destroyed, then the formation aboveground would stay in place. Otherwise, this formation wouldn’t have survived after multiple bug tides.

As they sat down, Xiong Li and the others began to relax. To be honest, they were quite tense. This was because they knew that without Zhao Hai, they couldn’t survive the bug attack.

In fact, what Xiong Li and the others didn’t know was that Zhao Hai can bring them above ground using the Space. They thought that Zhao Hai had no coordinates to Base Number 5 so he couldn’t send them back. They weren’t aware that Zhao Hai could just take them back at any time.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t bother bringing it up. He didn’t want his abilities to be known that much.

Once they had sat down, Xiong Li let out a long breath and then said, “I didn’t expect that we’d meet a bug tide. Little Hai, how do you think the other realms did?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I don’t know about the other realms. But I’m very sure that six participants from the Machine Field would get the top spots of the competition. Although the Cultivators are powerful, I’m afraid they would lose a lot this time. And there’s the bug tide as well. It would be very hard for them to deal with it.”

Li Kuangren was grinning as he said, “That’s good. Those guys in the Cultivation Realm are annoying to look at. I’ll be happy if more of them die. Once the competition ends, I’ll definitely teach them a lesson.”

When everyone heard Li Kuangren, everybody laughed. Then Zhao Hai smiled and said, “The Cultivation Realm’s losses shouldn’t be small, the same is true for the other realms. Even if we’re the only ones left in the Machine Field, I can affirm that we’ll have the best result in the World of Cultivation.”

Xiong Li and the others laughed. They knew that they would be making history this time. This would be good for their future plans in the Machine Field. After all, they were preparing to go independent.

Although Zhao Hai was happily chatting with the others, he was also paying close attention to the situation using the silver needles. Liquid Silver’s needles had been scattered all throughout the nearby cave system, waiting for any bugs to come in.

However, just like Zhao Hai thought, there were no eight-legged bugs in the surrounding area. This was because they had just destroyed the nearby nest. It would take some time before this region would be repopulated with bugs. Because of this, they were able to take a rare break.

In the next five days, no other bugs entered the region besides locust-like bugs. However, Zhao Hai didn’t treat these locusts lightly. He immediately dispatched several undead in order to deal with them.

Zhao Hai knew that these locusts were scouts and the large army of bugs would come later. If this was any other time, the other bugs might not come over once these locusts were killed. However, since a bug tide was forming, it’s almost certain that the bugs were heading over to kill the Undead.

Zhao Hai looked at Xiong Li and the others. They were currently stabilizing their breathing in order to maintain their optimum condition. Zhao Hai talked with a serious tone, “Brothers, there’s some work to do.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others opened their eyes. They looked at Zhao Hai who nodded and said, “Bugs are coming, and they are coming in fast.”

Everyone quickly stood up. Li Kuangren flexed his arms as he laughed and said, “Let them come. I’m even beginning to think that we’ll wait here until the elimination round ends.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, but his attention was still focused on the bug caves. He kept close attention to the areas that he blocked off before. So even if the bugs wanted to attack Zhao Hai and the others, they would have to spend a lot of time cleaning up those walls made by earth magic. And if they choose not to break through, then they would only have two entrances to go through. This would allow Zhao Hai and the others to defend their location quite easily.

Sure enough, an hour after the locust was killed, massive amounts of flying bugs flew over. There were also eight-legged bugs as well as small beetle-like bugs. These new beetle bugs weren’t high-level, but their number was enough to cause headaches.

When these bugs saw that the path in front of them was blocked, they didn’t take a detour. Perhaps there was no such thing as the word ‘detour’ in their minds. These bugs immediately started to excavate the earth in front of them. Zhao Hai discovered how fast the bugs could excavate. It didn’t take a long time for the bugs to go through a meter of earth.

The bugs were advancing at a very quick speed. Zhao Hai knew that it wouldn’t take long for them to go through the blockade. Therefore, he waved his hand and released a large number of Undead into the cave where the bugs were in. This time, the first Undead that Zhao Hai released weren’t all humanoid. Instead, most of them had beast shapes. Each body of these Undead were more than ten meters long. They had two eyes that lit up like torches as well as claws that could rip through bones.

Inside these beasts were humanoid Undead carrying cannons. These Undead were operating magic cannons. This made the Undead unit functionally similar to tanks.

Chapter 1244: Formidable Beast Undead Unit

Xiong Li and the others stared at Zhao Hai’s new Undead unit. After some time, Xiong Li turned his head towards Zhao Hai, eyes shining as he said, “Little Hai, how many secrets do you really have? Can’t you just take them all out?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “No rush, no rush. The place where I came from isn’t a peaceful place. I’ve encountered wars between million-people armies several times. If you’re not armed against those fellows, then you would die. But you can rest assured, we won’t have any problems defending for the next few days.”

Xiong Li didn’t ask more. They just turned their heads towards the Undead beast units. The beasts looked very sturdy, giving Xiong Li and the others morale.

Most importantly, besides the beasts walking on the ground, there were also plenty of them flying in the air. These flying beasts were also armed to the teeth, looking incomparably fierce.

All beast Undead that Zhao Hai released had every offensive part armed with iron fittings. Their teeth were reinforced with metal, their tails were supplemented with hammers, and some of their claws were sharpened. These bodily weapons might not look menacing, but these weapons were also inscribed with magic formations, the weapon shattering formation.

These iron fittings were the latest additions. When Zhao Hai gave the Undead army new weapons, Laura was the one to propose this idea. She also proposed using these beasts more often compared to humanoid Undead.

Zhao Hai didn’t know why this was the case, but Laura told him that it was for his reputation. No matter which place, releasing a large number of humanoid Undead would make people label you as an evildoer. This would be very disadvantageous to Zhao Hai’s future development since this would provide his enemies with a proper reason to deal with him.

Also, these beast Undead were large and had bodies that were highly transformable. They were also stronger compared to humanoid Undead. Because of this, Laura hoped that Zhao Hai would use them more often in the future.

Zhao Hai happily accepted Laura’s proposition. Then he made Laura install weapons on the beasts, and he also ensured that they all had weapon shattering. Naturally, the quality of their weapon shattering couldn’t be compared to Xiong Li and the others. Xiong Li and the others had weapons made with special materials, and while Zhao Hai had a lot of good materials in the Space, their ore veins were still in their growth phases, completely unsuitable for large-scale mining. Therefore, Zhao Hai could only use the Space’s stockpile of material to create weapons.

Nevertheless, the result was very extraordinary. After these weapons were installed, the beast Undead’s fighting strength had increased by at least three points. And if the magic cannons were added, then these Beast Undead unit’s fighting strength could seriously be considered as terrifying.

Because of this, Zhao Hai was able to make a death squad of beast undead. Moreover, these Undead had different weapons in their bodies, making them even more terrifying.

While the brothers were speaking, the flying mantis bugs had already flown into the cave. However, just as they appeared, they were suddenly met with a bone dragon and were immediately extinguished.

Although these flying mantis bugs weren’t weak, the bone dragons couldn’t be underestimated as well. After the Space leveled up several times, the bone dragons had also leveled up. Their strength had become formidable. Naturally, the bone dragons had no problems dealing with the flying mantis bugs.

However, these low-level bugs never won because of their strength, instead they depended on their numerical superiority. A seemingly inexhaustible amount of flying mantis bugs streamed into the cave. This opened the curtain for the beginning of the battle.

In the beginning, only the flying bugs were present so the Undead were able to easily deal with them. They haven’t even used their weapons yet.

But soon after, other blocked passages were beginning to be broken through. More and more bugs came, adding more oil to the fires of battle. The Undead beasts had one advantage over these bugs, and that was their size, defense, and strength. Therefore, they still had an easy time. There were also the magic cannons that helped them deal with the incoming bugs.

Xiong Li and the others discovered that they were too preoccupied being the spectators of the battle. They can only stand there and watch the Undead fight the endless stream of bugs.

Li Kuangren looked discontentedly at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, you’re hogging all the glory. Look at how busy the battle has become, do you hate me that much?”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Isn’t it fun to just watch? People from other realms would never find such an opportunity. I reckon those guys are getting desperate at this time. Hahaha. Think about it, while those guys are fighting for their lives, we’re here drinking and watching a show.”

As soon as they heard Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others laughed. Just like Zhao Hai said, while the others were going all out, they were here watching the battle as though it was entertainment.

Li Kuangren laughed as well, then he said, “That’s right. When I think of those guys from the Cultivation Realm looking desperate, I couldn’t help but be happy. Hahaha.”

Time went by as more and more bugs appeared. Moreover, as time passed, the bugs coming over were getting stronger and stronger. Some bugs can even fight the Undead one-to-one. However, those bugs would still die to the magic cannons. With the combined power of the beast Undead and the magic cannons, the bugs were unable to do anything for a while.

The cave where Zhao Hai and the others were wasn’t small, but it did appear like so. Undead and bugs filled the place up. From time to time, the Undead line would be breached by a couple of bugs, so Zhao Hai and the others would have to make a move themselves.

Although some gaps appeared in the Undead line, this didn’t mean that they were getting killed. The Undead held their own defensive position but they were also being tied down by multiple bugs. Therefore, one or two would inevitably slip in. However, those who did were easily dealt with by Xiong Li and the others.

Time passed as more and more bug corpses filled up the cave. Zhao Hai had yet to lose an Undead. This also allowed Zhao Hai to see how powerful these beast undead were. If the army was composed of humanoid Undead, then a few would have already died to the bugs.

It didn’t take long before Zhao Hai understood what was going on. Compared to humanoids, the beasts had stronger bodies. Because the humanoids had traded their body strength for wisdom, they became inferior to the beasts in terms of physiology. And after being turned into Undead, even if the two had the same level, the beasts would still have much sturdier bodies compared to humanoids. Especially the Undead that Zhao Hai had. Their bodies were formidable, strong, and had astonishing defensive strength. Although they couldn’t easily sweep through a human army, they were enough to deal with the bugs.

Upon thinking about this point, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel regret. If he had known this before, then he would’ve used beast Undead sooner. The firepower provided by these beast Undead made sure that each of them were their own war machines.

Xiong Li and the others were also able to see how powerful the beast Undead were. This made them excited, so they flew over and took out a few bugs to practice their moves.

When the group wiped out a batch of bugs, they returned to where Zhao Hai was. Xiong Li looked at the Undead as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Those guys are full of energy. Little Hai, you should have taken them out sooner.”

Zhao Hai smiled and didn’t say anything. At this time, Sun Fei looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, how long has it been? Why do I feel like time is moving too quickly?” Zhao Hai chuckled and said, “It’ll end soon. We should be able to return in eight hours. Rest assured, nothing wrong will happen.”

Sun Fei nodded and said, “I’m not worried about not being able to go back. But I just feel like time passed by quickly. In just a blink of an eye, seven days went by just like that.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Time passes quite fast for us. But for the others, I reckon they feel the opposite. Those guys should be very anxious to return.” Sun Fei and the others heard this and laughed. They completely agreed to Zhao Hai’s answer. To be honest, even if they were from the lower realms and hadn’t ascended for a long time, they were still aware that Zhao Hai’s Undead were insanely strong. They had never seen creatures as terrifying as them, whether it be in the lower realms or in the Machine Field.

However, they didn’t ask anything. Although they had become sworn brothers, they knew that they still had secrets that they kept from each other. If Zhao Hai doesn’t want to say it, then they won’t ask.

At this time, Zhao Hai turned his head to Lu Dingtian and said, “Second Brother, I think it would be better for you if you had a mount. Am I correct?”

Lu Dingtian nodded and said, “Yes”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Then if we have free time, I’ll give you a beast as a mount. I believe it will make you even stronger. What do you think?”

With shining eyes, Lu Dingtian nodded and said, “Good.”

Li Kuangren couldn’t help but interject, “Second Brother, would it kill you if you say a second word? You talk so little.”

Lu Dingtian nodded and said, “Yes.” His response caused everyone to laugh out loud.

Then at this moment, the transmission formation behind them suddenly emitted white light.

Chapter 1245: The Anxious Ma Rulong

Zhao Hai and the others stared, then they all cheered. Zhao Hai said, “Good, now that the transmission formation can be used, we can head back. But if we head back now, I’m afraid they wouldn’t calculate our scores. Let’s wait for a couple of hours before returning.” Xiong Li and the others nodded. They weren’t worried about returning. In any case, they weren’t in immediate danger. It would be no problem if they took a few hours before heading back.

Zhao Hai looked at everyone, then he smiled and said, “Alright, let’s go eat something. Let’s just leave everything else to the Undead.” Then he waved his hand and released some humanoid Undead. These Undead took on the task of cleaning up the bugs that were able to pass through the defense line. Meanwhile, Xiong Li and the others sat in the transmission formation and ate crabs while pouring each other drinks.

Now that the transmission formation has been activated, people from Base Number 5 could use it to enter the cave system and vice versa. But this was given that nobody was in the transmission formation. Since Zhao Hai and the others were sitting inside the transmission formation, then this was akin to the formation becoming useless.

But what Zhao Hai and the others didn’t think was that the transmission formation activated because Base Number 5 intentionally opened it. Zhao Hai and the others thought that they would be mocked by the Cultivators if they came out early. Therefore, they decided to wait a couple of hours before returning. However, this decision caused Ma Rulong to turn anxious.

Actually, the transmission formation has been activated ahead of time. This wasn’t only because they wanted the participants to head back, they also wanted to send reinforcements in.

The bases had already known about the bug tide that was happening. To ensure the safety of the competition’s participants, they decided to end the elimination round ahead of time then send support to get rid of the bugs. In fact, the moment the transmission formations were activated, the elimination round was over.

Zhao Hai and his brothers were completely oblivious to this. At the same time, since Laura and the others were monitoring the cave system, they didn’t have the time to care about what happened in the base. Therefore, nobody from their group knew that the elimination round was over, and that they were waiting for nothing.

On the other hand, Ma Rulong was too anxious that he looked like ants in a heated pan. The moment he discovered that a bug tide was ravaging through the cave systems, Ma Rulong knew that things weren’t doing so well. People would die from each realm, and the Machine Field might as well be annihilated, but it wouldn’t be a big deal since they were rookies. However, Ma Rulong was very worried about Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai blocked Li Chuchen’s three swords, killed Gongsun Zheng, and even managed to demonstrate his strength against the silverback gold-winged bug. This caused Ma Rulong to expect Zhao Hai to bring great results. If Zhao Hai perished because of this bug tide, then the Machine Field would certainly make Ma Rulong answer for it.

Because of this, the moment the transmission formation was activated, he immediately thought of going through it to aid Zhao Hai. However, even if the formation has been activated, it couldn’t be used.

The transmission formation designed by the Cultivation Realm was very clever. It had a function where if someone was standing on either side of the formation, then neither side could be used. Naturally, it wasn’t just people, any living thing standing on it could trigger this function.

Of course, when the people from the Cultivation Realm set up this transmission formation, they also thought about the possibility that other living beings would render it useless. Therefore, when they were making the formation, a special material was added. The name of this material was repellent incense. This material was a kind of wood that emits an odor that was disliked by the bugs and other beasts. In this way, the Cultivators were able to make sure that bugs and other beasts won’t occupy the formation.

It was also because of this setup that when Zhao Hai and the others were entering the caves for the first time, the formation wasn’t blocked by the bugs and was just surrounded.

Originally, Ma Rulong thought that when the formation has been activated, they could immediately head in and use it. However, it seems like the formation cannot be used. This caused Ma Rulong to be confused. Could it be that someone was standing in the formation? Moreover, this person was alive. It should be said that if a deceased person was on top of the formation, the formation would still work.

Ma Rulong doesn’t know what was going on. Bugs don’t like being around the transmission formation. Dead people cannot block the formation. Therefore, there shouldn’t be any problems in using it. Since this is the case, then there’s only one reason. Living people are standing in the formation. But if living people were in the formation, then they should know that it has been activated. If so, then why didn’t they head back immediately when they saw the light?

Ma Rulong was burning with impatience. He was completely clueless about the state of Fabio Planet’s underworld. He was afraid that Zhao Hai and the others had been annihilated. Although he already had that idea before, Zhao Hai had given him hope. If people don’t expect anything, then they won’t be disappointed. However, if they were given hope, and that hope was broken, then their disappointment would be doubled. Ma Rulong was in this state.

While  Ma Rulong was impatiently circling around the transmission formation, Zheng Li’s face was stuck on the formation. Zheng Li hasn’t been in Base Number 5 for a day or two, he had been here for several years. The battle with the silverback gold-winged bug was actually the most dangerous time he experienced here. If it weren’t for Zhao Hai, then even Zheng Li couldn’t guarantee the salvation of the base. Zheng Li wasn’t a person with no conscience, so he was also hoping for Zhao Hai’s good outcome.

However, he was left not knowing what to do at this time. The transmission formation wouldn’t function. He can only contact people from other places to see Base Number 5’s transmission formation underground. But Zheng Li knew that the success of this request was very unlikely. Now that a bug tide was happening underground, people already had their hands full. Fighting through the caves in order to reach Base Number 5’s formation was almost impossible.

Time passed by, and in a blink of an eye eight hours went past. Ma Rulong didn’t leave the transmission formation and continued to wait. And as time passed, the more and more convinced he was that the formation was faulty.

Then at this time, the transmission formation suddenly flashed. Ma Rulong and Zheng Li  who had been waiting for a long time were stunned. Then they stared at the formation without blinking. This was a large formation that allowed the transfer of 300 people at a time. They wanted to see how many people would go through this formation.

When the light vanished, only a handful of people appeared on the platform. But upon seeing these people, Ma Rulong couldn’t help but laugh. And at the same time, Zheng Li relaxed. It was Zhao Hai’s group who appeared on the formation.

However, it didn’t take long before Ma Rulong gasped. This was because Zhao Hai and the others had flushed faces. It was as though they had been drinking. Ma Rulong quickly approached Zhao Hai and the others, followed by Zheng Li. When Zhao Hai and the others saw Ma Rulong, they immediately gave a salute.

Ma Rulong waved his hand, then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “How come you’re only back now? Did the formation experience some problems?”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare, then he said, “There’s nothing wrong about the formation. We saw the formation activate, but since the elimination round has a seven-day duration, we decided to wait the time out.”

Ma Rulong was shocked by this response, his head couldn’t help but turn dizzy. Then after some time he said, “You mean to say, you waited even though you saw the formation activate?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “If we returned before the proper time, then our points might not be calculated. Therefore, we waited in the formation before heading back.”

Ma Rulong looked at Zhao Hai blankly. But at this moment, Zheng Li opened his mouth and said, “Zhao Hai, did you meet the bug tide below?’

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “We did. We’re fighting them as we waited.”

As soon as he heard Zheng Li’s question, Zhao Hai knew that the people aboveground were already aware of the bug tide. This also explains why the transmission formation was activated in advance.

Hearing Zhao Hai’s reply, Ma Rulong sighed and said, “So the others weren’t able to hold on for long because they waited?”

Zhao Hai knew what Ma Rulong was talking about. He didn’t plan to hide anything so he shook his head and said, “That’s not it. The moment we arrived underground, we were suddenly assaulted by a horde of bugs. I fought my way out and then turned around to help them. However, who knew that Streep would claim that I had snatched their loot. He even allied with everyone and Li Chuchen to kill me. In the end, I had no choice but to kill them all. Team Leader, am I guilty of a crime?”

Ma Rulong and Zheng Li stared at Zhao Hai, then they looked at each other. Ma Rulong said, “You mean to tell me that besides your group, everyone else was killed by you? And Li Chuchen? Where’s Li Chuchen?”

Zhao Hai replied, “I killed him. Ever since I blocked his three swords, he has been holding a grudge against me. Before the elimination round began, he gave a piece of jade to Streep. So Streep delayed for time in order for Li Chuchen to arrive. Then they would kill me together. Unfortunately for them, they’re weaker than me. So I killed them.”

Zhao Hai’s tone made the event seem superficial, but Ma Rulong and Zheng Li were shocked by what he said. Li Chuchen was a pinnacle rookie of the Cultivation Realm. And now, Zhao Hai claimed to have killed him, and that he was weak.

Ma Rulong turned his head towards Xiong Li and the others. Then his gaze stopped at Lu Dingtian as he asked, “Lu Dingtian, is Zhao Hai telling the truth? Did he really kill Li Chuchen?”

Ma Rulong knew certain information about the participants, so he was very clear that even if Lu Dingtian was a man of few words, he was very honest and disliked lying. Therefore, Ma Rulong decided to ask Lu Dingtian.

Lu Dingtian just gave a nod and said, “Yes.” Nothing else. However, Ma Rulong knew from this response that Zhao Hai was indeed telling the truth.

Not only was Ma Rulong not angry, but instead he laughed and said, “That’s good. But Zhao Hai, how well did you do?”

This was what Ma Rulong cared the most. He already knew that the people from the other realms were receiving aid from their respective bases. However, this still meant that they had lost a lot due to the bug tide. Their results shouldn’t be that great. Even if you kill bugs, it still doesn’t guarantee that you would get their parts.

From Ma Rulong’s calculations, he reckons that the survivors this time only numbered about 300, probably less than that. This was the biggest loss that the World of Cultivation experienced in one instance.

Although the losses from this elimination round were large, Ma Rulong was still worried. From these 300 people, only 100 could proceed to the next segment of the competition. If Zhao Hai’s score was unsatisfactory, then his chance of entering the ranking tournament would be gone. Therefore, Ma Rulong was intent on knowing Zhao Hai’s result. He was afraid of Zhao Hai having less than the enough score needed.

Zhao Hai looked at Ma Rulong’s expression as he smiled and said, “Team Leader, rest assured. Entering the top 100 shouldn’t be an issue.” Hearing Zhao Hai, Ma Rulong let out a breath of relief. Then he turned to Xiong Li and the others and said, “How about the rest of you? It doesn’t matter if you don’t have great results, entering the top 300 of the competition is already a good achievement for the Machine Field.”

At this time, Zhao Hai chuckled and said, “Team Leader, you’re misunderstanding. I meant that all of us can reach top 100 no problem. Not just me.”

Ma Rulong stared, then his eyes widened as his gaze was frozen on Zhao Hai. It was only after Zheng Li coughed that Ma Rulong recovered. He looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Are you sure? All of you are really entering the top 100?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “We should. We had a great harvest. We even managed to destroy an entire population of eight-legged bugs. Although we cannot take their nest back, all of its bugs have been killed by us. After dividing the spoils, it should be enough.”

Ma Rulong immediately asked, “How many eight-legged bugs are there inside one nest?”

Zhao Hai thought about it and said, “It should be in the tens of thousands. I can only remember that there were a lot.”

Ma Rulong let out a long breath as he nodded and said, “Alright. Then that’s good. Head back and take a rest first. Someone will come here in order to record your scores. Captain Zheng Li, I wonder if you can let us see the results of the other realms? This way, we can see an exact number for the bottom line.”

Actually, Ma Rulong already had a faint idea of the exact number. After all, the Machine Field had its own information network. But just to be sure, he wanted to see the figure that Zheng Li got. However, Ma Rulong already knew that as long as Zhao Hai and the others could present 10 thousand bugs each, then it’s certain that they would enter the top 100.

Naturally, Zheng Li wouldn’t decline. It was impossible for this matter to be hidden, so he nodded and said, “Alright, then everyone, please come with me.”

Chapter 1246: The Current First: Suo Liancheng

Zheng Li led the group to his office and then he took out a piece of paper which showed the current ranking. The first place named Suo Liancheng had a score equivalent to turning in 13,000 eight-legged bugs.

This meant that Suo Liancheng handed over not only eight-legged bugs, but advanced-level bugs as well. Bugs at a higher level would be converted to its value comparable to the eight-legged bugs. For example, a flying bug was equivalent to three eight-legged bugs. This conversion rate has been decided by statistics.

When Zhao Hai saw the name Suo Liancheng, Laura and the others immediately pulled out relevant information about him. Suo Liancheng, the Cultivation Realm’s rank one. He’s a sword cultivator with the Cultivation Realm’s most famous sword sect as his background, the Ten Thousand Swords Sect!

It has been four years since he ascended in the Cultivation Realm. And in just four years, he was able to become a Foundation Establishment Cultivator from Qi Condensation. It can be said that his progress was impressively quick, making him the Ten Thousand Sword Sect’s favored newcomer.

At the same time, Cai’er pulled out Suo Liancheng’s battle records in the bug cave. Zhao Hai and the others had been flying in the caves, so the Space had recorded where they went. Also, Cai’er had been monitoring the bug tide, so she wasn’t able to look much into the records. But now that Zhao Hai was safe, Suo Liancheng’s records can be looked into.

Upon seeing Suo Liancheng’s performance in the cave system, Zhao Hai was somewhat surprised. He discovered that he was still underestimating the Cultivation Realm’s talents. They were worthy to be called geniuses. Being able to go on top amidst the innumerable numbers of Ascenders was a testament to their strength.

Suo Liancheng alone couldn’t kill more than 10 thousand eight-legged bugs, unless he had the help of the Undead. A single person couldn’t kill ten thousand eight-legged bugs in just seven days.

Suo Liancheng’s 13,000 eight-legged bugs score wasn’t gained from killing eight-legged bugs. Instead, this number was gained from converting his achievements in killing higher-level bugs.

Seeing the quantity, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but nod. He was only able to kill so many bugs because of the Undead. Suo Liancheng only had his sword yet he was able to achieve something comparable. This wasn’t easy to do. This caused Zhao Hai to be more careful regarding Suo Liancheng.

They also looked at the other ranking. The people in this lineup were as expected, all of them were from the Cultivation Realm. There was also Yi Shuihan, Jiang Tian, Qin Zhang, Yao Gan. Cai’er took their records and then sent it to Zhao Hai. All of these people were in the Cultivation Realm’s top ten rookies.

But after looking at the 9th place, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gawk. This was because this person wasn’t from the Cultivation Realm. This person was called Tu Mietan from the Demon Realm. He became the Demon Realm’s top participant using his Blood Demon Art. His strength was said to be extraordinary.

At this point, Zhao Hai already had some understanding about the World of Cultivation. The World of Cultivation’s Demon Realm was different than Zhao Hai imagined. He expected it to be the same as the lower realm’s Demon Realm. However, the World of Cultivation’s Demon Realm was actually a part of the Cultivation Realm, but its inhabitants practice Demonic Arts. Because of how many people used Demonic Arts there, it was called the Demon Realm.

The Cultivation Realm was mostly made up of orthodox cultivators. Although there were some evil cultivators here and there, these people wouldn’t wantonly exhibit their moves. This was because they knew that they would be hunted down if they were ever spotted.

But things were different in the Demon Realm. Almost all sects in the Demon Realm were Demonic Sects. What they cultivated there were true demonic arts. While the Cultivation Realm considers human materials as taboo, it was a normal ingredient in the Demon Realm. Take the Blood Demon Art that Tu Mietan practice, for example, it required a large amount of human blood to practice. In the place where Tu Mietan was cultivating, a large number of blood slaves were bred in captivity. These blood slaves would provide a constant supply of flesh and blood. It can be said that the Demonic Sects regard humans as draft animals, and once they were needed, they would be slaughtered. It was a cruel world.

Originally, the Demon Realm and the Cultivation Realm were one. During that time, the Cultivation Realm was divided into Orthodox Cultivators, Demon Cultivators, Beast Cultivators, Spirit cultivators, Elven cultivators, and others. However, a war occured that made the Elven Cultivators, Orthodox Cultivators, and Spirit Cultivators to regard Demon and Beast Cultivators as evil. Naturally, the Demon and Beast Cultivators retaliated, causing a war that changed the color of the heavens and the earth. The planets that had been destroyed by this war numbered several thousands. In the end, the Demon and Beast Cultivators couldn’t resist the attack of the other three, so they cooped up inside the Demon Realm and Beast Realm.

But at the same time, the alliance between the Spirit Cultivators, Orthodox Cultivators, and Elven Cultivators couldn’t last for long. Orthodox Cultivators were innately greedy. After expelling the Demon Cultivators and the Beast Cultivators, they wanted to monopolize the Cultivation Realm. Therefore, another war occurred between them and the Spirit and Elven Cultivators. Finally, the Elven Cultivators and Spirit Cultivators separated themselves from the Cultivation Realm. This left the Orthodox Cultivators with the richest lands in the entire World of Cultivation.

After the Cultivation Realm was divided, there was a long time where no communication was made. These groups had been badly hurt and they would need to recuperate. But since the Cultivation Realm had the best location and access to information, they were able to recover quickly. This advantage allowed them to suppress the other realms.

Since the Cultivation Realm had the upper hand, it’s natural that they wouldn’t allow the other realms to progress. Therefore, they would periodically suppress these realms. And since the other realms cannot unite for various reasons, they had always been on the defensive.

Meanwhile, the Machine Field wasn’t in this scene at all. Whether it was the Cultivation Realm or the other realms, none of them put any attention towards the Machine Field. From what they can see, the Machine Field was just a collection of unorthodox Cultivators. They simply didn’t pose much of a threat.

Now that Zhao Hai saw someone from the Demon Realm, he couldn’t help but gawk. He immediately asked Cai’er about Tu Mietan. Unfortunately, Cai’er didn’t know much about him. The information the Machine Field had was lacking in this region.

Upon looking at the limited amount of information, Zhao Hai gave up and looked further down the list. Then as he looked, Zhao Hai saw that experts from other realms were beginning to show in the top 20 spots. There were a couple people from the Demon Realm, Beast Realm, Spirit Realm, and there was even an Elf.

The number of bugs these people collected wasn’t small. Although their scores didn’t reach more than 10 thousand, several thousand was still an astonishing amount. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but nod his head. It seems like this beginner competition didn’t only host the Machine Field’s strongest rookies in many years, the other realms were also blessed with a talented generation. The top 100 ranking tournament should be very fun to see.

As Zhao Hai was looking down the list, Xiong Li and the others were doing the same. Everyone was talking in hushed tones. It seems like they were also surprised by the results.

At this time, footsteps were heard from a distance. Then a group of Cultivators walked in. These people wore badges that weren’t from Sects. However, this badge still gave them status. They were the tabulation committee of the Six Realm Beginner Competition. They are here to record Zhao Hai and the others’ results.

Seeing these people walk in, Ma Rulong immediately went forward to greet them. He gave a salute and said, “Ma Rulong has seen everyone. Are you here to record our scores?”

The group also returned Ma Rulong’s salute. Then their leader smiled and said, “We heard that Zhao Hai and the others had returned. So we immediately came to tally their score.”

Ma Rulong nodded and said, “Alright, then please.” Then he invited the committee. But since they had to inspect a large volume, they would perform the counting outside. This way, they won’t run out of space.

Everyone walked outside. Naturally, Zhao Hai and the others were among these people. When they reached a large field, they stopped. Then two people took out a book and a pen as they prepared to record the results.

Of course, there were better ways of recording such as computers or jade. However, people were always afraid of tampering. Therefore, they could only use this primitive method of recording. Once this session of recording ends, this book would be sealed. Moreover, what’s written in this book will be transmitted to different areas in real time. This would make sure that several copies would exist for reference.

Seeing that everything was prepared, Ma Rulong turned to Zhao Hai and the others and said, “Alright Little Hai, just take a step forward and take out your harvest.”

Zhao Hai nodded. However, he didn’t walk forward. Instead, he had Sun Fei go first. Sun Fei nodded and then took a step forward before taking out a huge pile of bugs. The tabulation committee looked at the mountain of bugs and couldn’t help but stare. They didn’t expect the Machine Field to be able to take out this many bugs.

The tabulation committee had inspected a lot of loot. Therefore, they could estimate the points just by looking at how big the pile was. Seeing the pile that Sun Fei took out, the committee members reckoned that it shouldn’t score less than 20 thousand points.

The committee members looked at each other and saw the surprise in their eyes. One must know that the current first place, Suo Liancheng, only had a score of 13 thousand. But now, Sun Fei actually took out a pile that valued more than 20 thousand. This far surpassed Suo Liancheng! How was this possible? Moreover, Sun Fei was from the Machine Field!

Chapter 1247: Taking The Top Six

Everyone in the World of Cultivation was aware of the Machine Field’s strength. Therefore, upon seeing someone from that realm taking out so many bugs, people from the tabulation committee couldn’t help but doubt what they were seeing.

One of the committee members looked at Sun Fei, then he said, “Do you own all of these bugs?”

Sun Fei smiled faintly and said, “Of course, everything is mine.” The person nodded. Then a group of people proceeded to count. They didn’t use their hands to sort through the pile but instead used their spiritual force. After some time, several people shouted out numbers. The numbers they shouted out were different. From what Zhao Hai can see, it seems like they divided their tasks. Someone was in charge of counting eight-legged bugs, then one was tasked with the flying mantis bugs, and so on. After adding all of their counts, then Sun Fei’s result would be seen.

The group was well-organized. After everyone had shouted their count, Sun Fei’s score was then declared to be 23 thousand.

Sun Fei crushed Suo Liancheng’s score by a whole 10 thousand points, securing his place in the top 100. However, Zhao Hai knew that Sun Fei didn’t take out every bug they managed to loot. After all, he was the one who told Sun Fei to do so. This was because these bug parts had great uses.

The most valuable part of the bugs was actually their skeleton. Although they were a type of bone, this exoskeleton had a lot of useful applications. These exoskeletons can be added to other medicinal ingredients in order to make pills. They could also be added to weapons in order to help with refining. In the Cultivation Realm, the bugs had now become an indispensable ingredient in various weapons and pills.

But since Fabio Planet was too far from the Machine Field, the realm wasn’t able to get their hands on any of these bug parts. Instead, they could only buy them from the Cultivation Realm at a high mark-up price. Because of this, Zhao Hai told Sun Fei to leave some bugs behind and only release enough to secure a top 100 spot.

Now, Sun Fei released enough bugs to make him top one. However, Zhao Hai didn’t care. To him, these bug parts weren’t very precious.

After the tabulation committee recorded Sun Fei’s result, they stored the bug parts and then waited for Li Kuangren to step forward. In the end, the bugs that he took out were a bit more than Sun Fei. He scored 24 thousand points.

Next was Dongfang Yu, gaining 25 thousand points. Lu Dingtian came next, scoring 26 thousand. And then Xiong Li scored 27 thousand. When Zhao Hai’s turn arrived, his score amounted to 30 thousand.

The committee members were stunned silly. When they saw Sun Fei’s large pile of harvest, they thought that Zhao Hai and the others pooled their loot so that Sun Fei could top the elimination round. However, when Li Kuangren took out bugs that scored more than Sun Fei, these committee members were visibly shaken. They began to ask what kind of elimination round this was. Why does the Machine Field hold such an overwhelming advantage? Then more and more bugs were released from Dongfang Yu and the others.

Also, these committee members could see that Zhao Hai and the others were carefully releasing their bugs to be just right next to each other. This made Zhao Hai the first placer of the elimination round. This caused the tabulation committee members to sigh at the sight of the Machine Field’s unity.

When Ma Rulong saw Zhao Hai and the others releasing so many bugs, his eyes couldn’t help but water in happiness. This was the most beautiful scene he had seen. The top six of the elimination round was fully taken over by the Machine Field. Others wouldn’t be able to believe it if he told them.

After the tabulation committee recorded the scores, the head turned to Zhao Hai and the others and said, “Congratulations for becoming the top six of the elimination round. After a period of time, your prize will be delivered. Please have a good rest and prepare for the tournament in five days.”

Then after giving everyone a salute, the committee left.

When the committee completely left, Ma Rulong immediately laughed. Then he went towards Zhao Hai and then grasped his shoulder as he said, “Little Hai, great, great. Hahaha. Too satisfying, too satisfying. This old man finally saw the Machine Field winning. Good good, let’s drink. We need to get drunk!”

Zhao Hai and the others smiled faintly. They had already expected this outcome, so they didn’t think that it was strange. Ma Rulong led them back to the courtyard. Now that most of the people who stayed here had died, the courtyard appeared more spacious.

Zhao Hai and the others sat down as Zhao Hai took out food and wine. He also took out a couple of crabs since they also invited Zheng Li.

As soon as Zheng Li entered the courtyard, he immediately saw the crabs. There were huge red crabs there, still smoking after being cooked. They also emitted a very good aroma that stimulated everyone’s appetite.

There were also several side dishes on the table as well as several bottles of liquor. Since these were taken out by Zhao Hai, they were naturally very good.

Seeing this situation, Zheng Li couldn’t help but stare. This was because you basically can’t see these things in the base. People from the Cultivation Realm rarely ate meals, they were used to using fasting pills to satiate their hunger.

Fasting pills were pills deliberately invented by the Cultivators. This pill could allow one to survive a few days without eating.

Most importantly, there’s a belief in the Cultivation Realm that eating ordinary food would leave behind toxins in the body and affect one’s cultivation. Although eating fasting pills would still leave toxins behind, it was much less compared to eating a full meal. Because of this, even if there were armor shops, weapon shops, beast skin shops, and even robot shops in the Cultivation Realm, it was very rare to see a restaurant. Almost all Cultivators take fasting pills, nobody would eat a meal.

Therefore, upon seeing the amount of food prepared, Zheng Li couldn’t help but stare. Then he smiled faintly and remembered that the Machine Field’s people would always eat meals. Seeing that Zhao Hai and the others were inviting him over, this meant that he was being considered as a friend. Although this meant that he would have to eat a meal, Zheng Li still felt happy.

While Zhao Hai and the others were busily celebrating, Ma Rulong was busy himself. Zhao Hai and the others thought that this get-together was just among them. However, they didn’t expect Ma Rulong to bring everyone to have a feast.

After knowing the results, the other team leaders were also jubilant. Although Streep and the others had died, this didn’t mean much to them. Compared to annihilating his fellow participants, Zhao Hai’s accomplishment was much more historic.

Zhao Hai and the others had taken the top six positions, this meant that they were now at the top 100 of the elimination round and would progress to the next stage. Even if they didn’t win and were knocked out in the first round, it didn’t matter. Just being able to snatch a place in the top 100 was enough for the Machine Field to celebrate. This was something that never happened before. This was a breakthrough for the realm.

Zhao Hai knew that they weren’t the only ones celebrating. The entire Machine Field was also in a festive mood. Even Margaret has been called over to celebrate with the family. The better Zhao Hai’s achievement was, the greater it would be for the family. At this point, the rise of the Ashley Family was inevitable.

Zhao Hai didn’t care much about these things. He knew that the higher the position of the Ashley Family, the better it would be for his future plans.

Since Ma Rulong called everyone over, Zhao Hai needed to take out a couple more crabs. He also took out liquor before asking Zheng Li and the others to sit at their table.

In this table was Ma Rulong, Zheng Li, and Zhao Hai’s group of six. Once everyone has sat down, Ma Rulong poured some liquor into his cup and then loudly cheered, “This is a historic day for the Machine Field. What a great day! Little Hai and the others have made history. They’re heroes of the realm. For the Machine Field’s heroes, cheer!”

Everyone cheered, “For the Machine Field’s heroes!” Zhao Hai can see the sincerity in everyone’s eyes. They were genuinely happy, even much happier than Zhao Hai and the others.

Zhao Hai didn’t understand much about the grievance between the Machine Field and the Cultivation Realm. After all, the time he ascended was short. And only a few people had firsthand experience with regards to the Cultivation Realm’s suppression of the Machine Field. But he knew that in the previous competitions, the Machine Field had always been at the bottom. Now that the situation has been turned over, it was no wonder why they were very happy.

People continued to drink liquor, largely because Ma Rulong kept offering toasts. The team leader was too happy. Seeing the liquor being consumed quickly, Zhao Hai didn’t say anything. Instead, he just took out more liquor to drink.

Zhao Hai took out liquor and people kept drinking it. Seeing that Zhao Hai had a large supply of drinks, everyone laughed with satisfaction.

What Zhao Hai took out was rice wine. It wasn’t too strong and could be drunk in huge gulps. If Zhao Hai took out his stronger liquor, then a few people would have already blacked out.

But while Zhao Hai was busily taking out liquor to drink, he failed to notice Zheng Li’s change of expression after taking a sip. This wasn’t because the taste was bad, it was actually the opposite. Zheng Li had a very thick concentration of qi in his body. Nevertheless, Zhao Hai’s liquor still made him drunk. This made him very interested in Zhao Hai’s liquor.

Zheng Li was used to drinking in the past. Although he was a Cultivation Realm native, his background was poor. His parents were commoners and he started his cultivation by being a Rogue Cultivator. The Cultivation Realm’s commoners would still eat and drink. And back when Zheng Li was a Rogue Cultivator, he also drank liquor. This was because Rogue Cultivators were too poor to buy fasting pills. In order to survive, they would have to eat meals and drink liquor from time to time.

Chapter 1248: Spirit Wine and Faith Power

A Cultivator’s cultivation is a process of developing human potential and letting the body utilize this potential. Therefore, it can be said that Cultivators were somewhat experts in the human body. Even if they can’t understand other people’s body, at least they can understand their own. And this understanding began in the Body Refining period.

Cultivators in the Body Refining period would mainly cultivate their bodies. They would need to practice to a certain degree before they could start Qi Condensation.

But in Body Refining, one must pay close attention to their bodies. This was because internal injuries incurred in this period would have a huge effect during Qi Condensation. Most Cultivators who suffered internal injuries during Body Refining would be stuck at Qi Condensation their entire lives.  And even if they reach Foundation Establishment, their path to Core Formation would be several times harder than most. Reaching Core Formation would be close to impossible.

Only after Core Formation could the strength of their gold core cleanse and heal their body of toxins and injures. But even then, a large amount of strength and resources would be needed.

Because of this, Cultivators always regard the Body Refining Stage as crucial. The Body Refining Stage is a process of exercising and understanding one’s own body. It was also the first realm of Cultivation and the most important one. This was because any development in this stage had a huge impact on later stages.

There were also Cultivators in the Body Refining period that would eat meals, Zheng Li was among these Cultivators. Naturally, he drank alcohol during that time. It was well known that whenever they eat meals and drink liquor, toxins will spread throughout the body. And they would have no way to clear them.

Only after reaching Qi Condensation, when they become richer, could they buy fasting pills and no longer eat meals. These toxins would become a hindrance in going through to Foundation Establishment and Core Formation.

Zheng Li was currently a Core Formation Cultivator. Since he slowly crawled towards this level from a very poor background, he knew clearly how toxins would affect the body. Even if these toxins can be removed by pills, this would still take some time to clear out.

However, after he drank the liquor, Zheng Li discovered that the liquor didn’t leave any toxins behind, nothing at all. Moreover, the liquor has a dense amount of spiritual qi. Although this spiritual qi couldn’t help Zheng Li with his cultivation, it still had little use.

This discovery surprised Zheng Li. For so many years, he looked for something that can be eaten without leaving toxins behind. Although he managed to find a few things, they were too few and too expensive, and were only enjoyed by higher-level members of Sects. Ordinary Cultivators haven’t even seen them, let alone consume.

There were also special liquors in the Cultivation Realm. These liquors were brewed using special herbs. This special liquor was named Spirit Wine. This spirit wine is free of toxins and would provide great benefits to Cultivation. However, just like others of its type, it was very expensive.

Although the spiritual qi of Zhao Hai’s liquor was different in density compared to Spirit Wine, this liquor doesn’t leave behind toxins. In other words, Zhao Hai had an inferior version of spirit wine.

In order to Cultivate, Cultivators would need to control their desires and live a life of difficulty. They couldn’t eat nor drink and would only use fasting pills in order for their progress to be smooth.

But if there’s something that was delicious and would not leave toxins in the body, then the Cultivators would certainly welcome it with open arms. After all, Cultivators were still humans in the end. They also wanted to enjoy life from time to time.

Zheng Li looked at the bottle of wine with shining eyes. He hadn’t drank liquor for a long time that he had forgotten about how it tastes. The drink that Zhao Hai took out caused him to be excited. Drinking liquor without worrying about toxins was truly a great pleasure.

At this time, Zhao Hai finally noticed Zheng Li. Looking at Zheng Li’s expression, Zhao Hai was somewhat puzzled as he asked, “Mister Zheng, is there a problem? You don’t like it?”

Upon being asked by Zhao Hai, Zheng Li finally recovered. Then he looked at Zhao Hai with shining eyes as he asked, “Zhao Hai, this liquor, where did you get it?”

Seeing Zheng Li’s appearance, Zhao Hai knew that he was shaken from the liquor. This was the best liquor that the Space made, but Zhao Hai wasn’t planning on telling Zheng Li this. Judging by Zheng Li’s expression, it seems like this liquor was something important. This meant that it wouldn’t be good if its existence gets known by the Cultivation Realm. This was unnecessary trouble that Zhao Hai doesn’t want to see.

Zhao Hai was very clear that he was already eye-catching. If the Cultivation Realm finds something on him, then the troubles later would be problematic. Although this was only a guess, he wouldn’t dare make a gamble. Therefore, upon hearing Zheng Li’s question, he immediately smiled and said, “This liquor, it’s a long story. I brought this wine from the lower realms. Back then, I was able to discover a strange piece of rice paddy. The rice planted there turned out to be golden, and it also exuded a unique fragrance. Due to curiosity, I took them and made it into wine. I must say, this liquor is very good. I drank a lot of it in the lower realms. Because of this wine, I quickly advanced through my cultivation. But now that the density of spiritual qi is very thick, the liquor could no longer be used. Also, I only have a few bottles of it left. I’m saving them for happy events like this.”

Zhao Hai retold the story with a pained expression. However, upon seeing Zhao Hai’s acting, Xiong Li and the others couldn’t help but laugh inwardly. They knew that Zhao Hai was clearly lying. Although they didn’t know why Zhao Hai lied, upon seeing Zheng Li’s serious expression, they had a faint guess about what was going on.

The others cooperated with Zhao Hai’s acting, albeit they were all finding the situation amusing. Although the wine that Zhao Hai took out was a bit stronger than most liquors, it wasn’t outrageously strong. What Zhao Hai said was completely nonsense.

However, Zheng Li actually believed Zhao Hai’s nonsense. This was because Zheng Li knew that it was impossible to mass produce this liquor. The Cultivation Realm looked for ways to produce these types of things for countless years, so it was impossible for Zhao Hai to do it alone. Meanwhile, treasures could still be found in the lower realms. If he found those grains of rice in the lower realms, then he might also make wine just like Zhao Hai did.

Moreover, this also explained why Zhao Hai was able to skyrocket in strength upon ascending. The properties of the wine was enough to explain it.

With this thought in mind, Zheng Li couldn’t help but feel it was unfortunate. He nodded and said, “It’s a nice wine, very good. I hoped that you had a lot in hand so that I can ask for some. It’s a pity that you don’t have much left.”

Zhao Hai gave a slight smile as he said, “It’s truly a pity. But the Cultivation Realm has a lot of treasures, why would you care about this wine?”

Hearing Zhao Hai, Zheng Li gave a bitter smile as he replied, “The Cultivation Realm indeed has a lot of treasures, but these treasures are greatly divided among a lot of groups. People like me would be courting death if I desired for them.”

Ma Rulong chuckled and said, “A lot of people envying the Cultivation Realm have no idea about the state you’re in. They imagined that the Cultivation Realm had treasures growing everywhere. They wouldn’t expect that the competition here is much more brutal than back in the Machine Field.”

Zheng Li sighed and said, “That’s correct. I am a Rogue Cultivator. I only came to Fabio Planet because the resources allocated here by large sects are enough to support my Cultivation. Of course, this is because Fabio Planet is very dangerous. It’s considered a miracle that I was able to progress from Qi Condensation to Core Formation in this place.”

Zhao Hai and the others didn’t know what to say. And to be honest, they didn’t know how to respond. They know so little about the Cultivation Realm’s situation. The articles they read have a lot of false information. Therefore, they had no opinion about this matter.

Zheng Li looked at Zhao Hai and his brothers, then he smiled bitterly and said, “Ascenders like you are very lucky if you ascended in the Cultivation Realm. As long as you’re young, Large Sects would train you. Being able to ascend is already enough evidence that you’re talented. But for natives like me, if we want to get out of our commoner status and make our families live better lives, then the only thing we could do is work hard. The stronger we become, the better lives our families will experience. Therefore, for our families, Rogue Cultivators go all out. This is also the reason why I decided to take a gamble on Fabio Planet.”

Zhao Hai and his brothers looked at each other. They didn’t know what to say. In the Machine Field, Ascenders were being discriminated against. A lot of Machine Field natives took a disliking to them. But who would’ve thought that the Cultivation Realm looked at Ascenders as better than natives. In this realm, commoner natives were those who weren’t born into Sects.

It can be said that people in the Cultivation Realm were divided into three levels. The first level had descendants of Great Sects. These people were family members of sect members and had been raised with medicinal pills. Once they grew up, they would practice unique Cultivation Methods and would have access to numerous arts. They would also hold important positions in sects once they grow up. These were nobles of the Cultivation Realm, the top echelon.

The second level were Ascenders. Ascenders were talents from the lower realms. Due to their assured talent, sects would look for them and then enrol them into the sect. They could also become part of the top echelon of the realm. Ascenders were like Knights or Noble Lords. They might not belong to the noble class, but they held status higher than commoners. And they were also able to join the Noble group.

As for the third level, they were the commoners. They were peasants that were workhorses for the upper class. Only after a family member becomes a Cultivator would their situation improve.

Zheng Li looked at Zhao Hai and the others and smiled as he said, “I’m also aware of the Machine Field’s situation. To be honest, I wished for my family to live there. At least the position of natives there is very high. But in the Cultivation Realm, commoners are slaves that Great Sects collect Faith Power from.”

Upon hearing the latter part of Zheng Li’s statement, Zhao Hai’s interest was piqued. This was because he had long been curious about Faith Power. The Cultivation Realm’s collection of Faith Power even reached the lower realms. It was very clear that Faith Power was very important for Cultivators.

Zhao Hai already had a lot of races in the Space that treated him as a deity. They could provide Zhao Hai with Faith Power, but Zhao Hai was ignorant about it. The nature of Faith Power, and how to collect it, Zhao Hai had no idea. Now that Zheng Li mentioned this matter, he couldn’t help but be interested. He quickly asked, “Mister Zheng, what is Faith Power? What is it used for?”

Zheng Li smiled faintly and said, “This Faith Power is a kind of sentiment produced from the heart. Everyone has this power, even commoners. As long as you truly believe in a god, then they would get your Faith Power. The strength of Faith Power heavily depended on one’s heart. The more firm the belief, the more powerful Faith Power would be. As for the uses of Faith Power, there are multiple. From controlling artifacts to causing pressure to the enemy, Faith Power can be used almost everywhere.”

Zhao Hai had the look of interest in his face as he asked, “Then how can this Faith Power be collected? It seems to be something intangible. If it cannot be felt, then how can it be gained?”

Zheng Li smiled and said, “There are many ways to collect Faith Power. But a combination of Cultivation Method and Formations is required. Methods of collecting Faith Power is a huge secret of the Great Sects. Even if you’re a core disciple, it cannot be assured that you can get your hands on it. I only heard about it from rumors.”

Chapter 1249: We Are Friends

Although Zhao Hai was somewhat disappointed by what Zheng Li said, he didn’t let it show nor did he ask more. He knew that if he inquired too heavily on this subject, then people would be suspicious. The experts in the World of Cultivation are as common as clouds, he needed to tread carefully in these waters.

But at the same time, Zheng Li’s words enlightened Zhao Hai. If he wanted to know how to use Faith Power, then he needed to find core members of Sects and get the method from them. Otherwise, he wouldn’t be able to use Faith Power.

From what Zheng Li said, this Faith Power was a very good thing and it had many uses. Even if Zhao Hai has access to a large amount of Faith Power, he doesn’t have any means to make use of it. This was equivalent to having a gold ore deposit but not having the necessary tools to mine it.

The group didn’t discuss the subject further, Ma Rulong and the others were simply not interested. Zheng Li couldn’t care about it either, so the group quickly lost interest and then moved on to another topic.

After drinking two glasses of liquor, Zhao Hai looked at Zheng Li as he smiled faintly and said, “Mister Zheng, how long will you keep staying in Fabio Planet? Do you intend to stay here all the time?”

Zheng Li shook his head and said, “I won’t be staying here for long. I only stayed in Fabio Planet because I was provided a pill to reach Core Formation by the Great Sects. In exchange, I’ll stay in Fabio Planet for three years. I’m already approaching the end of my term. In a few months, I can leave Fabio Planet and be free. With my Core Formation stage, as well as my experience in Fabio Planet, I could become an elder in a sect. This will allow my family to leave the commoner life and officially enter a sect.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Being able to know Mister Zheng today is fate. How about we become friends? I don’t know if I have the honor to be one of yours?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, everyone turned to Zheng Li, including Ma Rulong. This was because this proposition was quite important to them.

For the Machine Field, Core Formation Cultivators were extraordinary existences. And even in the Cultivation Realm, these people were considered to be minor experts. Such people generally placed among the upper half of the cultivation food chain. There were a lot of Core Formation Cultivators that wouldn’t even look at people from the Machine Field. It was as if they would lose their status if they look at people from the realm. It can be said that Zhao Hai’s proposal was a bit ambitious.

When Zheng Li saw Ma Rulong and the others looking at him anxiously, he couldn’t help but find it funny. He grew up in the Cultivation Realm so he knew how Cultivators see people from the Machine Field. Even commoners of the Cultivation Realm look down on the Machine Field. If Zhao Hai’s proposal was heard by other Cultivators, then it’s quite normal for them to be angry on the spot.

However, Zheng Li wasn’t an ordinary person. He clawed his way up from a Rogue Cultivator to where he is now. He knew clearly that commoner life in the Machine Field was much better than in the Cultivation Realm. Moreover, people from the Machine Field weren’t any worse than in the Cultivation Realm when it came to attitude. And since Zhao Hai had saved his life before, Zheng Li always had a sense of gratefulness towards Zhao Hai.

Zheng Li wasn’t an ungrateful man, so when he heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but laugh a bit as he said, “Aren’t we already friends? If chance permits, we should drink more in the future.”

Upon hearing Zheng Li, Ma Rulong’s eyes shone while a smile also bloomed on Zhao Hai’s face. He laughed and then held up his glass as he said, “Alright, then let me offer this glass to Brother Zheng. “ Zhao Hai has already changed how he addressed Zheng Li from ‘Mister Zheng’ to ‘Brother Zheng’.

Zheng Li didn’t oppose, he also lifted his glass up and said, “This Zheng Li is honored to be your friend. Cheers!” Then the two clinked their glasses together before downing it down. Then they laughed.

The others in the courtyard felt the atmosphere and couldn’t help but laugh as well. Then the party reached its highest peak for some time.

While everyone was happily celebrating in the courtyard, other places didn’t share the same atmosphere. The bug tide that happened underground caused all realms to lose a lot. And at the same time, nobody thought that Suo Liancheng who scored 13 thousand would be knocked out from first place.

When everyone heard that the Machine Field’s participants had yet to return, they thought that they had all been annihilated. But as it turns out, six people survived and they all took the first six spots, pushing Suo Liancheng to seventh place. This was completely unexpected. Only a few people were calm, this included Suo Liancheng. He was now more certain that it was Zhao Hai who killed the five Cultivators from the Three Mountains Alliance.

Suo Liancheng was currently in his own courtyard, gently cleaning his golden sword. This golden sword was a special item only given to inner sect disciples. It was fast and had strong offensive strength. Using it alongside Ten Thousand Sword Sect’s Returning to Origin art made it an ultimate weapon. Sect disciples of the Ten Thousand Sword Sect used this sword to carve the name of the sect into the minds of the Cultivation Realm’s people. After Suo Liancheng joined Ten Thousand Sword Sect, he was quickly taken as an inner disciple and was given this golden sword to use. Seeing it as his responsibility to take care of it, Suo Liancheng would always take the time to clean it during his free time.

As his hand moved, Suo Liancheng’s heart calmed down. He was now more curious about Zhao Hai. The first time he got ahold of Zhao Hai’s information, he initially thought that it was fake. How could such a genius appear in the Machine Field? The information was certainly tampered with.

To be honest, Suo Liancheng didn’t care much that Zhao Hai had kicked him out of first place in the elimination round. Nor did he care about Zhao Hai killing other Cultivators. The Cultivation Realm was a cruel world. In this realm, life and death was as common as grass. If you stopped progressing, if your method wasn’t high enough, then you would die a dog’s death. What Suo Liancheng was anticipating right now was meeting Zhao Hai in the ranking tournament.

At this time, the gate to the courtyard was pushed open. A middle-aged person walked in. This person was wearing black clothing and had a longsword at his back. From what can be seen, the sword seems to be gold as well.

Suo Liancheng looked at the man and immediately stood up and gave his greeting, “Elder.”

The man nodded, then sat beside Suo Liancheng. He waved his hand and urged Suo Liancheng to sit down as well. The Elder looked at Suo Liancheng and said, “The Machine Field’s matter, do you know about it?”

Suo Liancheng sheathed his sword, then he nodded and said, “I do. They occupied the top six positions. How could I not know?”

The Elder nodded and then said, “Do you think there’s foul play involved?” Naturally, the Elder was very suspicious about the Machine Field.

Suo Liancheng shook his head and said, “I’m afraid that’s not the case. The Machine Field gained an extraordinary genius this time, Zhao Hai. I didn’t tell Elder of this before, but while I was underground, I ran across traces of a fight between two groups of people. All signs indicate that it was Zhao Hai fighting against the five people from the Three Mountains Alliance. Since those five didn’t come back, then this meant that Zhao Hai killed them. And since Zhao Hai can kill the five of them, then it’s natural for him to kill a lot of bugs. Also, it’s not impossible for him to divide his spoils among the others from the Machine Field. But things will be clear during the ranking tournament. If the other people from the Machine Field surrender immediately, then it’s Zhao Hai who gave them their bugs. But if they don’t, then this means that the Machine Field has somehow managed to produce six monsters.”

As soon as the elder heard Suo Liancheng, his eyebrows couldn’t help but furrow. Then with a surprised tone he asked, “Really? Something like that happened? Those five kids from the Three Mountains Alliance have the Five Element Formation. If Zhao Hai can kill them, then he’s certainly strong.”

Suo Liancheng nodded and said, “It’s not just the five people from the Three Mountains Alliance. I don’t know if Elder has already noticed, but someone has yet to come back. And that person has the capabilities to survive the elimination round.”

As soon as the elder heard this, his eyes lit up and then he said, “Li Chuchen?”

Su Liancheng nodded and said, “Right, Li Chuchen. Li Chuchen isn’t weak and he could handle killing bugs. But just as we entered the caves, he seemed to be anxious in heading towards a certain direction. It was as if he had somewhere to go. Li Chuchen had contact with the Machine Field’s Water Temple before his face was slapped by Zhao Hai. It’s possible that he gave someone from the Water Temple a way to track Zhao Hai. But unfortunately for him, he underestimated his enemy.”

The Elder nodded and said, “That’s highly probable. If that’s the case, then Zhao Hai is going to be a great rival. You need to be careful when you face him. But since he offended the Three Mountains Alliance as well as Extreme Cold City, I reckon he won’t be able to live long.”

After hearing this, Suo Liancheng shook his head and said, “I don’t think that will happen. Zhao Hai is very formidable. He was able to drive back a silverback gold-winged bug back in Base Number 5. At that time, everyone thought that he used a potion to increase his strength. But from how things stand right now, it seems like that’s not the case. Moreover, when he fought with the five from the Three Mountains Alliance, I felt the aura of a Nascent Soul Expert. This should be Mu Dan using a jade talisman to call an ancestor over. Zhao Hai was able to destroy the ancestor’s avatar, this shows that he is very strong.”

The Elder knit his brow and said, “Even a jade talisman is used? Then it seems like Zhao Hai is really difficult to deal with. Is there going to be a problem in the ranking competition?”

Suo Liancheng naturally knew that the Elder was referring to Zhao Hai. If Zhao Hai’s strength was really that great, then this tournament’s champion would be none other than him.

Suo Liancheng raised his eyebrows, then his fighting spirit rose as he softly chuckled and said, “I’m just looking forward to facing him. I hope that he won’t disappoint me.”

Seeing Suo Liancheng’s expression, the Elder gave a smiling nod. Sword Cultivators want nothing more than a good challenge!

Chapter 1250: Collection and Usage of Faith Power

Sword Cultivators were a special group among the Cultivators. It was well known that Cultivators used a lot of means during battles. Each one of them would have several artifacts in hand at all times. It’s even possible for them to take out ten artifacts during combat. And this was in addition to spells, paper talismans, and other special items. There’s also items to help with defense. These methods would number from the dozens and even to the hundreds.

But Sword Cultivators were the opposite. Sword Cultivators honed their skills to be one with the sword. They hardly study spells nor do they use other magic artifacts. Their weapon was only one, and that is the sword!

Sword Cultivators live by their swords and cherish them as though it was their second body. They train themselves to treat their swords as though it was their hand or foot. They even regard the sword’s spirit during practice. This made the attacks of Sword Cultivators the strongest in the Cultivation Realm. Foundation Stage Sword Cultivators could even contend against normal Core Formation Cultivators. This was because they concentrated their efforts in honing their sword skills.

Sword Cultivators weren’t only known for their attacks, they were also known for being akin to swords in their personal lives. Normally, they would be like sheathed swords, with a sharpness that was hidden beneath. But when they faced their enemies, they would release an imposing aura that was like a sword being taken out of its scabbard.

A Sword Cultivator’s spirit was the same as their swords, sharp. Once taken out, it would hurt people. But if a Sword Cultivator loses their drive, they would turn into rusted swords, useless and unable to cut.

Therefore, upon hearing that Suo Liancheng was looking forward to meeting Zhao Hai, the Elder was glad. Sword Cultivators needed this sharpness. Even if the enemy was powerful, a Sword Cultivator still needs to face them with their swords. Either way, they would win heroically, or have a glorious defeat. This is a Sword Cultivator.

The Elder nodded and said, “Very good. Take some rest and prepare yourself. Other people in the tournament will be hard to deal with, especially Tu Mietan. He’s known to be very suitable for his Demonic Art. If you run into him, make sure to be very alert.”

Suo Liancheng nodded. Then the Elder stood up and left. Suo Liancheng escorted the Elder out of the courtyard before going back to his table. Then he caressed his sword as though he was caressing a lover.

Suo Liancheng didn’t care about what the Elder said about Tu Mietan. His current goal was Zhao Hai, he couldn’t care less about someone from the Demon Realm.

Suo Liancheng was akin to a mountaineer. His goal was a tall mountain, so why would he care about a small hill?

Just like Suo Liancheng, Yi Shuihan, and the others, there’s also another person who paid great attention towards Zhao Hai. This person was the Demon Realm’s first newcomer, Tu Mietan.

Tu Mietan was the Demon Realm’s most talented genius in the last hundred years. He ascended to the Demon Realm four years ago and smoothly progressed to Foundation Establishment. In this Six Realm Beginner Competition, he entered as the Demon Realm’s qualifier champion. Moreover, he managed to enter the top ten in the elimination round.

However, who would’ve thought that his time in the top ten wouldn’t be long. He was kicked out soon after, and it was done by the Machine Field. Upon hearing this information, Tu Mietan found it hard to believe. But after seeing the official rankings change, he had no choice but to accept it.

Tu Mietan initially didn’t have any interest towards the Machine Field. However, after seeing the results of the elimination round, he immediately looked for information regarding the realm and its participants. It was then that he discovered that this change in the Machine Field was hinged on a single person, and this person was Zhao Hai.

Tu Mietan slowly put down the information in his hand, then he smiled faintly and said, “Zhao Hai? Interesting. He actually appeared in a barren place like the Machine Field.”

At this time, Zhao Hai and the others had just finished celebrating and Zhao Hai had already returned to the Space. Laura and the others were monitoring the situation of other participants through the monitor. They used the past few days to gain the ability to monitor the other bases. Because of this, they now knew about the other realm participants.

Laura and the others saw the response of Suo Liancheng and Tu Mietan. Naturally, Zhao Hai was able to see them as well. Although he drank a lot of wine, he was no longer affected by it due to his current strength. And after returning to the Space, he also drank some water and immediately sobered up.

Upon listening to Suo Liancheng and the Ten Thousand Sword Sect’s Elder’s conversation, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh as he said, “Suo Liancheng is indeed the Cultivation Realm’s strongest newcomer. Hahaha, sure enough, I cannot underestimate the heroes of the Cultivation Realm.”

Laura nodded and said, “With only a small amount of information, Suo Liancheng was able to get the picture. This person can’t be underestimated. But Brother Hai, since they already know that Li Chuchen and Mu Dan’s group has been killed by you, will the Three Mountains Alliance and Extreme Cold City retaliate?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I’m sure that they’ll come to deal with me. But I don’t have to worry much about it. My current strength is equal to a Nascent Soul Cultivator. People on the same level as me can establish their own sects in the Cultivation Realm. Nascent Soul Cultivators are the Cultivation Realm’s core fighting strength. Sects would need to think about dealing with one. After all, if they fail to kill a Nascent Soul Cultivator, the consequences will be serious. I’ll reveal some of my strengths in the competition. This will make those people wary and buy us more time.”

Laura nodded and said, “With your present strength, you don’t need to be afraid of anything. But after the competition, we need to leave the Ashley Family. Otherwise, if they can’t deal with you, then they’ll deal with the family.”

Zhao Hai agreed, “I’ve also thought about that. But there’s no need to worry. Nothing should go wrong. It’s just a pity that Zheng Li doesn’t know how to collect Faith Power and also how to use it. It’s unfortunate.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Laura smiled faintly and said, “Brother Hai, did you forget Lu Wei? Since he can collect Faith Power in the lower realms, he definitely knows how to collect Faith Power as well as how to use it. I think you should continue being friends with Zheng Li. This way, when Zheng Li joins a sect and becomes an elder, you can ask for his help to pay attention to Lu Wei. As long as we get information about him, then we can take action. Not only can we get the method to obtain and use Faith Power, we can also eliminate one enemy.”

Zhao Hai’s eyes shone, he nodded and said, “Right, I forgot about him. Good, good. And having someone on our side in the Cultivation Realm will make it more convenient for us in the future. Fortunately, Zheng Li doesn’t have any ambitions anymore. He just wants his family to live a good life. But if he wants his family to live better, he would need to be stronger. With our support, his strength will increase faster. Alright, this idea is great.”

Laura smiled and said, “In the tournament, Brother Xiong Li and the others should admit defeat immediately. They don’t have the strength to deal with the other realms. It’s best if they don’t get injured.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I think Boss Xiong and the others already understand this. There should be no problem. They aren’t the kind of people who would risk their lives just to save face.”

At this time, Margaret said, “Brother Hai, what do you feel about Tu Mietan? Why does he feel strange? I feel repugnant just looking at him.”

Zhao Hai’s expression turned serious as he answered, “Tu Mietan practices the Blood Demon art. I heard that this method requires the blood of living people to cultivate. Because of this, he has an uncomfortable aura about him. He’s been demonized. Although he has the body of a human, his mind can no longer be considered as a person.”

Megan and the others were somewhat surprised. Such a Cultivation Method actually exists. Megan’s had a blanched face as she said, “Brother Hai, why would such people survive in this world? Why don’t the Cultivators kill people like him?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s because of how powerful Tu Mietan’s Sect is. The Sacred Blood Sect is one of the Demon Realm’s Great Sects. Even Great Sects in the Cultivation Realm wouldn’t dare claim that they could destroy the Sacred Blood Sect completely. Even if a sect is brave enough to attack the Sacred Blood Sect and win, it would be after suffering heavy losses. Therefore, sects can only turn a blind eye to this situation. Also, using living people is quite a common method in the Demon Realm. The Cultivation Realm alone wouldn’t be able to stop them.”

Megan coldly snorted and said, “Those Cultivators are really hateful.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Forget about Tu Mietan for now. We don’t have any means to do anything about it. We have already offended the Three Mountain Alliance and Extreme Cold City. We also have Lu Wei, Spirit Wind Moon Emperor, and the Myriad Treasures Pavilion as enemies. It wouldn’t be wise for us to provoke the Demon Realm. Most importantly, the Cultivation Realm and the Demon Realm have different temperaments. The Cultivators wouldn’t pursue us immediately. Meanwhile, the Demon Realm’s people are lunatics. It’s possible that they’ll use all of their power to deal with us. If that happens, then we would have great troubles in the future.”

Megan nodded, she didn’t say anything more. Naturally, she was aware of Zhao Hai’s situation. Zhao Hai’s Nascent Soul-level strength might be strong, but compared to the entirety of the World of Cultivation, he was still nothing. Nascent Soul Experts dying in battle is very common here. Even if Zhao Hai has the Space and could survive almost anything, being chased down wasn’t ideal. Therefore, he could only hold back for now and give the Sacred Blood Sect more time.

However, Megan also believed that as long as Zhao Hai has the strength, then he’ll certainly deal with the Sacred Blood Sect. This was because if Zhao Hai couldn’t allow slavery, then the more he wouldn’t allow people being treated as livestock and draft animals.

Chapter 1251: Seeking Revenge

Although Zhao Hai has a sense of justice, he wasn’t a saint. It was also impossible for him to be saintly all the time. However, when important matters were involved, Zhao Hai can follow his own conscience.

After being educated for many years back on Earth, Zhao Hai was used to the idea that everyone was born equal. This idea has taken root deep inside Zhao Hai’s mind. And this ideology was also what connected Zhao Hai back to Earth.

Because of this, how could Zhao Hai possible acknowledge the existence of slavery? He had abolished slavery back in the lower realm. And in the World of Cultivation, human farms existed. So Zhao Hai needed to take care of it.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t an ordinary man. Before he makes any move, he would have to consider the possibility of success and failure. If he wanted to help others, then he would have to see to it first that he has the ability. Wanting to help end world hunger while you’re poor was useless. These words were what Zhao Hai thought about the most.

…………..

The ranking tournament for the competition was about to begin. Zhao Hai and the others were also leaving Fabio Planet since the tournament would be held in the Cultivation Realm’s Void Arena.

The Void Arena was a special place in the Cultivation Realm. The Void Arena was in a meteorite field. However, there were no dangers in that particular field. The Void Arena was the largest meteorite in that region. Cultivation Realm’s almighty beings were unable to replicate an arena as large as it. On the side of this huge meteorite were a lot of small meteorites orbiting and looking like they were floating on its surface. On these small floating meteorites were stands constructed for spectators. This allowed people to sit above the arena and see the situation below.

All previous newcomer tournaments were held in this arena. It had become a convention for the event. Naturally, this wouldn’t change this time.

Zhao Hai rested for the evening before preparing to leave Fabio Planet the next day. To be honest, upon hearing that they were leaving Fabio Planet, the team leaders were very glad. In their opinion, Fabio Planet was too dangerous. It would be better if they left it as soon as possible.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai and the others weren’t that anxious. They had seen so many bugs underground that they weren’t afraid of the bugs anymore.

After Zhao Hai got up in the morning, he knew that they would be leaving soon. Therefore, he immediately went out of his room and went straight to Zheng Li’s place. Laura already told him the day before to establish a good relationship with Zheng Li. This way, Zheng Li could help him pay attention to Lu Wei’s affairs. Naturally, since he was planning to deal with Lu Wei, he wouldn’t hold back.

When Zhao Hai arrived at Zheng Li’s courtyard, Zheng Li who was also heading out saw him. Zheng LI stared for a moment before he smiled and said, “Little Hai, you came. I initially wanted to see you off. I didn’t expect you to come here. Come over and take a seat.”

Zhao Hao nodded and then entered Zheng Li’s courtyard. Zheng Li’s place wasn’t very big. However, the entire courtyard belonged to him alone. Nobody could disturb him so it was very quiet.

Zheng Li was about to prepare some tea but Zhao Hai stopped him. Then Zhao Hai looked at Zheng Li and said, “Brother Zheng, we’re about to go soon so that we can prepare for the ranking tournament. Therefore, I came here to say goodbye.”

Zheng Li nodded, then he patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said, “Little Hai, I know that you are strong, and you can easily snatch the first place in the rankings. But you still need to be careful. You have offended Extreme Cold City as well as the Three Mountain Alliance. They would never let you go.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Brother Zheng, rest assured, I’m aware of it. Right, let me give this to you. With this, we can keep in touch even after I leave.”

As he said that, Zhao Hai handed a space ring to Zheng Li. Zhao Hai could make space rings whenever he wants at this point. Zhao Hai decided to give a space ring because this would incur the least suspicion. Zhao Hai had the Hundred Spirit Tree, whose fruits can be considered to be the best spatial items since one could plant things inside it. However, Zhao Hai cannot give Zheng Li a fruit. Therefore, Zhao Hai could only give Zheng Li a space ring, moreover, it was a space ring he gained as a spoil of battle.

Zheng Li scanned the ring upon receiving it and couldn’t help but stare. This was because there were three types of things inside the ring. The first type were various types of bug parts. There were piles upon piles of them. One must know that bug parts were still very profitable in the Cultivation Realm. This was akin to Zhao Hai giving him money.

The second type were liquors. This was the same liquor that they had drank last night. All in all, Zhao Hai gave 20 bottles.

The third type was actually a magic formation. It wasn’t a huge formation nor did Zheng Li know what it was used for. Upon retrieving his spiritual force, Zheng Li turned to look at Zhao Hai in confusion.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “These bugs are spoils that we got underground. I kept some for ourselves, I’ll give the rest to Brother Zheng. You will need a lot of money once you leave Fabio Planet. Although these things aren’t worth much, I hope that it will help you. As for the liquor, I can only give you this much. The magic formation is a small transmission formation which can only be used for communication. If Brother Zheng leaves this place, you can use it to contact me. At that time, we can drink together once more.”

When Zheng Li heard this, his eyes couldn’t help but turn red. People rarely made friends in the Cultivation Realm, especially Rogue Cultivators like Zheng Li. Of course, Zheng Li had friends in the past. But unfortunately, all of them failed to form a gold core and died. Since then, Zheng Li had nobody to call a friend.

Although what Zhao Hai gave him weren’t very precious, it was given with the sincerity of a friend. Zheng Li felt grateful. He received the space ring before he nodded and said, “Alright. Little Hai, your sentiment, I definitely won’t forget it. Once I leave Fabio Planet, I’ll contact you immediately.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, then it’s settled. Brother Zheng, I’m leaving.” Then he bowed towards Zheng Li and left the courtyard.

Zhao Hai didn’t return to their courtyard but instead to the transmission formation. Ma Rulong and the others were already waiting for him there.

Upon seeing Zhao Hai arrive, Ma Rulong nodded towards him. Zhao Hai made a salute towards Ma Rulong before standing alongside everyone.

Seeing about a dozen people in his team, Ma Rulong couldn’t help but feel heavy. When they first came here, they were a team of more than 100 people. But as soon as they reached Fabio Planet and encountered the bugs, they started having losses. And then after the elimination round, only Zhao Hai’s group of six were left. So how could he be in high spirits now?

Although the other participants were killed by Zhao Hai, Ma Rulong couldn’t blame him for it. He knew clearly that even if Zhao Hai didn’t kill them, they would still be surrounded by the bugs and be killed. Zhao Hai saved them but they actually wanted to kill Zhao Hai and take his spoils. It would be strange if Zhao Hai just stood there and accepted being bullied.

Ma Rulong sighed, then he waved his hand and said, “Let’s go.” Then everyone walked towards the transmission formation. As soon as everyone was in place, the formation lit up and everyone disappeared in a flash of light.

The transmission formation in Seamount City lit up with light before Zhao Hai and the others appeared on it. Ma Rulong waved his hand as the group headed towards the Machine Field’s courtyard. This was where they stayed before, so Zhao Hai and the others already knew the way.

What’s different this time was that nobody came to embarrass them. Conversely, the Cultivators around them were looking at them with mixed expressions of confusion and dread.

Zhao Hai’s achievements had already spread to several circles. Faced with such achievements, the entire World of Cultivation was shocked. Nobody could believe it, however it was true.

As soon as the Cultivators saw the Machine Field overwhelming them in the rankings, they couldn’t help but feel that this was a joke. But when they finally confirmed the idea, they felt that they were about to go insane. They couldn’t believe it. This prompted them to get information about Zhao Hai.

Information about Zhao Hai wasn’t difficult to find and before long someone had their hands on it. It was then that the Cultivation Realm knew about how much of a genius Zhao Hai was. And he was even able to fight a silverback gold-winged bug single-handedly. Upon hearing this, everyone was dumbfounded.

Silverback gold-winged bugs were very strong bugs. This was something that almost everyone knew in the Cultivation Realm. This was because legends about these bugs would often spread to the populace. It was said that a single silverback gold-winged bug could contend against two Nascent Soul Experts. Since Zhao Hai was able to drive one of these bugs out, then how strong was he? Does this mean that he can also fight two Nascent Soul Experts?

With this thought in mind, the Cultivators couldn’t help but behave. The Cultivation Realm worshipped strength above all. They also knew that some people cannot be annoyed. Naturally, Zhao Hai has been included into the group that shouldn’t be offended.

Therefore, Zhao Hai and the others wouldn’t experience any more trouble. It was also because of this that the Seamount Faction stopped their aggression. They wouldn’t dare embarrass Zhao Hai, especially after knowing about his strength.

Although the Seamount Faction was a sect, their current strongest member was at Core Formation Stage. Just like any other small sect, they wouldn’t dare think about offending someone who can fight a silverback gold-winged bug alone.

There were a lot of small sects in the Cultivation Realm where their strongest experts are at Core Formation. They lived their lives cautiously. They were afraid of offending existences that could destroy their sects.

Xiong Li and the others were initially surprised about this. They heard that only Nascent Soul Experts were allowed to establish sects in the Cultivation Realm. So why do these small sects have Core Formation experts as their strongest member?

But after some thinking, they finally understood. They learned that these sects were indeed established by Nascent Soul Experts. But after a long time, these Nascent Soul Experts had either entered a long seclusion or had died. Because of this, the strongest members of the sect became these Core Formation Cultivators. This was the case with the Seamount Faction.

So after Zhao Hai and the others appeared on the transmission formation, the Seamount Faction’s people didn’t make things hard for them. These people knew that if they offended Zhao Hai’s group, then Zhao Hai might deal with them.

From the Seamount Faction’s perspective, Zhao Hai didn’t deal with them before because he wanted to preserve his strength and hide it. This way, people wouldn’t be able to know how strong he was. But now that everyone knows his strength, there’s no need for Zhao Hai to hold back. If the Seamount Faction messes with Zhao Hai, then there’s no stopping him from attacking the sect.

When Zhao Hai and the others returned to their courtyard, they discovered that it was different compared to before. The decorations of the courtyard before were very simple, appearing very low key. But now, it seems like the courtyard had undergone a massive renovation. The interior decorations seemed very new. The signage outside the courtyard was also replaced with a much larger one. The words “Machine Field Institute” were clearly marked on top of the entrance.

In front of the courtyard were two robots. Just as Ma Rulong approached, the two robots bowed and said, “Team Leader Ma, welcome back.” Ma Rulong nodded and then walked in.

The courtyard looked cleaner compared to before. Inside were the two Mages from before. Seeing Ma Rulong’s group coming in, they immediately offered their greetings. The two bowed and said, “Congratulations Team Leader Ma for the victorious return.”

Ma Rulong looked at the two, then he nodded and waved his hand as he said, “Alright, arrange rooms for us. We need to rest.” The two complied and immediately took care of things.

Then at this time, someone suddenly called out, “Zhao Hai, come out and face your death!” As this voice was heard, a person’s shadow was seen approaching from a distant place. This development caused Ma Rulong and the others to stare.

Zhao Hai was also surprised. Then Laura immediately sent over some information. The declaration came from a middle-aged person. The person wore black clothing. Although he was handsome, his face was twisted as though he hadn’t eaten for some time.

Zhao Hai stared, this was because he didn’t know what this person was diong. Although he was confused, he didn’t say anything. The person approached the courtyard and appeared above the institute. Zhao Hai stared at the person and said, “This one is Zhao Hai. Friend, did I offend you?”

The person stopped a hundred meters in front of Zhao Hai. Then he coldly replied, “You’re Zhao Hai?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Correct, I am Zhao Hai. What deep enmity do we have for you to hate me this much?”

The person looked at Zhao Hai and then sneered and said, “You’re really worthy of being ignorant folk. You’re still clueless despite killing my people. Listen, this one is from the Three Mountains Alliance, Jade Mountain’s Inner Elder Helian Da. Dong Tutian who you killed is my disciple!”

Chapter 1252: A Shallow Purpose For Revenge

When Zhao Hai saw Helian Da, he knew that he came here for revenge. However, he didn’t know for whom he was seeking revenge.

Zhao Hai replied, “So it’s Elder Helian. Dong Tutian was indeed killed by me. But this is because he was going to grab my prey. Moreover, he’ll kill me either way, so I can only make the first move. Also, Elder Helian shouldn’t forget that during the Six Realm Beginner Competition, the contestants are protected.”

Helian Da laughed and said, “Protected? Who would protect you? You country bumpkins. Do you really think that the Cultivation Realm will protect you? Stop dreaming. You’ll die today.”

Zhao Hai looked at Helian Da, then he smiled and said, “Speaking of which, if I kill you, then I’ll be chased by Jade Mountain. But if you kill me, nothing will happen. Isn’t this a bit unfair?”

Helian Da laughed and said, “Fair? You dare talk fairness with me? Let me tell you this, in the Cultivation Realm, strength is fairness. Only strong people have the qualifications to demand fairness.”

Zhao Hai looked at Helian Da with a strange look, then he said, “Why are you so confident of being able to deal with me? I really want to know where your confidence is from.”

Helian Da sneered and said, “You don’t know the immensity of the heavens and the earth. Don’t think that you have the strength to talk equally with us Cultivators. Zhao Hai, since you’re ignorant about the Cultivation Realm, then I’ll make sure to educate you today.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Then I’ll gladly accept it. Let’s head out of the city, we don’t want to destroy things here.” Then he turned around and left the city with Ma Rulong and the others following behind him.

Although Ma Rulong’s strength was equivalent to the Cultivation Realm’s Core Formation experts, this was only in terms of spiritual qi density in his body. His combat prowess was still less than Helian Da. Cultivators of the Cultivation Realm had too many means to use in battle that the Machine Field had yet to learn.

Helian Da coldly snorted and then followed Zhao Hai out of the city. Although he blatantly declared revenge on Zhao Hai, he still needed to consider the Seamount Faction’s face. Of course, Helian Da wasn’t afraid of the Seamount Faction, after all it was just a small sect. The reason why he doesn’t want to offend the Seamount Faction was because doing so would invite a lot of troubles coming his way.

The Cultivation Realm wasn’t a peaceful place. A lot of small sects had been devoured by bigger sects. Because of this, small sects had found ways to continue surviving. The first method was alliances while the other was becoming vassal sects.

The method of alliance is very easy to explain. Some small sects would unite and work with each other. Although the scale of these alliances wasn’t big, their unity was still something that cannot be looked down upon.

On the other hand, sects that wanted to be vassals would profess their allegiance towards a nearby great sect. Once they submit, they would deliver tribute every year in exchange for protection from these great sects. It was the same as a Kingdom having vassal states.

Even if Helian Da wasn’t afraid of the Seamount Faction, he was wary of the Sect behind it. If he and Zhao Hai fought inside the city, it’s certain that they would cause huge damage to its infrastructure and population. This will end up damaging the Seamount Faction.

The people of the Cultivation Realm treated their face very seriously. If you give others face, then they would give you face as well. But if you don’t give face to others, then they might want to take your life. If Helian Da’s revenge causes Seamount Faction to lose out, then that would be akin to him slapping the Seamount Faction in the face. And there was no way for the Seamount Faction to just let this go.

Because of this, when Zhao Hai proposed that they fight outside the city, Helian Da agreed.

Also, Helian Da didn’t only look for Zhao Hai only for revenge. It was more about the Cultivation Realm suppressing the Machine Field once more. The Cultivation Realm does this to everyone around them, this event wasn’t anything special.

Zhao Hai and the others unexpectedly suppressed the Cultivation Realm in the elimination round. The Cultivation Realm doesn’t want to see such people who caused them shame. Regarding the Cultivation Realm that values face, suppression was the real reason of Helian De’s appearance, not revenge.

In the Cultivation Realm, the sentiment between Master and Disciple was very shallow. It’s impossible for Helian De to hunger for revenge just because his disciple Dong Tutian was killed. Dong Tutian wasn’t Helian De’s only disciple. Moreover, Dong Tutian wasn’t his most valued pupil. There definitely wasn’t any reason for Helian De to seek revenge.

Actually, Helian De was ordered this time to kill Zhao Hai. The Cultivation Realm’s people weren’t idiots. Conversely, each one of them were old villains. Upon analyzing the Machine Field’s result, they knew that everything was because of Zhao Hai. Therefore, they formulated this plan to deal with Zhao Hai. And Helian De was elected to be the executioner.

The people from the Cultivation Realm fully analyzed every report on Zhao Hai. However, they didn’t believe all of it. How could Zhao Hai, a rookie, be able to reach the strength of Nascent Soul just a year after ascending? This was absolutely impossible. In their opinion, it was more than enough to send a Core Formation Expert to deal with Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai soon arrived outside Seamount City. This was the same hill where Gongsun Zheng was killed. Zhao Hai and Helian Da stood a distance away from each other. Meanwhile, Ma Rulong and the others weren’t far away behind Zhao Hai. Ma Rulong’s expression was somewhat ugly.

But on the other hand, Xiong Li and the others had a nonchalant look on their faces. They believed that Zhao Hai would be able to easily defeat Helian Da. This was because they saw Zhao Hai fight against Mu Dan.

Ma Rulong also noticed Xiong Li and the others’ expression. They weren’t even paying attention to the situation. Instead they were chatting as though this wasn’t an important matter.

Ma Rulong flew beside Xiong Li and asked, “Aren’t you worried about Little Hai?”

Xiong Li looked at Ma Rulong. He didn’t dare neglect the team leader, so he immediately answered, “Team Leader, rest assured. Nothing bad is going to happen to Little Hai. That Helian Da couldn’t defeat him.”

Ma Rulong was confused, so he asked, “What makes you so confident? That Helian Da is a Core Formation Expert. Even in the Cultivation Realm, he’s treated as an Elder.”

Xiong Li smiled faintly and said, “Team Leader, there’s no need to worry. Back in the bug caves, a fellow named Mu Dan used a jade talisman during his fight against Zhao Hai. This jade talisman summoned an attack that’s from a Nascent Soul Stage Expert. However, Little Hai just went through it with one punch. Helian Da is just at Core Formation, it’s impossible for him to be Little Hai’s opponent.”

Ma Rulong looked at Xiong Li in surprise. If he wasn’t certain that Xiong Li wouldn’t dare joke about this matter, then he might think that Xiong Li was lying. Zhao Hai was able to repel a Nascent Soul Expert’s attack using only his fist? What kind of strength is that?

While Ma Rulong was thinking about this, Helian Da spoke, “Good, this place has good feng shui. It’s a proper place for your burial.”

Hearing Helian Da, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh. This wasn’t a forced laugh, he truly found it funny. This was because he remembered something.

Looking at Zhao Hai’s appearance, Helian Da coldly snorted and said, “Is there something funny?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I just found it funny because another Cultivator said the same thing to me. Moreover, we’re in the same place. It’s truly strange, it seems like Cultivators really like to talk a lot.”

Hearing Zhao Hai, Helian Da’s expression changed, then he said, “Enough talking, prepare to die!”

Helian Da waved his hand as a earthen yellow palm came flying towards Zhao Hai. Helian Da was also an earth-element Cultivator. His hand attack held some fame in the Cultivation Realm. It was called the Five Elements Palm. The Five Elements Palm wasn’t famous for its fierceness. Instead, it was well known because it can be used by Cultivators of any element. This Five Elements Palm was actually a kind of spell.

The Five Elements Palm that Helian De used had a name – Thick Earth Palm. It was the same as any other Five Elements Palm but it had some earthen veins going along the palm’s fingers. Nobody would dare look down on this kind of attack.

Helian Da was only probing this time, he wanted to know Zhao Hai’s strength. If Zhao Hai was killed by the Thick Earth Palm, then that would be best. But if Zhao Hai doesn’t die, then at least Helian De would have some idea about Zhao Hai’s strength.

Seeing Helian De’s move, Zhao Hai smiled before clenching his fist and punched. This fist didn’t carry his entire strength. It was just enough to meet Helian De’s palm attack.

Boom!

As the fist and palm hit each other, a huge explosion resounded. The hill underneath shook from the impact. At the same time, Helian Da’s eyebrows jumped as his expression turned serious. He was very clear that his probe did nothing to gauge Zhao Hai’s true strength. This meant that Zhao Hai was stronger than he anticipated. At this point, Helian Da has begun to consider Zhao Hai as an opponent at an equal level.

Zhao Hai looked at Helian Da, then he smiled and said, “If you want to kill me, then you’ll need to show some real skills. Probing attacks like that are useless.”

Helian Da coldly snorted, then he said, “You’ll see.” Then he waved his hand and took out a huge axe. This axe looked like a hatchet. Its shaft wasn’t long but its axe head was enormous. The axe’s entire body was golden yellow in color. It also had a dense and heavy aura. This axe was Helian Da’s weapon, the Ground Splitting Axe.

The Ground Splitting Axe was actually Helian Da’s Life Source Weapon. It was made from golden earth as well as multitudes of special metals. It took three years to make it and after it was done, Helian De immediately kept it in his dantian for nurturing. It was the weapon that Helian Da was most adept in using.

Chapter 1253: In But Five Seconds

Cultivators of the Cultivation Realm have plenty of magic artifacts. Some of these magic artifacts were refined by the Cultivator themselves while some were spoils of battle. Besides Sword Cultivators, if a Core Formation Cultivator’s artifacts doesn’t number more than a dozen, then they would be an embarrassment.

But these things were merely shallow instruments. Although the Cultivators have a lot of artifacts in hand, they only have one true weapon – their Life Source Weapon.

A Life Source Weapon was directly connected to its master’s life. Unless their master died, nobody would be able to take it away. And the longer a Life Source Weapon was nurtured, the more powerful they would be. Even short-lived Life Source Weapons were more powerful than ordinary weapons.

Life Source Weapons were important to Cultivators. Unless they meet a very formidable foe, then these Life Force Weapons wouldn’t be taken out.

And since these Life Source Weapons were important, a Cultivator needs to choose which artifact to designate as his own Life Source Weapon. If the Life Source Weapon wasn’t good, then the Cultivator would be greatly affected in his future progress.

People are different from each other. Two people might practice the same Cultivation Method at the same time, but they may reach a different conclusion. However, for a person to find the most appropriate Life Source Weapon for himself is very difficult.

The first consideration in choosing would be the shape of the weapon. It needs to be compatible with the user’s preference. A cowardly person would never be able to make use of a blade shaped Life Source Weapon. The blade just isn’t compatible with their character. People who use the blade needed to be aggressive, while cowards would never go in front and lead a charge. These kinds of people would rather choose a shield-type weapon or some other defensive artifact as their own Life Source Weapon.

Besides the shape of the artifact, the choice of material is also crucial to a Life Source Weapon. The material needed to go hand-in-hand with the user’s attribute while at the same time holding great potential for future growth. If a Life Source Weapon was made of ordinary iron, then it would hamper its master’s growth.

Because of this, Cultivators needed to be extremely careful in choosing their own Life Source Weapon. They would spend a very long time to determine the suitable weapon for themselves. And then they would spend an even longer time to find the materials to make it. They would need to find a trustworthy craftsman to make their Life Source Weapon as well. But if it was possible, it was best if the Life Source Weapon was made by the master himself. Then after the weapon was refined and its spirit was awakened, its owner would immediately send it to their  dantian for nourishment. As time goes by, this weapon would become a Life Source Weapon.

Therefore, just by seeing Helian Da’s Life Source Weapon, one could see that he’s extremely confident in his strength, overbearing, and wouldn’t accept losing. It also meant that he’s a straightforward person that went straight to the point.

Helian Da revealing his Life Source Weapon meant that he now regarded Zhao Hai as a person that is his equal.

As soon as Zhao Hai saw Helian Da’s Life Source Weapon, he knew that things were getting serious. This was because the moment Helian Da took out his Life Source Weapon, his aura changed. The self-confident and overbearing aura was much more tangible now. Moreover, the area covered by Helian Da’s presence had expanded. This made Zhao Hai think that the weapon was something extraordinary.

Helian Da looked at Zhao Hai and then coldly said, “Zhao Hai, being killed by my axe is a great honor. Now die!” He moved his hand and then with heaven breaking strength, he sent his axe chopping down towards Zhao Hai.

Seeing the situation, Zhao Hai didn’t dare approach it empty-handedly. He moved his hand as a sledgehammer appeared. Zhao Hai didn’t throw the sledgehammer to meet the attack on its own. Instead, he charged forward and then clashed with the Earth Splitting Axe.

Helian Da’s chop was filled with imposing aura, oppressing anything it came across. It was an aura that informed everyone that it wouldn’t retreat. Therefore, Heliand Da didn’t retreat when faced with Zhao Hai. He continued his attack and before long the two weapons clashed.

Clang! The sound of the clash was akin to a hammer hitting a bell. A huge sound wave followed soon after. Even Xiong Li and the others who were at a distance were able to feel this impact. Their clothes had been ruffled by the pressure.

Then a loud sound was heard as the Earth Splitting Axe was shaken away. Helain Da’s face changed color as he coughed up blood. It was clear that he had suffered a heavy wound.

Zhao Hai looked at Helian Da, then he coldly smiled and said, “Mediocre. Is this the strength you’re so confident of when you dared to take revenge? If that’s the case, then you can stay here forever.”

Then Zhao Hai’s figure moved as he charged towards Helian Da. Helian Da’s expression changed and then he waved his hand to release a defensive shell in front of him. At the same time, he took out a jade bottle and pulled out a fiery red pill from inside. He threw the pill inside his mouth and then chewed on it twice before swallowing.

It was at this time that Zhao Hai’s hammer hit Helian Da’s shield. The surface of the shield had a light screen that was covered with many runes that made it look mysterious.

As Zhao Hai’s hammer striked the shield’s screen, the runes went bright before losing their power. Zhao Hai’s hammer seemed to be unaffected by the screen as its momentum was the same. Then as it hit the shield, the shield immediately turned into powder.

Standing behind the shield, Helian Da looked at Zhao Hai in great surprise. But then he took out two artifacts and sent them towards Zhao Hai.

The two artifacts were a flying sword and a double-edged blade. With its two edges, this weapon was called an edge in the Cultivation Realm.

It was clear that these two artifacts were used for offense, and their target was Zhao Hai. But since these two weapons were just thrown out, they had no coordination with each other. Helian Da didn’t control them and treated them as hidden weapons as he retreated at the same time.

Zhao Hai sneered as he charged forward. In the next moment, he appeared beside Helian Da, his hammer already swinging towards the target.

Helian Da didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this quick. If the pill that he had taken before hadn’t acted, then Zhao Hai would have already killed him.

Helian Da expected Zhao Hai to spend some time breaking the shield so that the pill’s effects would cause his strength to increase. Even if he would suffer internal injury after, as long as he killed Zhao Hai, then he could rest easily.

He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to destroy the shield in one attack. The pill’s effect had yet to manifest fully. Helian Da’s hope right now was to retreat and buy a few breath’s of time. However, Zhao Hai actually flashed beside him, Helian Da was running out of time.

Heliand Da wasn’t given more time to make plans as he made a strange noise due to him consuming the strength of his soul to augment his cultivation. Then he used his axe to fend off Zhao Hai’s attack. Then suddenly, he felt his chest hurting. His five solid organs and six hollow organs were violently shaken and then crushed. His strength was also beginning to vanish.

 Helian Da couldn’t help but lower his head and saw a silver spear stabbing through his body. Zhao Hai was holding the other end of the spear. Helian Da couldn’t help but stare. He didn’t know when Zhao Hai changed his hammer into a spear.

Helian Da died as a confused ghost. He simply didn’t know that Zhao Hai had a transforming weapon, and he was still unaware of Zhao Hai’s strength.

The time that Helian Da and Zhao Hai fought was actually very short. The two only clashed for about five seconds. However, a lot of things happened in these five seconds. Helian Da probed Zhao Hai and even released his Life Source Weapon to deal with him.

When Zhao Hai saw Helian Da’s weapon and the extraordinary changes it created, he wasn’t polite and immediately took out his weapon. With the weapon shattering formation installed, Zhao Hai overthrew Helian Da Ground Splitting axe and caused heavy damage to Helian Da’s gold core.

After injuring Helian Da, Zhao Hai didn’t stop. He quickly chased him down. Helian Da took a pill, hoping to increase his strength temporarily in order to defeat Zhao Hai. He knew that if he didn’t eat the pill, then he would die here. Therefore, he released his shield in order to buy time. He expected Zhao Hai to be blocked by his shield, buying him time for the pill’s effects to manifest.

However, he didn’t know that Zhao Hai’s hammer had several layers of weapon shattering. And with Zhao Hai’s strength added, the shield was broken in one attack. Helian Da’s plan failed, so he quickly attacked using the two weapons. But how could he have known that Zhao Hai can teleport? Zhao Hai turned his hammer into a spear and pierced Helian Da’s chest. With the weapon shattering in the spear, Helian Da’s inner armor was destroyed along with Helian Da’s organs. No matter what Helian Da does from then on, it would be impossible for him to continue living.

Zhao Hai also decided to kill Helian Da immediately because he could feel several other presences paying attention to their battle. If he doesn’t kill Helian Da immediately, then these people might join in. Zhao Hai didn’t want more trouble, so he killed Helian Da swiftly. He wanted to let these people know that he couldn’t be trifled with. This will let those people wary and they might behave themselves.

Chapter 1254: Six Realms Battlefield

With Helian Da dead, Zhao Hai wasn’t polite as he immediately covered Helian Da with a dark mist before sending him to the Space. Xiong Li and the others knew that Helian Da was now going to be part of Zhao Hai’s Undead army.

As Zhao Hai received Liquid Silver, Xiong Li and the others flew towards him. Xiong Li laughed and said, “Good job Little Hai. The fight this time is shorter. You’re getting more and more fierce.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I actually want to play with him some more, but unfortunately, there are some people who can’t rest their eyes and want to see how I kill. So I can only fulfill their wishes and deal with Helian Da faster.”

Ma Rulong and the other team leaders were still shaken. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai and Helian Da’s fight to only last five seconds. And Zhao Hai won.

That was a Core Formation Cultivator, not an impudent commoner. Was Zhao Hai always this strong?

Now that they heard Zhao Hai, Ma Rulong and the others immediately understood what Zhao Hai meant. When they used their spiritual force to scan, they immediately felt several other spiritual forces converging in their direction. To be honest, Ma Rulong approved of Zhao Hai’s conduct. It was what needed to be done in order to stop a second, third, or fourth Helian Da from coming. If these people still want to make a move, then they have to consider it well. After all, their own lives were still the most important thing.

Ma Rulong looked pleasantly at Zhao Hai as he laughed and said, “Good, very good. You’re really lifting the face of the Machine Field. Let’s head back and have a drink.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly then he followed Ma Rulong back into the city.

As they were flying forward and while Ma Rulong had a positive expression, he whispered to Zhao Hai, “Little Hai, now that you killed Helian Da, Jade Mountain will certainly retaliate. You need to be careful. As soon as the ranking tournament ends, I will immediately arrange for you to return to the Machine Field. Although the Cultivators are arrogant, they wouldn’t dare attack the Machine Field.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Team Leader, rest assured. Unless they send a Transcending Tribulation Expert, they can’t do anything to me. There’s no need to worry.”

When Ma Rulong heard Zhao Hai, his body couldn’t help but shake. Then he looked Zhao Hai in the eye and said, “Little Hai, are you telling the truth? Do you really have Nascent Soul-level strength? Nascent Soul Experts in the Cultivation Realm are very powerful, they have much more methods compared to Core Formation.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Team Leader, don’t worry. After all, my weapon isn’t simple. It’s Senior Leng Wuyeng’s unfinished weapon.”

Ma Rulong paused, causing everyone behind him to almost hit his body. Ma Rulong didn’t care about them as he looked at Zhao Hai with shining eyes. He looked like a hungry wolf that just saw food.

Also in Ma Rulong’s eyes was amazement. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have the weapon of legend. No wonder he was so strong.

Immediately after hearing about Liquid Silver, Ma Rulong immediately gave it credit for Zhao Hai’s strength. This wasn’t strange since the legends about liquid silver were too numerous. Ma Rulong’s response was reasonable.

Ma Rulong looked at Zhao Hai with burning eyes because he heard that Leng Wuyeng once said, when liquid silver is completed, then it would allow the Machine Field to contend with the Cultivators. And it was clear that Zhao Hai verified those words. Now, Zhao Hai had the strength to face a Nascent Soul Cultivator.

After some time, Ma Rulong began to recover. He turned to look at everyone and then said, “Alright, let’s continue on.” Then he took the lead and flew forward. Everyone could see that Ma Rulong was very moved by what Zhao Hai said.

The exchange between Zhao Hai and Ma Rulong was very low, nobody else heard them. But it must be said that with the skills of these people, they were fully capable of listening in on the conversation. But Ma Rulong and Zhao Hai certainly wouldn’t be happy if their conversation was being eavesdropped. And with Ma Rulong’s status as well as Zhao Hai’s strength, the others didn’t want to offend them. Therefore, they had no idea what made Ma Rulong pause.

The group returned to Seamount City soon after. As for the Cultivators in Seamount City, as soon as they saw Zhao Hai and the others, they immediately got out of the way.

They were all aware of the Helian Da’s declaration of revenge as well as the fact that they fought outside the city. Now that Zhao Hai returned unharmed, this meant that Helian Da failed. It didn’t matter what happened to Helian Da, Zhao Hai’s strength has been affirmed. Since there were no powerful experts in Seamount City, they naturally couldn’t provoke Zhao Hai who could defeat a Core Formation Expert. Because of this, they behaved themselves and allowed Zhao Hai’s group to pass through.

As they went forward, Ma Rulong’s heart couldn’t help but be filled with emotions as he looked at the Cultivators around them. This wasn’t his first time in the Cultivation Realm. Therefore, he clearly knew how these people treated those from the Machine Field. When would these people make way for the Machine Field? It was even impossible for them to stay quiet while the Machine Field’s people were around. He never thought of the day where they would behave like this.

Now these Cultivators were lowering their heads and made way. They’re possibly afraid of the Machine Field’s group. This caused Ma rulong to sigh.

Before long, the group returned to the Machine Field Institute. Upon arriving, Ma Rulong made the two Mages prepare food and wine before he pulled Zhao Hai to his room.

After closing the door to his room, Ma Rulong immediately turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, are you really using that weapon?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “The weapon has been stored in the Ashley Family’s Bone Symbol Camp. Back then, Camp Lord wanted me to choose a weapon for myself, so I chose it. Then I used materials I found in the lower realms in order to complete it.”

Zhao Hai told his story with a light tone, but Ma Rulong knew that what Zhao Hai had from the lower realms must be extraordinary. But he didn’t ask, instead he nodded and said, “Alright, alright. Little Hai, this competition is already yours. When the rankings are finalized, I’ll have Xiong Li and the others surrender. This way, others wouldn’t be able to use them to deal with you. What do you think?”

At this point, Ma Rulong wouldn’t dare put on any airs in front of Zhao Hai. Although he was the head of the Machine Field’s delegation, he knew that Zhao Hai’s strength had already surpassed him. Therefore, whatever decision he settled on, he would ask Zhao Hai’s opinion about it.

Zhao Hai proudly smiled and then said, “Team Leader, don’t worry about this. I’ve already talked it over with Boss Xiong and the others. As long as it’s announced that the Machine Field holds the top six in the elimination round, then we have already won.”

Ma Rulong nodded and then he sighed, “But your journey wouldn’t be easy. Those Cultivation Realm folks have already begun their plot. They would also do all they can to stop you in the ranking tournament. Not only the Cultivation Realm, you also need to be careful about those from the Demon Realm, especially Tu Mietan. I heard that the kid isn’t easy to deal with.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare, then he asked, “Demon Realm? Doesn’t the Demon Realm have a grudge against the Cultivation Realm? Why would they deal with us? They should unite with us in order to strike at the Cultivators.”

Ma Rulong smiled bitterly and said, “That should have been the case. But we can’t do anything about it, our realm is too weak. Everyone wants to take a bite out of our territory. Although there’s nothing worth taking in our realm in terms of material resources, we still have something that other realms are paying attention to – our people.”

“Our people?” Zhao Hai looked at Ma Rulong in confusion. He doesn’t understand what he was saying.

Ma Rulong nodded and said, “Correct, our people.”

Then he sighed and said, “Little Hai, you should already be aware that our commoners have the best lives compared to the commoners from other realms. In the Cultivation Realm and the Demon Realm, commoners are treated as farm animals. On the other hand, the Machine Field treated commoners as equals. Because of this, commoners became our main fighting strength.”

What Ma Rulong said might sound contradictory. Commoners had the least fighting prowess in the Cultivation Realm and the Demon Realm. But in the Machine Field, their main fighting force were the commoners. It might sound confusing, but when Zhao Hai heard Ma Rulong, he immediately understood.

In the Machine Field, the main fighting forces were the Mechs and the Battleships. Mechs would need innately talented pilots with spiritual forces powerful enough to control their robot. Their bodies also need to be strong. Only after strict training could one become a mech pilot.

On the other hand, although the requirements for being a battleship crew was still high, it wasn’t as strict as Mech pilots. Besides its commander, most battleship soldiers were as strong as most commoners. They were responsible for operating the battleship. Even if they had different jobs, they had commoner strength nonetheless.

Since Battleships were part of the Machine Field’s fighting force, commoners became the main fighters of the Machine FIeld. And because of their influence to the realm’s military strength, it’s natural for commoners to have higher status compared to the commoners of the other realms.

Ma Rulong continued, “Because of how the Cultivation Realm and the Demon Realm treat their commoners, their commoner population is getting smaller and smaller. Due to how badly they are treated, most commoner babies would die shortly after birth. Moreover, the mortality rate of their commoners is very high. On the other hand, the commoner population of the Machine Field is constantly increasing. For the other realms, this is worthy of paying attention to. For the Cultivation Realm and the Demon Realm, the Machine Field is an untapped mine of manpower supply. But since they still have some reservations towards us, they held back.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “So it’s like that. In other words, the Demon Realm also wants to suppress the Machine Field? Hehe, so this means that Tu Mietan wants to deal with me? If he does, then that would be interesting. I happen to dislike him as well.”

Ma Rulong said, “You need to be careful about those from the Demon Realm. Although they had been suppressed by the Cultivation Realm, their cruel methods gave them strange offensive means. During life and death battles, they’re much more difficult compared to Cultivators. Moreover, those from the Demon Realm are known to use any means to achieve their goals.”

It can be clearly seen that Ma Rulong dreaded the Demon Realm. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but ask, “Leader, you seem to have a lot of understanding about them? Have you fought with the people from the Demon Realm?”

Ma Rulong’s face couldn’t help but twitch, then he said, “It’s not too early to tell you this right now. Besides ascenders who already learned magic or battle qi, families also have members who are Mages and Warriors. Moreover, our achievements are often higher compared to ascenders. Even so, the level of magic and battle qi in the Machine Field seems to stagnate. Do you know why?”

Upon hearing Ma Rulong, Zhao Hai did indeed feel strange. He looked at Ma Rulong and said, “Team Leader, why is that?”

Ma Rulong let out a long breath, then he said, “A lot of people in Families who practice magic and battle qi died. This wasn’t because of family tasks nor training, but because they died in a certain place. It’s a very special place in the World of Cultivation, the SIx Realms Battlefield!”

Zhao Hai asked, “Six Realms Battlefield? Where is that?”

Ma Rulong closed his eyes, then he slowly said, “That place is Hell, a living Hell. The Six Realms Battlefield is a subspace. I don’t know how huge this subspace is since it is very strange. It should be very enormous. But unlike the World of Cultivation that has planets, this subspace consists of a huge piece of land and large spans of oceans. There are all kinds of beasts inside as well as medicinal plants and treasures. It can be said that the plants harvested there comprises the majority of the Cultivation Realm’s pill ingredients. Moreover, advanced-level herbs can be found there every year.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be surprised upon hearing Ma Rulong. He didn’t expect such a place to exist. He didn’t say anything and just waited for Ma Rulong to continue.

Ma Rulong softly said, “One could only go there through spatial rifts. There’s also no way for transmission formations to be used on the other side. However, spatial rifts heading to that subspace are very rare.”

Zhao Hai continued to listen. This subspace seems very strange.

Then Ma Rulong continued, “Being able to establish a foothold in that subspace is very important to any realm. Naturally, this includes the Machine Field. But since the rifts to that subspace are very small, only Mechs and people could enter. Although Mechs have pretty strong fighting capabilities, its pilots would practically be killed there without the support of battleships. So if we want to occupy a place there, we need Mages and Warriors. A lot of our Mages and Warriors die in the battlefield just to protect the small foothold that the Machine Field was able to occupy.”

Chapter 1255: Half Succeeded

To be honest, Zhao Hai hasn’t thought of something like the Six Realms Battlefield existing. The Machine Field and the Cultivation Realm’s writings never mentioned such a place. After hearing Ma Rulong, Zhao Hai knew that this matter must have been held in great secrecy.

Ma Rulong, seemingly immersed in his memories, continued speaking, “In the Six Realms Battlefield, people would die every day. Because the Machine Field isn’t that strong, we can only rely on our numbers to defend our territory. But because of this, it’s impossible for us to expand.”

After he said this, Ma Rulong paused for some time as though he was recalling his time in the Six Realms Battlefield. Then he said, “In the Six Realms Battlefield, you fight any race. Besides people from our realm, you shouldn’t believe in anyone. Countless Mages and Warriors in the battlefield chose to die alongside their enemies since this is the only way for our realm to hold on. I stayed in the Six Realms Battlefield for three months. And in those three months, I almost died five times. And in that timeframe, I also went through hundreds of battles of different sizes. You can imagine what kind of place it is.”

Zhao Hai finally knew why Ma Rulong knew so much about the other realms. This was because he had fought against these people before. And it seems like they clashed more than one time.

Ma Rulong looked at Zhao Hai and said, “After you return, I’m afraid that you will also go to the Six Realms Battlefield. Little Hai, you need to go there so that our commoners wouldn’t become slaves to others. You go there to prove to everyone that the Machine Field couldn’t be easily provoked.”

Zhao Hai calmly nodded and said, “Yes, you can rest assured. If I’m arranged to go to the Six Realms Battlefield, I will definitely go.”

Seeing Zhao Hai’s calm reaction, Ma Rulong gave an appreciative nod as he said, “Alright. Go take a break. You still need to achieve good results in the ranking tournament.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he left. To be honest, he wasn’t too anxious to go to the Six Realms Battle and go all out like what Ma Rulong wanted. He has his own pace, and he liked to take his time.

The Six Realms Battlefield has a lot of treasures indeed, but for Zhao Hai, the amount of materials that can enter his eyes was too limited. Therefore, he wasn’t too anxious. Just like he said, if the Machine Field wanted him to go to the Six Realm Battlefield, then he will go. But if the Machine Field doesn’t send him, then he wouldn’t take the initiative to request service.

In Zhao Hai’s view, in order to ensure that the commoners of the Machine Field would maintain their current lives, killing in the Six Realms Battlefield wasn’t enough. Strengthening the common population should be first.

In fact, Zhao Hai doesn’t think that fighting in the Six Realms Battlefield was necessary for the greater good of the Machine Field. Fighting in the Six Realm Battlefield only exhausted the Machine Field’s talents. This caused the Machine Field’s strength to lag behind the other realms. Relying on battleships and mechs for the realm’s strength wasn’t good for the realm’s further progress.

But in the end, Zhao Hai was still someone from the Machine Field. He would still go to the Six Realms Battlefield for the benefit of the Machine Field. In any case, he would have a lot of free time after the competition. He wasn’t worried about going to the battlefield.

To be honest, Zhao Hai was very curious about the Six Realms Battlefield. He wants to know what the battlefield looks like as well as its current situation.

Besides this reason, he also wants to go to the Six Realm Battlefield in order to collect more Undead. The Six Realms Battlefield was a place where constant battles take place. Naturally, there would also be a lot of deaths happening there. From what Zhao Hai can see, these dead people were a waste if not utilized. If Zhao Hai was able to make these people into Undead, then nobody in the World of Cultivation would dare annoy him.

While he thought about this, Zhao Hai returned to his own room. The rooms had already been pre-assigned. Although the Machine Field institute had undergone a huge renovation, the inside of the rooms was still the same. Zhao Hai stayed in the same room he stayed in before.

Xiong Li and the others were waiting for Zhao Hai outside his room. Upon seeing Zhao Hai return, Xiong Li and the others immediately walked over as Xiong Li asked, “Little Hai, why did the team leader call you over?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s nothing important. Let’s head in and talk. I’m afraid the team leader is going to call us over later to have a drink.” Everyone’s face was smirking. Then at this time Lu Dingtian said, “Never seen the world.”

Zhao Hai and the other gawked, then they all laughed simultaneously. They understand what Lu Dingtain was talking about. The team leader and the other haven’t seen the world. Only a Core Formation expert’s death and they were already celebrating.

This statement wasn’t funny in itself, but when Lu Dingtian said it, it became hilarious. Lu Dingtian was a quiet person. He had a character that would make it seem like he’ll be uncomfortable if he spoke more than a single word. Now that such a person said a string of words, Zhao Hai and the others couldn’t help but laugh.

The group laughed as they entered Zhao Hai’s room. Upon closing the door, Zhao Hai immediately turned his head to Xiong Li and the others and said, “Boss, you and the others shouldn’t participate in the tournament. As soon as you’re declared as qualified to enter the tournament, immediately forfeit and then return to the Machine FIeld. Close up and practice your cultivation methods.”

XIong Li and the others stared. They don’t understand why Zhao Hai was so anxious this time. Then in a low voice, Zhao Hai told them about the Six Realms Battlefield. Then he said, “It’s possible that when the competition ends, they will send us to the battlefield. Therefore, you need to practice your cultivation method as soon as possible.”

Xiong Li and the others looked at Zhao Hai in shock. This was the first time they heard about the Six Realms Battlefield. But since they believed that Zhao Hai wouldn’t deceive them, they immediately nodded and said, “Alright, rest assured. We know what to do.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he waved his hand, taking out several sheets of papers. Then he handed the papers over to everyone and said, “These cultivation methods are compatible with your body’s attribute. Third Brother, you can teach Sixth Brother your Divine Fire Dragon Art. Also, please write it down for me.”

Dongfang Yu nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll do it now.” Then he walked out.

However, Zhao Hai held him back and said, “It’s fine, there’s still time. Right, you can all take this and use it when you go back and close up.” Then he took out several bottles and gave it to his brothers. These were all potions that are beneficial to cultivation.

Dongfang Yu naturally wouldn’t be polite as they all took their own bottle and stored it inside their spatial items. Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Let’s go and have a drink with the team leader. When the ranking tournament officially begins, you head back to the Machine Field. And when I return, let’s head to the Six Realms Battlefield together. Let’s teach the other fellows a lesson.”

Xiong Li and the others laughed. They weren’t that worried about heading to the Six Realms Battlefield. The main reason for this confidence was because Zhao Hai would be with them. As long as Zhao Hai was there, they don’t have anything to worry about.

When the group went out of the room, they saw that several tables filled with wine and dishes had already been prepared outside. But to be honest, when Xiong LI and the others saw the wine and dishes, they couldn’t help but frown a bit. This was because the dishes and wine weren’t a lot.

At this time, Ma Rulong also walked out of his room. He also saw the lack of food and wine on the tables, but he wasn’t surprised. Then he sighed and said, “It’s hard for us here in the Cultivation Realm. It’s not easy to get food in this place. Little Hai, if you eat and drink these things, then we might as well drink water.”

As soon as everyone heard Ma Rulong, they couldn’t help but laugh. To be honest, now that they had drank Zhao Hai’s liquor, they were somewhat spoiled.

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Team Leader, I’ll take care of it.” Then after he said that, a large number of wines and dishes appeared. Everyone didn’t hold back and immediately started to partake in the food. Since Zheng Li wasn’t present this time, everyone was a bit rowdy. The other team leaders were giving Zhao Hai’s toasts and chatted with him, trying to establish a closer relationship.

Although the status of these team leaders in the Machine FIeld wasn’t low, it wasn’t high as well. Naturally, they couldn’t compare to Ma Rulong. Now that Zhao Hai’s rise was unstoppable, these people took the chance to establish a good relationship with him. These people weren’t stupid, they knew that they could benefit from this in the future.

As soon as Zhao Hai saw these people, he knew what they were doing. However, he didn’t ignore them and instead chatted with them and established contacts. He even made sure to take note about their names as well as their origins.

Xiong Li and the others looked at Zhao Hai and couldn’t help but sigh. They began to think about what kinds of things Zhao Hai experienced in the lower realms. How was he able to handle everything?

Not only Xiong Li and the others, Ma Rulong was also sighing. Zhao Hai gave him a strange feeling, someone who couldn’t be completely understood. But Ma Rulong could see that Zhao Hai had some sentiment towards the Machine Field and had no favorable impression towards the Cultivation Realm. This made Ma Rulong relieved.

There were plenty of talents in the Machine Field that transferred to the Cultivation Realm. This wasn’t a rare thing. Ma Rulong was afraid that Zhao Hai would settle in the Cultivation Realm later on. He told Zhao Hai about the Six Realms Battlefield in order to make Zhao Hai feeling a sense of belonging to the Machine Field. But from what Ma Rulong could see, it seems like he had already half succeeded.

Chapter 1256: Poisoned!

It wasn’t unreasonable for Ma Rulong to think that he had half-succeeded. Ma Rulong found out that Zhao Hai already had some sense of belonging to the Machine Field. And this wasn’t only because Zhao Hai has a woman who was from the realm.

The moment Zhao Hai sees himself as someone from the Machine Field, only then would Ma Rulong be successful.

But Ma Rulong had yet to succeed. This was because he had underestimated Zhao Hai’s mental capability. Zhao Hai experienced a lot of things and his mind has become as firm as rock. Just a few words from Ma Rulong wouldn’t make Zhao Hai excited. Fighting desperately against the other realms? That’s impossible for Zhao Hai. And Ma Rulong realized this, so he reckoned that everything he had done until now only brought him halfway to succeeding.

Actually,  Ma Rulong didn’t deceive Zhao Hai. The Six Realms Battlefield was truly the main fighting stage of the World of Cultivation. Moreover, a lot of Machine Field practitioners perish there. There were various geniuses from great families that went there to temper themselves to become formidable Mages and Warriors. Moreover, they learned how to effectively coordinate with each other. It can be said that those people were the true elites of the Machine Field. If the Machine Field took them out of the Six Realms Battlefield and used them in the realm, then they wouldn’t be easily bullied. After all, these people were as strong as a thousand battleships.

However, it should be noted that even if this power couldn’t be underestimated, it was heavily controlled by the families of the Machine Field. Why were there many powerful Ascenders that haven’t entered the Six Realms Battlefield? This was because these Ascenders weren’t under the control of any high-ranked family. And even if they managed to enter the battlefield, they would still be recalled soon after.

What the Machine Field’s higher-ups needed were obedient people. They’d rather have someone obedient rather than someone who was strong but was uncontrollable.

There was a valid reason why the Machine Field’s higher-ups chose to do this. The density of spiritual qi in the Six Realms Battlefield is very strong, it was a place very suitable for practice. Whether it be Mages or Warriors, practicing in the Six Realms Battlefield was very beneficial. Besides the density of spiritual qi, the battlefield was also rich in medicinal plants. Even if they hadn’t been processed and were taken directly, these plants would still improve one’s cultivation speed.

In this case, if the Machine Field’s higher ups don’t control which person to let in to the battlefield, then these uncontrolled folks would get stronger and stronger. And then there would come a point where they could no longer be commanded, and then they would be able to wrestle for influence in the Realm.

Because of this, the Machine Field’s higher-ups decided to have firm control on who to send to the Six Realms Battlefield.

Ma Rulong becoming the team leader for the rookies wasn’t accidental. He actually received an order from the Machine Field’s higher-ups to be in constant contact with the rookies. As long as Ma Rulong doesn’t have any issue with a particular rookie, then they would be enlisted to enter the Six Realms Battlefield. But if Ma Rulong thought that the person was unreliable, then there’s no knowing if they can ever enter the battlefield.

However, the Machine Field’s higher-ups sent the wrong person this time. Although Ma Rulong was very loyal to the Machine Field, he also stayed in the Six Realms Battlefield. He knew much more about the situation there than the Machine Field’s higher-ups.

For the Machine Field’s higher-ups, the battlefield was a place where they lost their powerful experts. However, these losses were reduced to mere numbers. But for Ma Rulong, these losses were his allies, his brothers!

When two different emotions head for the same goal, then the final result would naturally be different. Ma Rulong doesn’t care about loyalty like the Machine Field’s higher-ups. What he wants was a strong person to go to the Six Realms Battlefield and avenge those who died there. He wanted to vent air!

Because of this consideration, Ma Rulong told Zhao Hai about the Six Realms Battlefield in a manner that only resulted in half-success.

Ma Rulong was quite impatient in this situation. He knew that normally, it would be impossible for Zhao Hai to enter the Six Realms Battlefield. But if he said a few good words about Zhao Hai, then entry to the battlefield might be a possibility.

With this thought in mind, Ma Rulong couldn’t help but down a whole glass of wine. He was thinking whether he should support Zhao Hai or not.

To be honest, although the Six Realms Battlefield was filled with battle, it was also a good place for practice. If Zhao Hai went there, then he would be able to rapidly increase in strength.

But after thinking about his hardworking comrades back in the Six Realms Battlefield, Ma Rulong finally decided to help Zhao Hai in. Even if Zhao Hai would be there for a short time, he would still be able to reduce the pressure felt by the Machine Field’s people there.

Zhao Hai noticed that Ma Rulong was somewhat silent, but he didn’t mind it. Back when Ma Rulong talked about the Six Realms Battlefield, his tone was somewhat solemn.

As the party continued, and people were chatting and drinking, one person suddenly coughed loudly and then vomited blood. Moreover, the blood was blackened.

Zhao Hai stared, this was obviously a poisoning. He immediately flew towards the person and then took out a glass of water.

The man’s face began to turn black. When Zhao Hai gave him the glass of water, his condition began to calm down. The black lines on his face also slowly subsided.

However, besides Zhao Hai, the people in the courtyard had yet to catch up on what was going on. Some haven’t even put their glasses down as they stared at Zhao Hai.

At this time, Ma Rulong responded. He went to Zhao Hai’s side and said, “Little Hai, what happened?”

Zhao Hai said solemnly, “Poison.” Then he turned his head and looked at the man’s wine glass. Then he smelled the liquor inside it and found out that this wasn’t his wine.

Then he looked under the table and saw a small bottle. The bottle wasn’t among the ones he took out. It seems like the liquor bought by the two Mages of the institute. Zhao Hai took up the bottle, smelled it and then drank its contents.

Zhao Hai’s action gave Xiong Li and the others a scare. They had an idea of what happened by watching Zhao Hai’s movements. They knew that the bottle had the poisoned liquor. But Zhao Hai actually drank it. Xiong Li hastily yelled, “Little Hai, you’re insane!” However, he didn’t have enough time to stop Zhao Hai from drinking the poisoned liquor.

After Zhao Hai drank the liquor, he swished it in his mouth before swallowing. Then he shook his head and said, “The taste of this wine isn’t very good. This man must have drank rarely, or else he wouldn’t drink this liquor.”

At the same time, the moment the liquor entered Zhao Hai’s mouth, a prompt was heard in his brain, “Deadly poison detected inside host’s body. Detoxifying. Detoxification success. Analyzing. Poison has an energy absorbing ability, swallowing the host’s spiritual qi and turning it into deadly poison. It will make the host faint before killing him.”

Zhao Hai put the bottle down, then he turned to Ma Rulong and said, “This liquor has been poisoned. It swallows spiritual qi and makes people faint. It’s quite fatal as well. Let me look at those dishes.” Then he took a bite of the dishes that had been bought outside.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “These dishes are also poisoned. Moreover, the poison is different. It’s also fatal.”

Although Ma Rulong had no idea why Zhao Hai was fine, but after seeing that the man was fine after Zhao Hai gave him the cup of water, he knew that Zhao Hai must have a type of universal antidote on him. Ma Rulong also believed in Zhao Hai’s words, his expression changed as he said, “Bring those two guys here.”

The other team leaders were all startled right now. They immediately searched all directions for the two Mages. Before long, the two were found, but they had already been killed by the poison.

The bodies of the two Mages were completely black. Ma Rulong’s expression darkened. If the food didn’t look unappetizing, and Zhao Hai didn’t have any experience with poison, then the entire Machine Field’s delegation would have been wiped out today.

Zhao Hai looked at Ma Rulong’s expression, then he smiled and said, “Team Leader, if you agree, I can turn them into Undead. The Undead don’t lie, perhaps we can find out what’s going on.”

Ma Rulong nodded, “Alright. Whether they were killed or committed suicide, we still need to know who wants to poision us.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then wrapped the two corpses with black gas. When the gas disappeared, the two were already standing up. The black on their faces disappeared, it was as if the two were alive. However, they were no longer breathing.

Ma Rulong couldn’t help but be surprised with Zhao Hai’s technique. But he had no time to ask about it, instead he looked at the revived Mages and asked, “Is it you who poisoned us?”

The two shook their heads and one of them said, “We are unaware about the poison. We just went to the place where we can buy food and wine. The owner of the place invited us for some drinks. We don’t know what happened next.”

Ma Rulong nodded and let out a sigh of relief. It’s good that they weren’t spies. Zhao Hai looked at Ma Rulong and said, “Team Leader, I’ll go and take that shop’s owner. We’ll slowly investigate this matter.”

Ma Rulong said, “Do you think those people are still there?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “They’ll be there. Maybe they just changed clothes. I’ll return quickly.” Then he disappeared in place. Ma Rulong looked at the place Zhao Hai disappeared from with a strange expression. Zhao Hai was becoming more and more mysterious in his eyes.

It didn’t take long before Zhao Hai reappeared. He waved his hand and threw several people on the ground. They were all wearing normal Cultivator clothing. They look nothing special.

Chapter 1257: I Am Proud

When Ma Rulong looked at the people dressed in Cultivator clothing, he discovered that they weren’t breathing. He couldn’t help but look at Zhao Hai and say, “Little Hai, are they dead?” Zhao Hai nodded and said, “They’re dead. They should be the people that sold the food and wine.”

Ma Rulong nodded, then he turned his head to these people and said, “Are you the ones who put poison into our food?” The group of Undead simultaneously said, “Yes.”

Ma Rulong let out a long breath. Then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, aren’t you worried that you’ll kill the wrong person?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “If I made a mistake, then I made a mistake.”

Hearing Zhao Hai, Ma Rulong along with Xiong Li and the others sucked in a cold breath. Zhao Hai’s tone seemed like he didn’t treat human life seriously. They remembered that Zhao Hai was someone who killed a lot of people back in the lower realms. Killing a few people was no big deal to him.

Ma Rulong took deep breaths to calm himself down. Then he turned his head to the Undead Cultivators and said, “Where are you from?”

After which, some of the Undead replied, “We’re from the Three Mountains Alliance.” Ma Rulong expected this answer. Zhao Hai and the Three Mountains Alliance now had a big enmity. For the Alliance to retaliate was reasonable.

Then the other Undead replied, “We’re from Extreme Cold City.” This was also not unexpected. Zhao Hai wiped out Li Chuchen, leaving Extreme Cold City with no benefits to gain in the competition. It was natural for them to hate Zhao Hai.

Finally, one Undead was left. Although this person was already dead, one could still see that he already looked like death when he was alive. Upon seeing this person, one would feel uncomfortable. This Undead opened his mouth and said, “I’m from the Demon Realm’s Sacred Blood Sect.”

Upon hearing this person, Ma Rulong couldn’t help but frown. Zhao Hai and the Sacred Blood Sect had no enmity. For the Sacred Blood Sect to participate in dealing with Zhao Hai only meant that they were already considering Zhao Hai as a threat.

When he thought of this, Ma Rulong couldn’t help but turn to Zhao Hai. Seeing Ma Rulong look at him, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. Then he waved his hand to store the Undead and at the same time he said, “Team Leader, it seems like it’s impossible for me to not offend the Sacred Blood Sect.”

Ma Rulong sighed and said, “Demon Cultivators are much greedier than ordinary Cultivators. This time, they rely on Tu Mietan to get them benefits the same way the Machine Field relies on you. It’s no wonder that they treat you as their biggest opponent.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s good that they see me as an opponent. I just don’t know if they can afford having me as an enemy.”

Ma Rulong pursed his lips and didn’t say anything. If others were to say those words, then nobody would believe them. But since it was Zhao Hai, he has the qualifications to say so.

Zhao Hai looked at Ma Rulong and said, “Team Leader, these two Undead Mages, I’ll take them away as well. You can have someone else take their place. But I think we should just leave it to robots. After all, people staying in this place is too dangerous. We’re not counting on this place to make money as well. And I’m afraid we wouldn’t be able to collect information. So we might as well have robots taking care of this place.”

Ma Rulong nodded, “I’ll take care of this. You can take those two away.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then took away the two Undead Mages.

At this time, people had already lost interest in celebrating. The two robots were left to clean up the courtyard while Zhao Hai and the others returned to their room to rest. Then Zhao Hai went to the Space.

To be honest, Zhao Hai didn’t really expect the Sacred Blood Sect to deal with him. He didn’t want to provoke the people from the Demon Realm yet, but it seems like this was no longer possible.

Laura and the others naturally knew about what was happening outside. Seeing Zhao Hai return, they greeted him and then they all sat down. Meg brought Zhao Hai tea as Laura looked at him and said, “Brother Hai, what do you plan to do now?”

Zhao Hai just sneered and said, “What else can I do? I’ll deal with Tu Mietan first. Doesn’t Tu Mietan want to deal with me? Since it’s come to this, then let’s see how it turns out. And I reckon I’ll be sent to the Six Realms Battlefield after the competition. I’ll look for trouble with the Sacred Blood Sect there.”

Laura nodded and said, “That’s also good. But Brother Hai, I think what you should do right now is study the Cultivation Realm’s methods and also the way to use those magic artifacts, like flying sword techniques. Even if they can’t help you much, at least you have some knowledge about them.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll use the next few days to study. I’ll begin once I had Third Brother’s Divine Fire Dragon Art analyzed by the scanner.”

Laura wasn’t against this method. With Zhao Hai’s current ability, it would be very simple for him to learn these things. However, Zhao Hai would need some time to find a suitable technique for him.

At this time, Lizzy opened her mouth and said, “Brother Hai, you need to teach them a lesson in the tournament. Let them know that you aren’t easy to mess with.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Rest assured, I will. This time I need to teach them a very good lesson. Otherwise, they’ll get troublesome. I must call Helain Da and ask about this.”

The women nodded and didn’t say anything. They had long since been used to the Undead. To them, Undead and Robots were the same.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and Helian Da appeared in front of him. Helian Da’s wound had already vanished. He was standing there respectfully.

Zhao Hai could see that Helian Da’s strength hasn’t regressed, it had been preserved. He’s now a Core Formation Undead.

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “Helian Da, can you still practice?”

Helian Da nodded, “Replying to Young Master. I can still practice my original cultivation method. And my gold core hasn’t been affected at all.”

Upon hearing Helian Da, Zhao Hai stared. He was confused about this so he called Cai’er over and said, “Cai’er, what is this about?”

Cai’er appeared beside Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, this is the benefit that the upgraded Space provided. They can preserve their original strength. The other Undead can also practice cultivation methods. Young Master, you should know that the Space has been turned into a small universe. Naturally, it has the same energies present outside. The Space’s Undead are also different from the Undead outside that only has the dark attribute.”

Zhao Hai nodded. And since there’s no need to tell Cai’er that he understood, he allowed Cai’er to go on.

Cai’er continued, “But the Space is different. Everything in the Space follows Young Master’s wishes. And since you have already recognized the Undead as an independent race, the Space’s Undead became different from the Undead outside. In fact, the Undead are now like the Beastmen and the Elves. And by becoming independent, their attribute is no longer tied to the dark element. Now, they can practice any cultivation method they want. That’s why Helian Da is like this.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t expect his action to have this much impact. The Undead were now able to practice any cultivation method. However, Zhao Hai was still puzzled, he looked at Cai’er and said, “But before, the Undead still cannot practice. Their progress is still the same as the Undead outside.”

Cai’er nodded, “That’s correct. But that is because Young Master’s level is too low. Even if the Space has been turned into a small universe, its level is still too low to allow the Undead freedom in cultivation.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly. In the end it came to levelling. Only by levelling up could he become strong. Once the Space reaches a higher level, everything else would follow. It seems like upgrading the Space was still his only way forward.

What Cai’er said about Zhao Hai’s wishes being followed by the Space was only half right. The Space did indeed base its laws according to Zhao Hai, but these laws can only be implemented if its level was high enough. There were still a lot of laws not being implemented in Zhao Hai’s Space.

However, Zhao Hai believed that if he continues with upgrading the Space, then he would have a universe that belongs entirely to him. What he wishes would be law of that universe.

Zhao Hai let out a long breath. Then he nodded and said, “So that’s the case. Alright, make them cultivate. Right Cai’er, distribute the cultivation methods we gained to the people in the Space. The methods of the Space are too simple. Now that we have more advanced cultivation methods, let’s have them practice it as well. Give it to the Undead as well. The more powerful we are, the better.”

Cai’er nodded. Then Zhao Hai looked at Helian Da and said, “Tell Cai’er about your methods and techniques later. Tell Li Chuchen and the others about this as well. You can keep your magic weapons, but your methods need to be recorded.”

Helian Da nodded, then he followed Cai’er out.

But before the two left, Laura called out, “Cai’er, ask them about the Cultivation Realm’s situation. Especially the relationships between the Sects. We need to know which sects are allied and which one have grudges with each other.” Cai’er nodded before leaving with Helian Da.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s good that you think these things carefully. I wouldn’t have thought about this. With you here, I’ll have more presence of mind.”

Laura smiled and said, “You’re alone outside dealing with those people. If we can’t handle these things for you, then wouldn’t we be useless?”

Zhao Hai gently hugged her without saying anything. They had been together for so long that they no longer need to speak to convey their emotions.

Lizzy and the others were in the hug as well. Their destinies were now tied together. There’s nothing in this world that can separate them.

Then at this time, there was a flash of white light before Margaret appeared in the Space. Margaret had been spending her time lately in the Ashley Family. This was because the family had been very busy in the past several days.

Zhao Hai’s name was too attractive at this time. From how he, along with Xiong Li and the others snatched the top six in the elimination round to his declaration of brotherhood with Xiong Li and the others, all of it has been passed back to the Machine Field. The realm was currently in awe of Zhao Hai’s performance. At this point, Zhao Hai’s popularity had reached a level that was unimaginable.

Zhao Hai became the hero of the Machine Field. No one cared that he’s an ascender nor did they mind him killing the other participants. What everyone was focused on was the fact that Zhao Hai made history, something that the Machine Field would remember for many years to come.

And this brought unimaginable benefits to the Ashley Family. People who had nothing to do with the family suddenly established diplomatic relations with them. Families who were hostile to them immediately resolved their misgivings. The entire Machine Field’s eyes were directed at what the family would do. The space outside Ashley Family’s planet became very busy. Numerous space platforms were built in order to accommodate the ships flying to and from the planet. It seems like the Machine Field had turned frantic.

The Machine Field was suppressed for too long, and they badly needed a hero to look up to. Now Zhao Hai was here. Not only did he win first place in the elimination round, he also killed Li Chuchen, in addition to his many exploits. These things caused the Machine Field to heat up.

Because of this, it was impossible for Margaret to return to the Space. She was Zhao Hai’s woman, so people would want to meet her. Every day, misses and madames of families asked to meet her. Their number reached hundreds, causing Margaret to be exhausted.

Today she had a rare break so she immediately ran to the Space to take a good rest.

Just as Margaret entered the Space, she saw Zhao Hai sitting there with Laura and the others in his embrace. Seeing Margaret appear, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and opened his arm to welcome Margaret. Laura and the others couldn’t help but laugh.

Zhao Hai patted Margaret’s head. After some time, he said, “Margaret, you’ve worked hard.”

Margaret shook her head and said, “It’s not that hard. Brother Hai, you have to see it for yourself. The entire Machine Field is going insane with happiness because of you. It makes me very proud to be your woman.”

Chapter 1258: Core of the Formation

Time passed and five days went by in a blink of an eye. A lot of things happened in these five days. One of the most important things was the release of the top 100 rookies in the elimination round. And as expected, Zhao Hai and his brothers occupied the top 6 in the ranking.

Because of the rule of the Six Realms Beginner Competition, the results couldn’t be changed. Otherwise, not only the Machine Field, but the other realms would protest.

Once the list was released, it could no longer be changed. Even if someone quits now, it would only be counted as forfeiting. Then their names would be placed at the bottom. It was impossible for others to substitute them.

Because of this rule, once the official list went out, Xiong Li and the others forfeited immediately. The committee for the competition reviewed their request and accepted their withdrawal. Before the official matches even started, five people were already ranked at the bottom five of the leaderboard.

The only person from the Machine Field who didn’t forfeit was Zhao Hai. It was also impossible for Zhao Hai to quit. After all, he was planning to win the whole tournament.

Regarding the Machine Field’s shameless approach, the other realms didn’t have any problem with it. On the other hand, what the Machine Field did was good for them. Everyone knew that the Machine Field’s people weren’t easy to deal with. It was said that it wasn’t only Zhao Hai who was a monster, the others were quite strong as well.

Now that five of the Machine Field’s participants had withdrawn, this meant that the weakest of the 100 were now bumped up by five places. This was good for the other realms.

At the same time, the Machine Field felt that this decision was acceptable. After all, being able to take place in the top 100 was already a historic accomplishment. In addition, Zhao Hai didn’t withdraw. They still had someone representing their realm in the competition. Therefore, the fact that Xiong Li and the others withdrew wasn’t much of a problem to them.

Compared to Xiong Li and the others’ forfeiture, the Machine Field paid more attention to another news, it was Zhao Hai’s killing of Helian Da.

Helian Da publicly declared his revenge on Zhao Hai. This was something that the entire Cultivation Realm was aware of. But Zhao Hai was currently living well, while Helian Da disappeared. Even an idiot would know that Helian Da has been destroyed by Zhao Hai.

This information was world-shaking for the Machine Field. Helian Da was an expert in the Core Formation stage. If Zhao Hai could easily deal with an expert like that, then how easy would it be for him to take the top spot in the competition?

This fact was also very significant for the Cultivation Realm. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be able to deal with Helian Da. Helian Da was a known Core Formation Expert. Even common Core Formation Experts would behave in front of him. But now, Zhao Hai eliminated him. In other words, it was impossible for Core Formation Experts to deal with Zhao Hai. So now, would they send a Nascent Soul Expert to deal with Zhao Hai? That is only if the Cultivation Realm had no concern about their face.

Zhao Hai was just a rookie!

This made the Cultivators feel awkward. Cultivators were very concerned about saving their face. Sending a Core Formation Expert to deal with Zhao Hai might be a little bit justified. But a Nascent Soul Expert? If they really use a Nascent Soul Expert, then they would be laughed at by the other realms.

Moreover, the Cultivators had yet to know about Zhao Hai’s real strength. If Zhao Hai really had the strength to fight a silverback gold-winged bug, then even if they send out a Nascent Soul Expert, then they might not even be able to deal with Zhao Hai. Because of this, the Cultivators were stuck on what to do.

Meanwhile, Zhao Hai rarely appeared outside in the past few days since he was closing up. Ma Rulong had already accustomed to Zhao Hai’s habit of closing up. This time, he didn’t meet with Xiong Li and the others. He just approached Dongfang Yu for his Divine Fire Dragon Art and fire dragon sword technique. Other than that, he spent the entire time inside the Space.

What Zhao Hai practiced this time was mainly the manipulation of flying swords as well as using the various magic artifacts. He has Liquid Silver that can be turned into almost any mag artifact. This type of transforming ability would have great uses in later fights. Therefore, Zhao Hai wants to gain a small mastery of it.

Originally, Zhao Hai didn’t know much about magical artifacts. He had obtained some formations to control them before, but he was clueless about their specific applications. After all, he wasn’t a Cultivator and never learned any of this. Even if the Universal Scanner was very formidable, it cannot analyze unless there was sufficient data.

But now things were different. Not only did Zhao Have Li Chuchen, he also had Helian Da, a native of the Cultivation Realm. Helian Da was born in Jade Mountain under a Cultivator family. He has received a lot of education since at a very early stage.

In fact, Zhao Hai was an elementary level Cultivator. He even has the best Cultivation Methods as well as knowledge about formations. What Zhao Hai needed right now was a good teacher to instruct him in how to fight like a Cultivator. And Helian Da was that good teacher.

In the last few days, Helian Da instructed Zhao Hai about the Cultivation Realm’s formations, how to use them, and their various applications. Then Cai’er had these methods analyzed by the scanner before handing it over to Zhao Hai.

But since time was short, Zhao Hai was unable to study all of these things. However, since these things had been saved inside the Space, he would be able to use it all the time. This was Zhao Hai’s biggest advantage.

Besides these formations, after getting the fire dragon sword technique, Zhao Hai used the scanner to make him the most compatible sword technique.

To be precise, this cannot be regarded as a full set of sword techniques. Instead, it was a set of combinations of methods that could allow Liquid Silver to exhibit its maximum potential.

Zhao Hai was very optimistic about this method. He researched how to manipulate flying swords and found how unique they were. Although he took Liquid Silver out before and had it fly, opportunities to use it to attack the enemy was very few.

Now that he saw the methods to control flying swords, Zhao Hai has to recognize how formidable the Cultivation Realm was. The ease of use was incomparable. With this newfound ability, Zhao Hai’s ability to use Liquid Silver has increased significantly.

Actually, there were a lot of formation methods in the Cultivation Realms, and there were also a lot of formation methods to use in controlling flying swords. But the key to mastering control over flying swords and magic artifacts lie in their formation cores.

As long as Zhao Hai makes use of this formation core, he can use Liquid Silver like a flying sword. These formation cores apply differently to different weapons. Take the golden light sword, for example, because of the materials used being of the earth element, its formation core was tailored to benefit the earth element. Therefore, the sword was able to have increased attacking power and speed.

However, Zhao Hai doesn’t actually need to get a hold of so many formations. He only needed to grasp these formation cores and replace the others with the Machine Field’s magic formations. Moreover, its resulting might wasn’t any worse than the original.

Zhao Hai spent the past few days practicing how to control Liquid Silver with this new method.

Naturally, since Liquid Silver was Zhao Hai’s life source weapon, it didn’t need a formation core to be operated. But now that it had a formation core, it seems like it had been installed with a small computer. It was now much easier for Zhao Hai to control it.

After days of uninterrupted practice, Zhao Hai was now able to control Liquid Silver as though it was an extension of his arm. This allowed Zhao Hai to add some more variations in his attacks. Liquid Silver was made with special materials and special methods. Even if it was placed in the Cultivation Realm, it can still be considered as a high-ranked weapon. These kinds of weapons would be treasured items in sects. But Zhao Hai has one currently in use.

It can be said that at this moment, Liquid Silver’s abilities were being displayed to their full potential. Zhao Hai’s attacks were now more comprehensive. In addition to his fist techniques, Zhao Hai now has Liquid Silver for offense. Moreover, Liquid Silver can use the Space to return to Zhao Hai’s side. This increases Zhao Hai fighting strength. Compared to before, it can be said that his strength has increased by close to a double.

Five days later, Zhao Hai headed out to attend the ranking tournament. At this time, Xiong Li and the others were also heading back to the Machine Field under Ma Rulong’s arrangements. Not only Xiong Li and the others, besides Zhao Hai and Ma Rulong, only ten team leaders were left. The rest of them had returned to the Machine Field.

Zhao Hai knew that Xiong Li and the others were going to study their newly acquired Cultivation Methods. This was also what he wanted to see.

After going out, Zhao Hai went with Ma Rulong. What they needed to do right now was head to the transmission formation in order to go to the Void Arena.

When Zhao Hai and the rest of the Machine Field’s delegates headed out, they immediately attracted the attention of Seamount City’s Cultivators. They knew where Zhao Hai was headed, so their vision followed behind him. However, nobody dared to cause trouble. Those who dared to look for trouble were known to be killed.

Zhao Hai had already made several moves that caused everyone to know that he wasn’t polite to his enemies. He made it known that he wasn’t someone that could be offended.

While Ma Rulong and Zhao Hai headed to the transmission, they chatted with each other.

Zhao Hai looked at the Cultivators around them then looked at Ma Rulong and said, “Team Leader, Boss Xiong and the others, have they been sent back properly?”

Ma Rulong smiled faintly and said, “Rest assured, they’re fine. I heard that after returning, they immediately closed up. They should be practicing right now. You don’t need to worry.”

Zhao Hao nodded. Then he said, “We already reached an agreement. After the competition ends, we’ll go to the Six Realms Battlefield to have a stroll. I really want to see how strong the experts of the other realms really are.”

Chapter 1259: Void Arena

When Ma Rulong heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but look him in the eyes. Then after some time, he sighed and said, “Alright, I’ll take care of it. Don’t make me lose face.”

Zhao Hai smiled and didn’t say anything. At this time, the group arrived at the transmission formation. Although the formation was managed by someone from the Seamount Faction, they didn’t dare provoke Zhao Hai’s group. They had decided to not mess with Zhao Hai anymore.

When the group stepped on the transmission formation, a white light flashed before they disappeared. Seeing the group vanish, people in Seamount City began to hum in discussion. It was because of Zhao Hai that they didn’t dare make a sound.

If someone were to tell them that they would be frightened of the Machine Field’s people before this, then they would laugh at it as though it was a joke. But now, they were even too scared to talk. This was because of how the Cultivation Realm had been looking down on the Machine Field.

However, after Zhao Hai arrived, the people from the Cultivation Realm began to understand that there were some people from the Machine Field that they couldn’t annoy.

…

A white light flashed as Zhao Hai and the others appeared on a huge slab of asteroid. Just as they appeared, a voice greeted them, “So it’s the Machine Field. Please take a rest.”

Zhao Hai and the others looked at the direction of the voice and saw a Cultivator standing not far away from them. Also, they actually know of this person. It was the person who was sent to Seamount City to calculate the points.

Fan Yi was a member of the Six Realm Beginner’s Competition’s committee. He was specifically responsible for receiving visitors and team leaders this time. Naturally, it’s possible for him to be there when the Machine Field arrived.

Ma Rulong held his fist and said, “Thank you for the trouble.” Then he followed Fan Yi to where they would be resting.

The asteroid that they were in wasn’t very big. It also had a transmission formation that would lead them to a larger asteroid not too far away. On this larger asteroid was a house. However, this house wasn’t built but instead it was carved.

The shape of this asteroid was originally an irregular oval. But now, the upper half of this asteroid was carved into the appearance of a house.

Looking at this house, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile as he said, “This place is very good. I expected us to live in a cave, I didn’t think that it would be a house. Powerful experts of the Cultivation Realm are truly formidable. Such a huge asteroid was actually carved into this structure. It’s extraordinary.”

Fan Yi interjected with pride, “Mister Zhao Hai, actually, this region was filled with smaller asteroids. Because of those small asteroids, this region was filled with danger. These asteroids would hit larger asteroids, creating more asteroids. Later on, after the Void Arena was made, all those small asteroids had been cleared. The surrounding gravity had been changed as well to ensure that no asteroids collide.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Putting it into perspective, the power of the Cultivation Realm’s top experts is really admirable. Just a few moves from them greatly improved our lives.”

Fan Yi didn’t boast this time, instead he smiled and said, “Mister Zhao Hai got first place in the current ranking and has the strength to face a silverback gold-winged but alone. You can already be considered as a powerful expert in the Cultivation Realm. If Mister comes to the Cultivation Realm, you can already establish your own school.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “This Zhao Hai doesn’t have such huge ambitions. Open a sect and establish a school? Hehe. A lot of Cultivators see me as an enemy. If I really moved here, I’m afraid I’ll be killed before establishing a school.”

Although Ma Rulong didn’t interrupt Fan Yi and Zhao Hai’s conversation, he was actually nervous. When he heard that Zhao Hai admired the skills of the Cultivators, Ma Rulong became nervous for a moment. Zhao Hai had been in the Machine Field for less than a year. If it weren’t for Margaret, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t have anything tying himself to the Machine Field. If we moved to the Cultivation Realm, then the Machine Field would be losing a lot.

However, Zhao Hai’s next words reassured Ma Rulong. It was impossible for Zhao Hai to move to the Cultivation Realm, Ma Rulong was certain of it.

As long as Zhao Hai doesn’t move to the Cultivation Realm, everything else would be a breeze. Ma Rulong had this mentality because Zhao Hai was just too powerful. He could kill Core Formation Experts, much less those weaker.

With Zhao Hai present, the practitioners in the Machine Field would have hope. If Zhao Hai really moved to the Cultivation Realm, then the spiritual impact to the Machine Field would be huge. Although Ma Rulong had been in the Cultivation Realm all this time and had limited understanding about the current state of the Machine Field, he knew that Zhao Hai’s reputation in the realm had reached an unprecedented height. There were now a lot of young people who look up to Zhao Hai as their idol.

If Zhao Hai were to suddenly join the Cultivation Realm, then it would be a huge shock to External Halls of the Machine Field. This would make people think that the Machine Field had no future for them. Once that happens, then people from External Halls might move to the Cultivation Realm as well. This would spell disaster for the Machine Field.

Whether Ma Rulong wanted it to be or not, but Zhao Hai was now the banner of the Machine Field. This young man had a huge influence on the youth of the Machine Field.

This particular house was prepared for the Machine Field. People from the other realms had their own places arranged for them. So after leading Zhao Hai’s group here, Fan Yi left.

To be honest, the decorations of the house wasn’t very good. It can even be said to be simple, very true to the style of the Cultivation Realm. In the Cultivation Realm, gorgeous houses were almost nonexistent. This was because beautiful houses would make people distracted. And being distracted was the last thing that a Cultivator wanted.

On the other hand, Cultivators would build their houses on geographically beautiful places. This was also one of the obsessions of the Cultivators.

After picking a room, Zhao Hai entered it and looked at its interior. There really wasn’t anything great inside. The room was very simple. It only had a table, a chair, and a few ornaments. The lack of aesthetics would make people speechless.

Zhao Hai went out of his room and then stood on the roof to look at the surroundings of the asteroid. Around the asteroid were other asteroids. However, these asteroids seem to have their own trajectory that didn’t interfere with others. Moreover, on these asteroids, Zhao Hai could see that houses were being carved out. There were even some where rows of seats were carved. It seems to be made for spectators.

And in the center of these asteroids was a very large asteroid. This asteroid was enormous. It can even be classified as a small planet. However, this asteroid wasn’t a complete sphere, only half of one. This was because this asteroid’s top part was cut cleanly and turned into a platform, this asteroid was the Void Arena.

At this time, Ma Rulong walked besides Zhao Hai. He looked at the Void Arena and said, “I heard that the Void Arena is formed by a single sword from a Sword Cultivator. Such strength can only be reached by a salvo from a battleship fleet.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Right. The Cultivation Realm is indeed very powerful. Especially their use of magic artifacts, which is beyond the Machine Field’s technology. I think we should study the Cultivation Realm’s formations and use them in our battleships.”

Ma Rulong nodded and said, “A lot of people wanted to do that. But unfortunately, after Senior Leng Wuyeng’s matter, the Cultivation Realm had increased their pressure on the Machine Field. If they discover one of us studying their formations and manage to escape back to the Machine Field, the Cultivators would do all they can to chase them down. Therefore, until now, we don’t have much information about the Cultivation Realm’s formations. Additionally, the Machine Field has too few high-level materials. So even if we use the Cultivation Realm’s formations, we still wouldn’t be able to match the Cultivators. So even if we can use the Cultivation Realm’s formations, some still opt to use magic formations. Because of this, people drifted away from using the Cultivation Realm’s formations and instead just used them as reference to improve magic formations.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “That can be a good thing. What’s good for others isn’t necessarily good for us. Only those that suit us matter. We can just take all of what’s good about other methods and discard the rest. With this, the Machine Field can slowly develop.”

Ma Rulong nodded. Although his face had no expression, his heart was actually glad. This was because Zhao Hai was speaking about the Machine Field as though he belonged to it. This meant that he regarded himself as a person of the realm. For Ma Rulong this was very good news.

Zhao Hai continued, “However, I don’t agree with the attitude of the Higher-ups. They seem to think that the practitioners of the Machine Field are inferior compared to the other realms. Therefore, their attitude towards us is neither cold nor hot. From what I can see, the Machine Field has the strength to compete with the other realms ever since it was formed. However, the realm’s higher-ups are always focused on mechs and battleships, ignoring our Mages and Warriors.”

Ma Rulong looked at Zhao Hai but didn’t say anything. Zhao Hai looked at Ma Rulong and said, “I reckon it’s because mechs and battleships are too tied up to a lot of people’s interests. Because of this interest, the higher-ups decided to suppress Mages and Warriors. After all, who wants to lose their benefits?”

Ma Rulong looked at Zhao Hai in a bit of shock. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to say these things. To be honest, Zhao Hai sounded like a Machine Field native. Immediately, Ma Rulong’s image of Zhao Hai blurred once more. It seems like another layer of fog was covering his true identity.

Chapter 1260: Doesn’t Want To Change Too Much

Changes in terms(my bad): Demon Realm -> Devil Realm(Mo), Beast Realm -> Demon Realm(Yao), Elves -> Sprites, still reading forward to see if Spirit Race = Elves. No precise description given yet.

Zhao Hai told Ma Rulong this in order to see his response. If Ma Rulong was shocked, then this meant that he guessed right. If Ma Rulong was confused, then this represents that Zhao Hai’s guess was wrong, or that Ma Rulong was unaware of this matter.

In the end, Zhao Hai was able to get his answer – he guessed right!

Upon seeing Ma Rulong’s shocked expression, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but bitterly smile. It seems like the higher-ups of the Machine Field suppressed people for a long time already. Moreover, this wasn’t news otherwise Ma Rulong wouldn’t have such an expression.

As for why some Ascenders had yet to know about this, Zhao Hai had some guesses. First was that they haven’t felt any suppression done to them. Another reason was that the Ascenders had not reached a high enough position in the Machine Field. High positions in the Machine Field had always been controlled by the natives. Things like suppressing Ascenders couldn’t be done on a large scale, otherwise Ascenders might revolt.

After Ascendants ascend to the Machine Field, they will find out that the environment that they ended up in was much better compared to before in all aspects. They would also find out that if they wanted benefits, then they would have to work hard practicing. Because of this, Ascenders place great importance in cultivation. If these Ascenders were to find out that their path ahead was being blocked by the Machine Field’s higher-ups, then these Ascenders would certainly revolt.

In the Machine Field, various great families would have external halls. And the majority of the members of these external halls were ascenders. This was a collective strength that cannot be ignored. If these Ascenders were to revolt, then the damage to the Machine Field would be enormous.

Most importantly, if these Ascenders were to revolt, the other realms would certainly add fuel to the fire. The Machine Field would be destroyed in no time.

Because of this, although the Machine Field was suppressing people, the methods they used were different. They wouldn’t make it clear that they were suppressing you, they would even lift an Ascenders status sometimes. This would make Ascenders think that the realm was looking out for their well being.

The higher-ups of the Machine Field had always done this, and they had done their job well. They haven’t been found nor highly suspected. So when Zhao Hai expressed his view, Ma Rulong was shaken.

Zhao Hai looked at Ma Rulong, he smiled bitterly and said, “I think the legacy left behind by Senior Leng Wuyeng was very good. Mechs and Battleships during his time couldn’t compare to what they are now. So the main strength of the Machine Field at that time are the Mages and Warriors. It seems like Senior Leng Wuyeng took note of the losses incurred during that time. During the war, 13,000 battleships were lost. With each battleship being manned by about 1000 people, they lost more or less 13 million people. On the other hand, Mages and Warriors that died during the war numbered 200 to 300 million. Such casualties showed the true fighting force of the Machine Field. It can be said that during that war, battleships were mere blockades against the Cultivators while the Mages and Warriors sacrificed their lives to drive them back. If it weren’t for this reason, Senior Leng Wuyeng wouldn’t have tried to make Liquid Silver during the late stages of his life. He wants to enhance the strength of Mages and Warriors. Senior Leng Wuyeng doesn’t want the Cultivation Realm to suppress the Machine Field. He wanted the Machine Field to be treated at the same level as the Cultivation Realm, or even higher.”

After speaking up to this point, Zhao Hai stopped, then he sighed and said, “But afterwards, people only saw how small the losses incurred by the battleships and mechs, so they see them as formidable. They failed to see the true fighting force of the Machine Field. After that,  large scale improvements were done to Mechs and Battleships while practitioners were marginalized. Moreover, the manufacturing of Mechs and Battleships gave enormous benefits to those in the supply chain. Those higher-ups probably knew about these benefits. So they didn’t promote cultivation and instead backed the production of Mechs and Battleships. Because of this, the Machine Field became the weakest realm when it came to Cultivation. Moreover, people in the Machine Field look down on practitioners. People only saw our practitioners being defeated time and time again by the other realms. The people failed to see that the resources allocated to the Machine Field’s practitioners was only 1% compared to the resources allocated by the Cultivation Realm to its Cultivators.”

Ma Rulong looked at Zhao Hai, he didn’t know what to say. Even he didn’t remember these casualty numbers, but Zhao Hai did. Ma Rulong couldn’t help but be surprised.

Most importantly, if Ascenders were to hear about what Zhao Hai said, the consequences might be dreadful.

Ma Rulong didn’t say a word for quite some time. When his emotions had calmed down, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, if you thought about this, then why didn’t you tell anyone?” He found out that his voice was a bit dry, the words that came out of his mouth didn’t sound like his.

Zhao Hai glanced at Ma Rulong and then turned to the Void Arena and said, “Tell anyone? What benefits would it bring me? What good would it do to the Machine Field? To be honest, although the Machine Field has been suppressing the Ascenders, its treatment of commoners is very good. If the Machine Field turns its effort to the practitioners, then the situation of its commoners might become the same as those in the Cultivation Realm. If I spread the information out, then Ascenders might cause a disturbance. When that time comes, the commoners would be the ones suffering the most. And if the Machine Field is conquered by the other realms, then the commoners would live horrendous lives. Therefore, if I gain enough ability in the future, I’ll try to change things in a way that preserves the current lifestyle of the commoners.”

Ma Rulong felt relief. At the same time, the way he looked at Zhao Hai changed. Before, he would look at Zhao Hai with appreciation and maybe hope. But now, he looked at Zhao Hai in awe.

Ma Rulong was aware of Zhao Hai’s potential. Not even a year after he ascended, Zhao Hai was able to eliminate a Core Formation Cultivator. This was something that most people wouldn’t achieve in their entire lives. After seeing Zhao Hai close up multiple times, Ma Rulong thought that he was a cultivating madman. But after hearing Zhao Hai’s words, Ma Rulong was made aware that Zhao Hai wasn’t just a cultivating madman, he was also a person who thought about the Machine Field’s affairs. And it seems like his contemplations had run very deep.

Ma Rulong was shocked by Zhao Hai’s sheer potential. In the past, he thought that Zhao Hai’s cultivation speed was monstrous. But now it seems like he was still underestimating Zhao Hai. It wasn’t his cultivation speed that was monstrous, Zhao Hai himself was a monster!

Ma Rulong wiped a cold sweat from his forehead then he said, “I didn’t expect you to have thought this far. But unfortunately, things have already gone to this point. Ever since Senior Leng Wuyeng passed away, nobody has been able to succeed him. There have been some people who tried to change the state of the Machine Field, but all of them failed. Because of the Mechs and the Battleships, the Machine Field’s higher-ups had formed an airtight network with each other. So even if they had some internal fights now and then, their cumulative strength can still shake the realm. They’re fully capable of suppressing anyone.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I understand. I don’t intend on changing the Machine Field’s current status quo, but I just want practitioners to be treated better. Why should we choose one over the other? If the Machine Field has strong battleships as well as powerful practitioners, then how could the entire World of Cultivation underestimate us? If given the chance, we might even conquer all the realms.”

Ma Rulong didn’t say anything. Although he was excited by Zhao Hai’s words, he knew that this couldn’t be achieved in a short time. After all, cultivation cannot increase in one or two days. Zhao Hai wasn’t monstrous enough to take the entire World of Cultivation in a blink of an eye.

At this time, Fan Yi flew over to the roof and then gave the two a bow before saying, “The tournament is about to begin. Please follow me, we need to draw lots for the Machine Field.”

Zhao Hai and Ma Rulong nodded. They were aware that the ranking tournament of the competition was the same as the Machine Field’s. But besides drawing lots for one’s opponent, the distribution of seats needed to be drawn as well. Once selected, that spectator spot would belong to whichever realm drew it, no other realm was allowed to sit there.

It can be said that people from all walks of life were watching the tournament. Even some people from the Machine Field came. But since they were afraid of disturbing Zhao Hai, they waited for their spectator seats

Zhao Hai’s assigned seat was at a small asteroid. There were a few dozen seats here but less than a hundred. Besides Zhao Hai, Ma Rulong, and the remaining team leaders, nobody else was here. The same treatment was given to all participants.

Zhao Hai looked all around them and discovered that there were several asteroids around them. Sat on them were people wearing Mage and Warrior Clothing. It was clear that this group of asteroids had been drawn by the Machine Field.

Before this, Zhao Hai heard that a lot of people from the Machine Field came to watch. However, he didn’t expect so many people. From what he can see, there’s no less than a few thousand people from the Machine Field watching.

One must know that it wasn’t easy coming to the Cultivation Realm from the Machine Field. For so many people to come certainly surprised Zhao Hai.

Ma Rulong looked at their surroundings, then he sighed and said, “I didn’t expect this many people to come. In the past, whenever the Six Realms Beginner Competition was held here, almost nobody from the Machine Field came. Besides the participant and the team leaders, there’s no one else. The Machine Field’s delegates looked solitary in the empty region while the other realms were surrounded by their people. Ah, let’s forget about that….”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “That’s because everyone has no hope of winning before. But now that there’s hope of winning, all of them want to see it for themselves. Oh, the drawing has begun.”

Sure enough, just as Zhao Hai finished talking, a robot appeared on the Void Arena. Then the eyes of this robot projected upwards, revealing two people. Upon seeing the two combatants, Zhao Hai immediately lost interest. Since none of the two were him, he didn’t care. He just sat down and didn’t bother himself with the fight.

On the other hand, Ma Rulong and the others kept standing. They were looking straight into the arena. Before long, two people appeared. These two looked like Cultivators. Although this was the Six Realms Beginner Competition and people from the other realms were among the top 100, the top ranking was still being dominated by the Cultivation Realm. Of the top 100, 85 of them were from the Cultivation Realm. As for the remaining 15, six were taken by the Machine Field, three were from the Devil Realm, two from the Demon Realm, two from the Spirit Realm, and two from the Sprite Realm. In this case, two Cultivators facing each other wasn’t strange.

The battle siren immediately rang. What differentiates the Void Arena compared to other arenas was the fact that it didn’t have any protective barriers. Because of this, people could see the action with their eyes. Those strong enough could even hear what’s happening in the arena.

However, because of the sheer size of the Void Arena, it was impossible for the two to go out of bounds. And because of how huge the arena was, the two combatants have great freedom in their actions.

After the two combatants entered the arena, they didn’t talk much and just attacked immediately. It can be seen that this wasn’t their first battle. Both parties were aware of how strong the other was. Because of this, the clash between the two was quite lively.

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything about battle as he just sat there with a smile on his face. Meanwhile, Ma Rulong was looking at the battle with a calm face. Although the two Cultivators were showcasing their impressive strength, Ma Rulong couldn’t sense any malice from their moves. It was as if the two were conversing instead of fighting.

Ma Rulong turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, can you see this? They seem to be sparring.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “They are indeed sparring. Cultivators dominated the top 100 for many years. So all they had to do was decide on who was the strongest. But now, the top positions were taken by people like me and Tu Mietan. Naturally, those people would want to deal with us, so they won’t reveal their abilities this early.”

Chapter 1261: Sprite vs Formation Seal Cultivator

Changes in terms(my bad): Demon Realm -> Devil Realm(Mo), Beast Realm -> Demon Realm(Yao), Elves -> Sprites, still reading forward to see if Spirit Race = Elves. No precise description given yet.

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Ma Rulong frowned and said, “So I’m right. If this is the case, then a Sect will certainly lose out. One of them will lose and they will have a lower ranking in the tournament. Isn’t that bad for them?”

Zhao Hai sneered and said, “Not necessarily. As long as they reach an agreement, these Sects can divide the spoils among themselves. This is so that they can suppress the other realms to the bottom of the rankings. In the end, wouldn’t they still benefit?”

Ma Rulong stayed quiet. This was because he knew that Zhao Hai was right. Cultivators normally fought with each other, but when faced with the other realms, they would unite.

At this time, the two people in the arena had finished their spar. The loser was defeated by just a small margin. The person who lost had a sad expression while glee was seen on the face of the winner. No magic artifacts were sent out, nor were there any pills used. There weren’t even paper talismans or other consumable items. The battle was as simple as it can be.

It was at this time that everyone else had the same idea as Ma Rulong – these Cultivators were just acting out a play. The other realms couldn’t help but get angry, but they couldn’t do anything since the Cultivation Realm didn’t break any rules. In fact, even if the Cultivators don’t act and one of them just forfeited, it would still be fine. This play was done just to give others face.

Many people couldn’t help but curse deep inside. However, they didn’t protest since they knew that it was useless. In their eyes, what the Cultivators were doing was much more shameless than the withdrawal of the Machine Field’s participants.

The people from the other realms initially thought that it was the Machine Field that was being shameless. Besides Zhao Hai, the other five participants didn’t have any intention to fight at all. They were able to get a lot of bugs because Zhao Hai gave it to them. And after they got on the top rankings, they forfeited immediately. Although they only got the final five places, there were still rich rewards waiting for them. Also, these rewards were pre-arranged before the competition began so nobody can change it. These rewards were rich enough to live luxuriously. And because they couldn’t say anything about the Machine Field’s action, they see them as shameless.

However, the Machine Field didn’t violate any rule. The insects were obtained by them from the bugs underground. They followed everything. Moreover, the elimination round allowed teaming up and the division of spoils.

The Cultivation Realm and the Machine Field exploited the loopholes in the competition’s rules. Nobody could say anything and they just had to accept it.

At this time, the drawing of the second battle had ended. The participants were still Cultivators. And after the two put up a small fight, they left the arena. They merely made a few moves.

This went on until the tenth battle. This was where a true battle will happen. One side was a Cultivator while the other was a Sprite.

Sprites in the World of Cultivation were different compared to Elves in the lower realms. Once Elves in the lower realms ascend, they can at most look like someone from the Spirit Realm. The World of Cultivation’s Sprites weren’t humanoid. Instead they were their own special race. They resembled Cai’er and were no taller than a person’s arm. They had winged backs and were very small. Each one of them looked like dolls.[1]

However, if you treat them like dolls, then you will suffer immensely. These people weren’t dolls, they were gods of slaughter.

Sprite attacks had their own special characteristics. They can communicate with a lot of things and use them to attack. This was also the origin of the name Sprites.[2]

The Sprites’ ability to communicate didn’t only limit them to living things, this also includes the air, rocks, and all visible and invisible things.

This was an inherent skill of the Sprites that no other race had. However, since they also control ascending points, all Ascenders in the Sprite Realm can be part of the Sprite Race. Although their cultivation method is different from Sprites in the lower realms, as long as they were the same race, they all had this skill.[3]

Although it might seem like other races have the same skill as the Sprites, like humans that can control metal, this metal manipulation was on a very ordinary level.

The skill of the Sprites is much more powerful than simple metal manipulation. Not only could they manipulate metal, they could breathe life into it. They can also instill intelligence on the material. This was what made the Sprites terrifying.

Zhao Hai was already aware of the Sprite Race’s abilities even before seeing one of them. However, he has yet to see one fight. Their battle style would certainly enlarge his insight.

When the Sprite  and the Cultivator got on the arena, they gave each other a salute. Then the two didn’t speak. Zhao Hai then saw the Sprite waving its hand as a transparent humanoid appeared in front of it.

Right, it was transparent, completely clear. Only through spiritual force could this humanoid’s presence be felt. Ordinary people wouldn’t be able to see it.

Zhao Hai stared for a moment. This was because he could feel the invisible being absorbing the surrounding energy. And within a very short time, the invisible being was able to reach Foundation Establishment-level strength. Then it slowly stopped absorbing energy.

This was the first time that Zhao Hai was able to see a technique like this. It’s quite strange. It was one of those odd things that made Zhao Hai curious. Now, he wants to see how strong this being was during a fight.

On the other hand, the Cultivator took out his items. What Zhao Hai felt strange was the items that the Cultivator took out were jade charms.

Right, jade charms, a complete set of 9 jade charms. One big charm and eight small ones. The Cultivator held the big jade charm in his hand while the other eight were rotating around it.

It didn’t take long before the two sides began fighting. Zhao Hai was now aware of the strength of the invisible being. This being was actually able to control an invisible type of energy akin to air but not really air. Moreover, not only could this invisible being control energy, it can also turn it into various shapes to attack its enemy. In this regard, it was akin to Zhao Hai’s Liquid Silver.

At the same time, the jade charms of the Cultivator were clearly not ordinary. The eight smaller charms contain eight different kinds of energy. These energies were respectively, heaven, ground, fire, thunder, wind, water, mountain, lake.

On the other hand, the large jade charm operates the other eight. This was the center of the eight charms forming the eight trigrams. In the middle was the Cultivator that controlled them all.

Seeing the Cultivator’s methods, Zhao Hai understood that this was a Formation Seal Cultivator. He should have come from the Cultivation Realm’s Sealing School.

The Sealing School had the same uniqueness as Sword Schools. They were a special school in the Cultivation Realm. Sword Cultivators treat the sword as their life partner and specially nurture it to grow. There might be some special Sects that might have other means to use a sword, but they were swords nonetheless.

As for the Sealing School, just like its name suggests, specialize in seals. They make sealing talismans and then use them as weapons. They take sealing talismans as their specialty, it’s the area in which the Sect researched much of.

Among these Sealing Schools were special kinds of people. These were Formation Seal Cultivators. These Cultivators specialize in making formation charms first and talismans second. They assemble formations into their charms in order to fight their enemy. The combination of the sealing charms and formations makes them strong in the battlefield.

There was a fierce struggle between two evenly matched opponents. Both sides were formidable in their own right. Zhao Hai discovered that the Sprite was still somewhat controlling the invisible being after summoning it. Although the being had some sort of wisdom, it was still the Sprite’s weapon. It was just like artifact spirits of Cultivators.

Moreover, Zhao Hai could see that Sprites were a difficult race to deal with. Their attacks also have special characteristics. Besides the Sprite’s transparent summon, once in a while two stone golems would come out and attack the Cultivator. These stone golems were also quite strong. This fighting style expanded Zhao Hai’s vision once more.

It was at this point that Zhao Hai discovered that no race in the World of Cultivation was easy to deal with. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have been able to keep their own territories. This explains why Cultivators were still wary of them.

The Formation Seal Cultivator’s methods were also uncommon. Besides the eight trigrams jade charm, he also had a lot of magical artifacts in use. Naturally, the majority of it were jade charms while some were talismans. Moreover, each item had great might.

After seeing the Formation Seal Cultivator making moves, Zhao Hai began to have some general understanding about their methods. These charms weren’t consumable goods, instead only low-level talismans were single-use. Higher-level talismans and charms require high-level materials to be used. Single-use talismans that were powerful were very rare.

At the same time, Zhao Hai could also see into the methods of the Sprites. Although they can communicate to all kinds of things, they should also have their own attributes. They will choose to communicate with the things that were compatible with them. They would inject wisdom into that certain thing and then cultivate them. It was just like how a Cultivator grows his Life Source Weapon. Instead of themselves, the Sprites Cultivate their summons or familiars. It was just like how Zhao Hai strengthens his Undead. It was just that the methods of the Sprites were much more powerful.

* * *

The two have the same characters 精灵 but it’s evident that they weren’t the same. So I separated the two into Elves and Sprites.

Elves here are two characters 精灵(Jīnglíng) meaning fine, refined, or smart spirit

I think this refers to Elves with the same form

Chapter 1262: Zhao Hai vs Jiang Tian

Changes in terms(my bad): Demon Realm -> Devil Realm(Mo), Beast Realm -> Demon Realm(Yao), Elves -> Sprites, still reading forward to see if Spirit Race = Elves. No precise description given yet.

The two sides were intensely clashing. This wasn’t a spar like previous battles, this was a real fight.

In the end, the Cultivator gained the upper hand and defeated the Sprite. But in order to win, the Cultivator had to go all out. From Zhao Hai’s calculation, the Cultivator used more than 300 paper talismans as well as about 20 jade talismans. And also, he used a single-use jade charm.

Zhao Hai was now certain that the Cultivators had united and had supplied their participants with rich resources to defeat the other realms. They fully intend on suppressing the others.

At this time, the 11th pair was drawn. When the pairing was revealed, everyone couldn’t help but pause. This was because the two that had been drawn were Zhao Hai and Jiang Tian!

The reason why people were stunned was because Zhao Hai’s appearance was dreaded by the Cultivators. Although Devil Realm’s Tu Mietan was strong, people don’t care much about him. In the end, Tu Mietan was still a Foundation Establishment Cultivator. On the other hand, Zhao Hai was able to kill a Core Formation expert, such difference was very clear.

Zhao Hai didn’t have much of a reaction upon seeing his name. He just smiled and flew towards the arena. As he was flying, everyone’s gazes were focused on him. This also made Jiang Tian feel uncomfortable as he flew towards the arena.

Jiang Tian was a son of heaven. He was a genius from the lower realms. After he ascended, he became even more focused on cultivating. Because of this, Jiang Tian was very proud. Besides some people, he wouldn’t pay attention to anyone.

Although Zhao Hai’s legendary exploits have been flooding his ears recently, Jiang Tan wasn’t convinced that Zhao Hai was invincible. His weapons and items had been supplemented and replaced, which made him even more confident. He wants to let everyone know that he was still a genius and the most talented among every participant present.

This arrogant mentality can’t be developed in just one day. Jiang Tian received compliments from everyone ever since he was a child. Because of this, he gradually formed this arrogance. And it would be difficult to get rid of it.

Zhao Hai slowly fell on the arena. He really didn’t expect to face Jiang Tian in his first battle. Jiang Tian was one of the powerful young experts of the Cultivation Realm. But since Zhao Hai has seen the recording of Jiang Tian analyzing what happened to Mu Dan in the underground caves, Zhao Hai was certain that he was an arrogant person. He was far from Suo Liancheng’s attitude.

Jiang Tian and Zhao Hai stepped on the arena at almost the same time. Jiang Tian looked at Zhao Hai’s ordinary face and couldn’t help but snort coldly, then he said, “Zhao Hai, you’ve been quite famous recently. I just don’t know if you really are that strong.”

Zhao Hai heard Jiang Tian and just smiled faintly as he said, “Am I strong? Mister Jiang will soon know about that. Is Mister Jiang ready to begin?”

Jiang Tian sneered, “I wanted to give you more time to live. But since you can’t wait, then die!” After he said that, a flying sword appeared in his hand. Then he commanded it to attack Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t take Liquid Silver out. Instead he waved his hand and caused a 100-layer formation to appear. Then an arrow rain burst out to meet the sword.

Jiang Tian took out a shield-shaped artifact and used it to block in front of him while his sword attacked Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai waved his hand and then a 200-layer formation appeared that became a big shield.

Zhao Hai didn’t use Liquid Silver nor did he use his fist techniques. He was using formations to  fight Jiang Tian. Even so, Jiang Tian still felt that Zhao Hai’s actions were very strong. At this point, he had already used five magic artifacts while Zhao Hai was still fighting barehanded. Such contrast caused Jiang Tian to feel uncomfortable.

Jiang Tian thought himself to be heaven’s favored son. Besides a few people like Suo Liancheng, nobody was his opponent. However, Zhao Hai’s appearance caused him to understand what a monster really was.

People had mixed feelings as they looked at the arena below. Everyone can see that Jiang Tian was doing his best. With Jiang Tian’s present strength as well as the quality of artifacts that he took out, most Foundation Establishment experts would have no chance against him. However, he was being held back by Zhao Hai who was unarmed. This only shows how formidable Zhao Hai really was.

At this time, Zhao Hai felt that it was time to stop playing around. He waved his hand as a 1000-layer formation appeared in front of him. Then when the formation activated, a huge fire dragon burst out and threw itself towards Jiang Tian.

Jiang Tian could feel the powerful aura of the fire dragon. He couldn’t help but be shocked. Then he retrieved his flying sword and at the same time he took out a shield-shaped magic artifact. There were also two jade talismans in his hand, but he had yet to use them.

The fire dragon swung its claws and bit its teeth towards Jiang Tian. And while Jiang Tian was focused on the dragon, a huge stone golem appeared behind him. As soon as the golem appeared, it gave out a punch towards Jiang Tian.

While he was under his shield, Jiang Tian suddenly felt danger coming from his back. He immediately blocked the golem’s fist. However, this caused the shield to be occupied defending the back. The fire dragon used this opportunity to charge forwards.

The unexpected attack caught Jiang Tian off-guard. The moment he was able to respond, the fire dragon was already in front of him.

Jiang Tian grunted, then he shattered the jade talisman in his hand. As soon as the jade talisman was shattered, sword energy immediately spread out and cut the fire dragon. The fire dragon cried out pitifully before it and the sword energy vanished.

However, the fire dragon’s actions caused the spectators to stare. They knew that the fire dragon was made from magic, not a true lifeform. So why did the fire dragon cry out when it was cut? Wasn’t this too strange?

Meanwhile, Zhao Hai felt that the sword energy released by the talisman had Core Formation-level strength. No wonder it could cut a 1000-layer formation fire dragon.

But Zhao Hai wasn’t startled by this result. Instead he waved his hands once more as another 1000-layer formation appeared. This formation set formed into a humanoid being. This humanoid being wore golden full-body armor. In its hand was a double crescent halberd. The humanoid being was the same color as iron and it towered at ten feet tall. When it appeared, it immediately attacked Jiang Tian with its halberd.[1]

Jiang Tian didn’t expect Zhao Hai to release such strange magic. However, he knew that he had to prepare. Paper talismans appeared in his hand. And with a wave, he sent the talismans towards the armored giant. At the same time, he controlled his flying sword to enlarge and attack.

If it was any other event, Jiang Tian’s methods would have earned him the appreciation of the spectators. After all, being able to swifty use magic artifacts, charms, and talismans was something noteworthy for a Foundation Establishment Cultivator.

Jiang Tian’s paper talismans erupted into lightning and struck the armored giant. However, it seems like the armored giant didn’t feel it as it continued to go forward to attack Jiang Tian. At this time, Jiang Tian’s flying sword enlarged itself to about ten meters long. Then it went overhead in order to cut the armored giant.

But at this moment, the golden armored giant raised its halberd and struck Jiang Tian’s sword. A loud sound was heard before the sword was thrown outwards. Jiang Tian’s face was pale. If one were to look closely, then they would discover that Jiang Tian’s sword had a chip that was the size of a grain of rice.

Jiang Tian’s sword wasn’t just an ordinary sword where a small chip can be fixed by a few hammering and polish. This flying sword was a precious treasure. Damage done to it would make the sword’s ability plummet. And at the same time, the backlash caused Jiang Tian to be injured.

However, this wasn’t the end. The golden giant didn’t care that Jiang Tian was injured. It raised its halberd once more as it smashed it downwards.

Jiang Tian’s facial color changed. His face showed grief as he crushed another jade talisman. Then sword energy was released once more to cut the armored giant. Naturally, its might was equal to a Core Formation Expert’s attack.

The armored giant probably felt danger coming since it changed the trajectory of its halberd to block the attack. But a small click was heard as the sword energy cut the giant’s halberd. Then the sword energy pierced towards the body of the armored giant. After a crunching sound, the sword energy went through the body of the giant, leaving behind a massive hole. Then the sword energy hit Zhao Hai’s shield before disappearing.

Seeing the wound on the armored giant’s body, Jiang Tian began to feel relief. Then his eyes sharpened as he took advantage of the opening to execute his sword art to attack Zhao Hai. Although his flying sword was damaged, it could still be used.

But at this moment, Jiang Tian’s face changed color as he quickly took back his flying sword. This was because he discovered that even if the armored giant had been injured, it wasn’t a living creature. Therefore, it didn’t die from the wound. And instead of blood, particles were flowing down from its wound before restoring the giant’s body. At the same time, its halberd has been repaired to its original form. This change caused Jiang Tian to be startled.

Jiang Tian really wished that he could use his shield to protect himself at this time. However, the stone golem was still attacking the shield. This left Jiang Tian with no way to deal with the armored giant in front of him.

* * *

https://external-content.duckduckgo.com/iu/?u=https%3A%2F%2Ftse1.mm.bing.net%2Fth%3Fid%3DOIP.QFaEwwtTCnuikV9fN8aVKQHaE6%26pid%3DApi&f=1

Chapter 1263: I Can Come Back Later

Changes in terms(my bad): Demon Realm -> Devil Realm(Mo), Beast Realm -> Demon Realm(Yao), Elves -> Sprites, still reading forward to see if Spirit Race = Elves. No precise description given yet.

Foundation Establishment Cultivators have limits to how many magic artifacts they can simultaneously use, which was about three. And this was given that the three were only controlled. If one of them was being intensely utilized, then three was impossible.

Jiang Tian’s shield was being attacked by the stone golem while the armored giant was in front of him. Jiang Tian also didn’t dare to use his flying sword to stop that armored giant’s attack. His flying sword had already been damaged by the halberd. If he used the flying sword to block a few more times, then the flying sword would definitely be destroyed.

Upon thinking of this, Jiang Tian received his sword and rook out a ring-type magic artifact. The ring-type artifact defended his entire body. This way, Jiang Tian was able to retrieve his shield artifact. Then when the shield was taken away, he took out a sharp blade and attacked the armored giant. He also used the paper talismans in his hand. He threw them all towards the armored giant as though he was throwing away money.

However, Jiang Tian forgot that Zhao Hai can still release more magic. Therefore, as Jiang Tian was preoccupied by the stone golem and the armored giant, Zhao Hai released another 1000-layer formation. When this formation appeared, a great wave of water came out before it formed into a water giant. Then the newcomer proceeded to attack Jiang TIan.

The methods of this water giant were very strange. It was like the transparent being that the Sprite used in the previous fight. The water giant’s attacks look very soft. However, everyone that was spectating the arena knew that this water giant wasn’t simple.

Jiang Tian also discovered the water giant. His expression was now difficult to look at. Then a fierce light flashed before his eyes as he bit his own tongue and took out some life essence blood. He sprayed his life essence blood on the blade in front of him. Upon being injected by the life essence blood, the blade changed trajectory as it bypassed the armored giant and the water giant to attack Zhao Hai directly.

But at the same time, Jiang Tian’s move caused his ring-shaped defensive artifact to fall. If this attack doesn’t have any effect on Zhao Hai, then Jiang Tian would lose.

Zhao Hai saw Jiang Tian’s approach and couldn’t help but frown. Jiang Tian was actually going all out. Zhao Hai knew clearly how important life essence blood was to Cultivators. Losing life essence blood was a great disadvantage. This would make a Cultivators future path more difficult.

And this consequence was much more significant to a Foundation Establishment Cultivator. It can be said that Jiang Tian was sacrificing his future development with his current action. Cultivators would only use their life essence blood during extremely dangerous situations where life and death was decided in a blink of an eye.

However, this was the ranking tournament of the Six Realms Beginner Competition. This wasn’t a life and death battle. As long as Jiang Tian admits defeat, then Zhao Hai would stop his attacks. But instead of admitting defeat, Jiang Tian used his life essence blood to attack. No matter what angle one looks at, Jiang Tian was having desperate thoughts.

Zhao Hai knew that he now had a heavy enmity with Jiang Tian. Even if he defeated Jiang Tian, then this battle would still affect Jiang Tian’s cultivation. Affecting a Cultivator’s cultivation was akin to endangering their lives. Jiang Tian had sown enmity that cannot be resolved.

Zhao Hai coldly snorted. Since this was an irresolvable enmity, then there’s no need to solve it. There’s only one good way to deal with such enemies, kill them! When he thought of this, Zhao Hai stretched forward and pointed out.

This was an attacking method that was from the tempering fist technique. It wasn’t at full power, but its strength was still very great. Jiang Tian wouldn’t be able to withstand it.

Zhao Hai’s finger crashed through Jiang Tian’s blade and immediately turned it into ash. Then the attack proceeded towards the ring-type artifact. Jiang Tian’s ring-type artifact screeched before it broke. Then seemingly unaffected by everything it passed through before, Zhao Hai’s finger attack hit Jiang Tian’s body. Jiang Tian’s body shook before it fell to the ground, shock was evident in his eyes.

Jiang Tian died expecting Zhao Hai to spare his life. He expected Zhao Hai to not have the guts to kill him in public. He used his life essence blood to attack just to see if it succeeds. If it didn’t then he was prepared to admit defeat. However, he didn’t expect that he wouldn’t given the opportunity to surrender.

There was no rule in the Void Arena that disallowed killing. In the past, when people from the Cultivation Realm dominated the top 100, they rarely battled to death in the arena. And if someone died, it would always be Cultivators killing people from the other realms.

But today’s situation where Zhao Hai killed a Cultivator in front of the crowd never happened before. Even the people from the other realms didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have the courage to do so. Although they weren’t from the Cultivation Realm, they knew that Cultivators were able to kill people from the other realms because they had many methods and were rich in resources.

However, Zhao Hai actually did kill someone on the void arena. He looked at Jiang Tian’s body and then waved his hand, covering it with black gas. Then when the black gas vanished, Jiang Tian’s corpse vanished as well.

Those in the scene weren’t amateurs. Seeing Zhao Hai’s action, they knew that Zhao Hai turned Jiang Tian into the Undead. In other words, Jiang Tian was now Zhao Hai’s Undead.

Hua!

An uproar was heard from all around the arena. Nobody thought that Zhao Hai would be so rampant. Not only did he kill a Cultivator, he also turned him into an Undead in front of all the other Cultivators. Wasn’t this slapping the Cultivation Realm in the face?

Sure enough, just as Zhao Hai received Jiang Tian, a voice was heard, “So brave, Zhao Hai. You dared to kill Jiang Tian!” Then with his voice, sword energy came slashing towards Zhao Hai. This sword energy was similar to the sword energy emitted by the two jade talismans used by Jiang Tian. It was sword energy that had Core Formation strength. The speed of this attack was very fast and its aura was also quite strong.

Zhao Hai coldly snorted, then he pointed his finger and dispelled the sword energy. Then he turned at the Cultivator and said, “The Void Arena is a place of competition and life and death battles. Since he’s too weak to stop my attack, then he deserves to die. If I wasn’t skilled enough and was killed by other people, would you protest? If you want to complain, then come here and let’s fight!” Zhao Hai’s eyes were looking straight towards the Cultivator that sent the sword energy.

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the Cultivator couldn’t help but coldy snort as he said, “Extremely arrogant. You just won a few fights and now you think highly of yourself. But since it’s the day of the tournament, I’ll let you off. I’ll certainly ask you for advice on another day.”

Zhao Hai just sneered. Then he flew towards the Machine Field’s stands and then returned to his seat.

Zhao Hai’s attitude made the other realms see how domineering he actually was. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this formidable.

However, people were quick to analyze what just happened. Zhao Hai didn’t intend to kill Jiang Tian. He has been using magic to fight, it was clear that he had to intention of murder. Otherwise, he would have easily murdered Jiang Tian.

Jiang Tian going all out and using his life essence blood to attack Zhao Hai was clearly the reason why Zhao Hai was angry, and chose to go for the kill. Those who were discerning could understand Zhao Hai’s decision. But nevertheless, they were surprised by the method he used.

There were very few people who challenged the dignity of the Cultivation Realm in front of the Cultivators. The other realms had learned to endure. But if they cannot bear the insults, then they would go for the kill. But they would make sure that the Cultivators don’t find out about the killer.

Zhao Hai was the first to kill a Cultivator in public in several years. However, the people from the other realms calmed down when they remembered that Zhao Hai had already done this before.

Now that they think about it, Zhao Hai had done this act a lot of times before. His killing of Li Chuchen was semi-public, the same was true for his eradication of the five participants from the Three Mountains Alliance. Then there was his victory against Helian Da. But of those who he publicly killed, Helian Da had the greatest weight to his status. Jiang Tian was a rookie, while Helian Da was an Elder of the Three Mountains Alliance. Zhao Hai dared to kill Helian Da, so his actions today shouldn’t be a surprise.

When Zhao Hai returned to his seat, he could feel the piercing looks directed at him. However, he didn’t care as he sat down and then closed his eyes.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s reaction, Ma Rulong couldn’t help but smile bitterly. However, much of it was because of appreciation. If this wasn’t the Cultivation Realm, then he would have loudly yelled with glee. Unfortunately, he can’t do it now. Ma Rulong also clearly knew that the people from the Cultivation Realm couldn’t be reasoned with. So even if Zhao Hai wanted to keep low-key, he has no choice but to act domineering. And since the Cultivators present couldn’t defeat Zhao Hai, they can only behave.

People who came from the Machine Field were also looking at Zhao Hai. They heard about Zhao Hai’s exploits in the Cultivation Realm back when they were still in the Machine Field. At that time, they were able to vent bad air. Zhao Hai’s strength caused them to secretly applaud him. Just like Ma Rulong, they couldn’t really cheer loudly.

But since things needed to proceed, the battles continued. Before long, the day ended and a total of 48 people would proceed to the next round. It was also time for Zhao Hai and the others to rest.

When the Machine Field returned to their residence, Ma Rulong and the others immediately went to Zhao Hai’s room. To be honest, Zhao Hai’s room wasn’t large. With so many people coming over, it made the room very crowded.

Seeing Ma Rulong and the others, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “What’s the matter? Why is everyone here? Do you want to drink?”

Ma Rulong smiled bitterly and said, “Little Hai, how can anyone have any mood to drink? You really shouldn’t have killed Jiang Tian. This is like slapping the face of the Cultivation Realm. The Cultivators will never let you off.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Not let me off? To be honest, I’m not really afraid.”

Seeing Zhao Hai’s indifferent reaction, Ma Rulong sighed and said, “Little Hai, you think too simply. With your current strength, even if you can act freely in the Cultivation Realm now, you still shouldn’t offend the Cultivators. After all, you still need to use transmission formations in order to return to the Machine Field. If you slap their faces too hard, then those fellows will find ways to deal with you. Things like redirecting the location of a transmission formation. Or even sending you to a dangerous region. Such things have been done before in the World of Cultivation. A lot of experts went missing because of this.”

Upon hearing this, ZHao Hai stared, then he said, “Such things happen? Really? I didn’t think about that. But Team Leader can rest assured. I’ll be fine. Don’t forget that I can use space magic. If I really want to return to the Machine FIeld, then I can do it alone as long as I prepare.”

Ma Rulong gawked when he heard Zhao Hai. Then his eyes shone as he said, “Little Hai, are you telling the truth? You don’t need the Cultivation Realm’s transmission formation to return to the Machine Field? So does this mean that you didn’t need to use the transmission formation when we came here?”

Zhao Hai looked at Ma Rulong and then said, “No, I can’t do it before. Since I don’t have the Cultivation Realm’s coordinates, I can’t come here directly from the Machine Field. But now that I’m here and I have coordinates, I can enter and exit the Cultivation Realm on my own through my magic.”

Ma Rulong’s eyes turned brighter, then he said, “In other words, as long as you have gone to a place, then you can use space magic to go there? No matter the distance?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Yes, but of course the difficulty varies. The farther the distance, the more preparation I would need. Moreover, the consumption of spiritual qi increases with distance. If I want to conduct long distance transmission, then I would consume a lot of energy. If I transport more people, the consumption will increase as well.”

Ma Rulong nodded. He felt that this made sense. If Zhao Hai doesn’t pay any price to go anywhere, then it would be totally unrealistic. However, Ma Rulong didn’t know that this unrealistic thing was in fact realistic.

Ma Rulong turned his head to everyone and said, “Everyone, you need to keep what you hear as a secret. Don’t mention it to anyone else. People with abilities like Little Hai are really important to the Machine Field. If the Cultivators know about it, then it would cause great trouble to Little Hai. Understood?”

Chapter 1264: Smuggling

Changes in terms(my bad): Demon Realm -> Devil Realm(Mo), Beast Realm -> Demon Realm(Yao), Elves -> Sprites

Although the other team leaders didn’t quite understand what Ma Rulong meant, they still nodded. These team leaders were also practitioners. And to be honest, Zhao Hai’s actions made them feel great. Additionally, they had shared drinks with Zhao Hai, so their relationship was very good. It was not a problem for them to keep Zhao Hai’s secret.

Zhao Hai looked at Ma Rulong, he didn’t know what he was excited about. So he asked, “Team Leader, what’s important about this information?”

Ma Rulong looked at everyone around him, but he didn’t make the other team leaders go out. The team leaders already knew about this, so it would be too much to make them leave. Then he said, “This is very important for the Machine Field. As far as the realm is concerned, it would have a very significant impact.”

Zhao Hai and the other team leaders look at Ma Rulong in confusion. Ma Rulong took a deep breath and then waved his hand, making everyone go out of the room and look for a bigger place. Zhao Hai’s room was not huge, so it wasn’t a good place to have a conversation in. Just outside was a small living room that can accommodate everyone.

After everyone had sat down, Ma Rulong opened his mouth and said, “Everyone should know that there are a lot of treasures in the Cultivation Realm. This is because the lands of the Cultivation Realm are very good. There are more than 10 thousand habitable planets in the Cultivation Realm. And if a planet is uninhabitable, that doesn’t mean that it doesn’t have anything good in it. The minerals obtained by the Cultivators from those planets are very precious. And there are a lot of those minerals that aren’t available in the Machine Field.”

Everyone nodded. This was something that everyone in the Machine Field understood. However, they don’t understand why Ma Rulong must mention this matter at this time.

Ma Rulong continued, “Although our Machine Field has our own mines for spirit stones, our production capacity isn’t that large. It is because of this that we use machine coins as currency in the Machine FIeld. It is different compared to the stones that are used in the Cultivation Realm.”

Everyone was still confused, they had yet to see where Ma Rulong was heading towards. Seeing everyone’s reaction, Ma Rulong said, “Since the Machine Field has so few spirit stones, it’s very difficult for use to buy those minerals from the Cultivation Realm. Additionally, the Cultivation Realm imposes heavy tariffs on our imported goods. And there are even some ores that are banned from being sold to us. This is one of the reasons why the Machine Field’s development is very slow.”

This was something that people knew and it was part of the Cultivation Realm’s suppression of the Machine Field. Not only the Machine Field, the Cultivation Realm does this to the other realms as well. Therefore, nobody had yet to beat the Cultivation Realm in strength.

Ma Rulong looked at Zhao Hai and said, “But with Little Hai’s ability to come in and out of the Cultivation Realm at will, he doesn’t need to pay any tariffs. If he wore Cultivator clothing and bought the materials we can’t buy, then wouldn’t that be a significant thing for the Machine Field?”

Smuggling! This was the first word that came into Zhao Hai’s mind when he heard Ma Rulong. Ma Rulong was planning on using the Space for smuggling. Zhao Hai doesn’t know whether to laugh or cry.

Back in the lower realms, he would use his Space to do business most of the time, but he doesn’t need to smuggle goods. This was because he was a noble, so he has the privilege to be exempt from tariffs. He didn’t expect that the Space would have to smuggle goods in the Machine Field.

Unlike Zhao Hai, the others immediately understood Ma Rulong’s words. They couldn’t help but stare before they reacted. Instantaneously, the look they gave Zhao Hai changed.

To be honest, the Cultivation Realm was truly rich in resources. They have a lot of things that they want to buy here, but they simply don’t have spirit stones to purchase with. Although these team leaders were quite rich in their respective families, most of them had their wealth in machine coins. They were no poorer than children here in the Cultivation Realm.

In the Machine Field, spirit stones were highly sought after goods. Therefore, it wasn’t regarded as currency. Moreover, great families would use their spirit stones to trade with the Cultivation Realm most of the time. These stones don’t circulate in the Machine Field. It was just like having foreign currency reserves of a certain country. They would only use it to transact with that country and never with their own people.

So even if these team leaders wanted something in the Cultivation Realm, they couldn’t afford it. But if Zhao Hai does indeed have the ability to go to the Cultivation Realm without going through transmission formations, then they can definitely ask Zhao Hai to help them buy some things and pay him in machine coins, or other precious goods. It can be said that Zhao Hai was now a highly sought after smuggler in their eyes.

Zhao Hai looked at everyone’s expressions and knew what they were thinking. He couldn’t help but chuckle as he looked at Ma Rulong and said, “Team Leader, rest assured. As long as the Machine Field is in need, I’ll do my best to help. Since Zheng Li is now a close friend, then I can ask his help to deal with this matter.”

Ma Rulong couldn’t help but increase his evaluation of Zhao Hai upon hearing this. He befriended Zheng Li before this, so it was actually for this purpose.

At this moment, there was a loud noise coming from outside. Ma Rulong stared, then he stood up and looked out. There were a lot of Mages and Warriors that came to visit. These people just came to see how Zhao Hai deals with the other realms, and Zhao Hai didn’t disappoint them. He killed Jiang Tian, which made them very excited for the events to come.

Seeing this situation, Ma Rulong knew what these people came for. To be honest, for these people to come here from the Machine Field meant that they weren’t low-ranking people. They were usually descendants of great families. Counting on these people to not visit after seeing the battle was almost impossible.

People from External Halls couldn’t go here. It’s difficult for them to use transmission formations, and even if they arrive at the Cultivation Realm, they wouldn’t have any spirit stones to pay for the transmission fee to go to the Void Arena. Therefore, Ma Rulong knew that those who were able to come to the Void Arena weren’t people that could be offended.

At this point, it doesn’t matter if Zhao Hai becomes the champion or not. He will surely rise up in the Machine Field. Most of these guys knew that establishing relationships early was very important. Also, Zhao Hai was used to these kinds of events.

Zhao Hai received these people with great enthusiasm and entertained them. If one were to look at it, Zhao Hai had the lowest status among everyone in this room. Moreover, he was the only Ascender present here, the others were natives of the Machine Field. If Zhao Hai wasn’t monstrously strong, then these people wouldn’t’ have wanted to be intimate with him. And the Ashley Family might not allow his marriage to Margaret.

However, now that Zhao Hai can defeat Cultivators and allow the Machine Field to release bad air, he became the realm’s poster child. It can be said that Zhao Hai had the qualifications to sit and chat with these people.

This doesn’t mean that there were no families in the Machine Field that was established by Ascenders. In fact, families established by Ascenders held quite some influence in the Machine Field.

Because of this, people approached Zhao Hai with the identification of being from a family established by an Ascender. They felt that their relationship with an Ascender will help with their interaction with Zhao Hai, especially since Zhao Hai was a very powerful Ascender.

A lot of people who visited Zhao Hai were from these families that were founded by Ascenders. But at this point they were already considered to be natives of the Machine Field. After all, these families had been around for a long time, with some of them having survived for dozens of generations. Naturally, their descendants were no different from the natives of the Machine Field.

Zhao Hai got along with these people very well. He did these kinds of gatherings many times in the lower realms. Rapport was slowly being made and everyone was delightedly chatting.

After talking and drinking for a while, Zhao Hai sent everyone off. But as these people left, they were already calling Zhao Hai brother. For most people, sentiment was easiest to make on the liquor table. Although it was only through some wine and dishes, they became friends immediately. Now, if these people wanted to handle some matters outside of their control, they could ask their other brothers for help. Compared to looking for strangers for help, this method was much easier.

When the visitors left, Zhao Hai immediately went back to his room and then entered the Space. Upon entering the villa, he immediately asked, “How is it?”

His words might sound senseless, but Laura actually knew what he was asking about. Zhao Hai released silver needles in order to spy on the other realms present in the Void Arena. Now Zhao Hai was asking Laura and the others about their findings.

Laura nodded and said, “The reaction is quite big. However, since the Spirit Realm, Sprites, and the Demons have nothing to do with us, their reaction isn’t as big as the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm. The Cultivators ordered their participants to give 120% of their effort when they meet you in the arena. Otherwise, they would be punished. One the other hand, the Devil Realm lost two participants today, so they’re now relying on Tu Mietan to advance. It seems like the Devil Realm has given Tu Mietan a powerful artifact to cope with you especially.”

Zhao Hai nodded, this response was within his expectations. It wasn’t a big deal if the Devil Realm took out one or two artifacts to deal with him. As for the Demon Realm, Sprite  Realm, and the Spirit Realm, their participants had been wiped out in the first round. Therefore, they don’t care much about the ongoing battles. But when they saw how powerful Zhao Hai was, they were also able to vent out some bad air.

Chapter 1265: Formation Expert

Changes in terms(my bad): Demon Realm -> Devil Realm(Mo), Beast Realm -> Demon Realm(Yao), Elves -> Sprites, still reading forward to see if Spirit Race = Elves. No precise description given yet.

Zhao Hai took a six-hour break inside the Space before heading back out again. This was because the second round of battles was about to begin. Actually, Zhao Hai doesn’t need to participate in this round since he gained first place in the qualifiers. However, he still wanted to look at the battles. This was because he would be seeing more actions from the Demons, Spirit Race, and Sprites. Zhao Hai’s understanding about these races was too few.

The Demon Race were in fact monsters and plants that had gained sentience and gained humanoid forms. Therefore, they were called demons(yao). These people were also very formidable. They gain strength from preying on other people.

The Demons who came to participate in the competition were also beasts and plants from the lower realms. When they ascended, they gained their humanoid form. And after practicing, they were able to increase their methods and were now more difficult to deal with.

On the other hand, the practice of the Spirit Race was somewhat special. They have methods that’s a combination between the methods of Ghost Cultivators and Sprites. They collect spirits and then cultivate them. They use these spirits as weapons as well as energy.

There are several ways to collect these spirits. One was after someone died. However, not all souls could become spirits. These spirits only come up when someone dies of special circumstances.

Another method to generate spirits was to use one’s own spiritual force to rip their souls to generate a new spirit. This was also a special method of the Spirit Race. The Cultivation Realm also has the same method, but it could only be done by Soul Severing Experts.

People from the Spirit Realm were able to divide their soul into two because of the unique property of their soul.  When Spirit Realm practitioners split their souls, the split soul would become their Life Source Spirit, an external incarnation of their soul. It was a type of weapon that’s tightly linked to their entire being. It was similar to a Cultivator’s Life Source Weapon. But strictly speaking, Life Source Spirits were much more advanced than Life Source Weapons. However, splitting one’s soul was a very painful practice. This would also affect the Spirit Race’s cultivation. It’s a dangerous and sometimes fatal process.

Although the Spirit Realm and the Cultivation Realm’s practices were different, their respective might was extraordinary. One shouldn’t look at the fact that the Cultivation Realm had been suppressing the other realms and conclude that there are problems in the methods of the other realms. In fact, the Cultivation Methods of all the other realms were perfect as well, their only problem was resources.

Resources spent by the Cultivation Realm to cultivate was much more compared to the other realms. The other realms weren’t able to be as strong as the Cultivators because they just don’t have the resources to do so.

It’s like a poor person gambling with a rich person. Even if the two had similar techniques, the rich person would still be in a much better state. If the rich person and the poor person were dealt with similar cards, then the rich person could just drown the poor person to defeat using money and the poor person would have no way of fighting back.

It was because of this that Zhao Hai understood that the people from the World of Cultivation couldn’t be underestimated. Even the Machine Field had something hidden that wasn’t simple.

The second round of the tournament ended quickly. Naturally, Cultivators didn’t waste too much time. As soon as two Cultivators meet, they would exchange a few moves before the loser was decided. Then when they were against people from the other realms, the Cultivators would employ ruthless methods, but there had been no casualties yet.

The result of the second round was just like what Zhao Hai thought. The people from the other realms occupied the 90’s and late 80’s rankings. It can be said that the suppression was fierce.

After the round, no time for rest was allocated as the third round immediately began. This round was still done by drawing two participants. And this time, Zhao Hai would fight.

But what surprised Zhao Hai this time was that Tu Mietan was drawn along with a Cultivator. Zhao Hai expected the Cultivation Realm to pull some tricks, but it seems like they didn’t.

Actually, what Zhao Hai didn’t know was that the Cultivation Realm had fostered an arrogant character due to their successful suppression of the other realms. They simply disdain using tricks during these competitions.

Zhao Hai was able to spy on Tu Mietan yesterday. To be honest, people from the Devil Realm were really similar to the Cultivation Realm. They also used a lot of magic artifacts. However, their magic artifacts were filled with ghastly auras. They all had the stench of blood and looked disgusting.

Zhao Hai also knew that the Devil Realm’s artifacts had the property to corrupt other magical artifacts. If a magic artifact clashed with a devil artifact for a long time, then they would get corroded.

It can be said that devil artifacts suppressed the Cultivation Realm’s magic artifacts. If a Cultivator wants to fight someone from the Devil Realm, then they would generally use magic artifacts that were alloyed with a special material in order to cancel the corrosive properties of devil artifacts. However, these special materials were rare, and no average Cultivator could afford it.

In addition to alloying special materials to their weapons, Cultivators could also attach purifying formations on their weapons. Although their weapons could still be corroded, as long as it wasn’t serious, it could recover on its own.

Tu Mietan was initially bestowed devil artifacts by the Sacred Blood Sect. From what Zhao Hai saw, there were three devil artifacts that were handed over, one was a blood red ghost head sword, a black colored flag, and a devil face shield. These three devil artifacts were the most commonly used types of artifacts by the Devil Realm. Moreover, the qualities of these particular three wasn’t any worse than weapons used by the Cultivation Realm.

The ghost head sword looked very powerful. Average flying swords couldn’t survive fighting against it due to its powerful corrosive ability. As for the ghost face shield, Zhao Hai was able to experience it before. It’s defensive strength was very strong. Once it was used, it would provide Tu Mietan with great defensive capability.

The black colored flag was even more extraordinary. When Tu Mietan used the flag and swung it gently, innumerable ghost heads came out of the flag and threw themselves towards the target as well as their magic artifacts. Most magic artifacts would be eaten by the ghost heads in no time.

These weren’t just the things that Tu Mietan had in hand. As for how many cards he has, nobody knew. And with his already great strength, he has yet to lose to a Cultivator. Because of this, he was able to step on the top 50 of the rankings.

This time, Tu Mietan’s opponent was quite well known among the Cultivation Realm’s ascenders. The two battled for some time, but in the end Tu Mietan was able to win.

Although it took some time before Tu Mietan won, Zhao Hai didn’t dare underestimate him. This was because Tu Mietan was still using his three common devil artifacts to win. He has yet to use anything else.

Even if the Devil Realm had inferior resources compared to the Cultivation Realm, Zhao Hai doesn’t believe that the Devil Realm relied on Tu Mietan to get a greater ranking using only these three weapons. For Tu Mietan to reach his current position without using any other devil artifact could only be explained by one thing, he had yet to go all out.

Zhao Hai has been paying attention to Tu Mietan’s conduct. Although Tu Mietan has a heavy killing aura aroundhim and seemed to go for murder if there’s an opportunity, he actually had some discretion when fighting in the arena. He won his battles without severely wounding his enemies. It was obvious that he was a person who knew how to advance and retreat. He understood what needed to be done.

Also, whether spectating or in battles, Tu Mietan seemed to greet everyone with an everlasting smile. This caused him to gain Zhao Hai’s admiration.

After several rounds of drawing lots, Zhao Hai’s name was finally pulled out. But when he saw his opponent, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gawk. This was because this person was also among the group that examined the fight scene underground along with Jiang Tian – Yao Guang. This person’s formations were definitely the most profound out of those present at that time.

Zhao Hai clearly knew that both Jiang Tian and Yao Guang were in the top ten of the Cultivation Realm’s qualifiers. Being able to battle two top tens in a row caused Zhao Hai to have some suspicions about the Cultivation Realm doing underhanded methods.

However, he doesn’t have much time to think about this as he was close to the arena. Just as he stepped on the ground, Yao Guang stepped in as well. Yao Guang was very polite as he bowed towards Zhao Hai and said, “I have seen Mister Zhao Hai. This Yao Guang has heard mister Zhao Hai’s recent exploits. Being able to face Mister today is certainly my honor.”

Zhao Hai didn’t lower his guard just because Yao Guang was being polite. He was aware that the Cultivators had already issued a death order on his head. No matter who encountered him, they would have to go all out. Even if they couldn’t defeat him, they should at least make him waste a lot of energy. If they could injure him, then that would even be better.

Zhao Hai expected such an order from the Cultivators. He was aware that he was already seen as an enemy of the Cultivators. If the Cultivators didn’t decide to deal with him, then they could no longer be from the Cultivation Realm.

Zhao Hai didn’t show an arrogant expression as he returned the courtesy with a smile and said, “I have seen Mister Yao Guang. Mister’s formations have gained this one’s admiration. Being able to compare notes with Mister is a great fortune. Mister Yao Guang, please.” Then Zhao Hai gave a gesture of invitation towards Yao Guang.

But when Yao Guang heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but stare. His achievements regarding formations were known to very few people in the Cultivation Realm. He would normally act as an average Cultivator and used magic artifacts to deal with the enemy. He would rarely use formations in battle, he even deemed it as his trump card. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to see through his strongest point. This caused Yao Guang’s heart to beat more loudly.

However, since Yao Guang was also a person with deep thoughts, he didn’t display his surprise and instead just said, “Mister Zhao Hai’s praise makes me happy. Then Mister, I’ll make my move.” Then he waved his hand, causing a flying sword to come out.

This was a very ordinary flying sword. It was obviously inadequate to deal with Zhao Hai. However, Zhao Hai didn’t look down on this flying sword. Yao Guang was a formation expert, the methods of people like him were very difficult to predict!

Chapter 1266: Truly A Formation Expert

Zhao Hai didn’t make a move nor did he take out his weapon. He only looked calmly at Yao Guang. However, Yao Guang didn’t dare to treat him lightly. This was because he knew that Zhao Hai was capable of defeating a Core Formation Cultivator without using any weapons. Underestimating such a person would basically be courting death.

In fact, what Zhao Hai guessed was right. Yao Guang was just a normal Cultivator when it came to using flying swords. His greatest strength was his formations.

Now that the Cultivation Realm had issued a death command, everyone facing Zhao Hai would need to go all out to defeat him. Yao Guang wouldn’t dare go against the will of the Cultivation Realm, so he would need to use his full power. And this meant that he would have to take out his formidable formations.

Two people were in opposite directions of each other, both had yet to make a move. But then, Yao Guang began taking out hundreds of formation flags. As long as he could constrain Zhao Hai for a while, then he would be able to arrange a powerful formation. He immediately commanded his flying sword to pierce towards ZHao Hai. In his battles before this, Yao Guang used this flying sword to deal with his enemies without them knowing that his true strength was in formations. It can be seen that his flying sword technique was not simple. At the very least, he was much better compared to average Cultivators of his level.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly before he waved his hand and made a 100-layer formation appear to block Yao Guang’s sword. But at this time, Yao Guang saw an opportunity. He threw eight formation flags from his hand towards eight directions, completely encircling Zhao Hai.

The reason why Zhao Hai didn’t deal with Yao Guang immediately was because he wanted to see how strong the formations of the Cultivation Realm were. At this time, he knew more about the magic formations of the Machine Field. He knew that the Cultivation Realm’s formations weren’t any less powerful than the Machine Field’s. Although he learned how to arrange formations from Helian Da, Helian Da wasn’t a Formation Cultivator in the end. There were still plenty of formations that he didn’t know about. This was especially true for offensive formations.

But Yao Guang was different. He was proficient in attacking enemies using formations. It can be said that he was a true Formation Cultivator. The formations in his hands were ever changing and they were extremely powerful. Because of this, Zhao Hai wanted to experience it for himself. Therefore, he wasn’t anxious of ending the battle.

If it were someone from the Machine Field or even the Cultivation Realm, they wouldn’t do the same thing as Zhao Hai. This was because even if they saw the formation, they wouldn’t know how it worked. However, Zhao Hai was different. He has the Space that can record the battle. And once Yao Guang’s actions were recorded, it could be analyzed by the Scanner and harvested for data. Therefore, Zhao Hai waited to see Yao Guang’s formation.

But if his opponent was exchanged to another famed Formation Cultivator, Zhao Hai wouldn’t dare do this. The Cultivation Realm’s formations are very formidable. Underestimating it wouldn’t bode well for anyone and Zhao Hai doesn’t want to be an unlucky ghost. But Yao Guang was different. Ya Guang’s formations might be fierce, but his strength was still low at Foundation Establishment Stage. Even if his formations were exquisite, the effects were still limited and couldn’t be a threat to Zhao Hai. It can be said that Yao Guang was the best candidate for Zhao Hai to test the Cultivation Realm’s formations.

Naturally, Yao Guang was unaware of these thoughts. He was thinking that Zhao Hai was holding back and underestimating the might of the Cultivation Realm’s formations. Because of this, he made sure to set up his formation correctly. The formation that Yao Guang used this time wasn’t a simple formation. Instead, it was the very famous Eight Dragon Shackles formation! The formation flags used for this formation were made out of eight dragon bones, its might was said to be extraordinary!

Of course, this extraordinary might refers to the true Eight Dragon Shackles. The formation that Yao Guang used was merely a replica. However, the materials that Yao Guang’s sect used for this formation was still very precious.

Once the eight formation flags have been inserted, Zhao Hai immediately felt his surroundings change. The formation flags vanished as well as Yao Guang. All around him was a golden mist, then the roar of a dragon was heard. When the dragon roar came out, the earth split and eight golden dragons emerged. But although the dragons came out, their tails seem to be anchored to the ground. Then the eight dragon heads met together to form a huge cage.

As soon as he looked at these dragons, Zhao Hai guessed what the formation was doing. He immediately released a 100-layer formation to attack one of the dragons.

However, just as the 100-layer formation was sent out, the eight dragons moved. They fiercely growled at the incoming attack and pressed their heads down as they shot out golden light from their mouths. However, not all golden light attacked Zhao Hai’s formation, some of them were headed towards Zhao Hai as well.

Zhao Hai knew that although these weren’t true gold dragons, they were comparable to the fire dragons that he released. They have their own entities and can give real attacks. If one regards these golden dragons as imaginary, then they would experience extreme bad luck.

Zhao Hai wasn’t polite, he waved his hand and released a series of 100-layer formations. Fire dragons came out of these formations to attack the golden dragons. But even if the fight between the fire dragons and golden dragons were fierce, Zhao Hai just calmly stood on the side and observed with great interest. It was as if he wasn’t taking things seriously.

On the other hand, Yao Guang was busily preparing for another formation. Formation flags and formation disks flew out of his hand and gathered around Zhao Hai.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t actually idling at this time. He was making Cai’er record Yao Guang’s every movement and every formation arrangement. Even those formation flags and formation disks had silver needles attached to them.

The silver needles were rapidly analyzing the materials used to make the flags and disks, the way they were refined was being analyzed as well. This ability was also something that Zhao Hai just recently discovered after the Space leveled up. This ability was very useful for Zhao Hai. Before this, he could only analyze these flags and disks when they were sent to the Space. But now, having silver needles attached to them was sufficient.

Yao Guang was arranging his formations while Zhao Hai was just looking at it. However, the spectators were seeing another thing.

Yao Guang had a lot of support from the Cultivation Realm. But still, the amount of formation flags and formation disks he has in hand was very astonishing.

Also, it seems like Yao Guang was truly a rare talent in formations. The formations that he arranged were set up perfectly. They were connected with each other and formed a cohesive set. Additionally these formations were all targeted towards one person – Zhao Hai. Once this formation was finished, even Nascent Soul Experts wouldn’t be able to sit still.

The Cultivation Realm’s people highly praised Yao Guang’s actions. The Elders of Yao Guang gave him special training that was only given to Core Disciples. Although Yao Guang’s sect wasn’t a traditional Sect that specialized in Formations and were primarily an Orthodox Sect, they couldn’t ignore Yao Guangs talent and decided to vigorously train him.

In the Cultivation Realm, Sects were bound to receive special talents. As long as these talents were discovered, these Sects would immediately give them training appropriate to their abilities. And just because they were special talents, they weren’t suppressed – this was impossible for Sects. Even Sword Sects would have numerous Pill Masters, Forging Masters, and Formation Masters.

In reality, these Crafting Masters were often more popular than ordinary Elders in a Sect. These people hold a Sect’s technological level in their hands. No matter where, these people were highly looked upon. This reputation also applies to common craftsmen. People were afraid of offending a future Master of a craft.

But even if Yao Guang’s comprehension was very good when it came to formations, he was still at the level of an Inner Disciple and not a Core Disciple. After all, Yao Guang’s time in the Cultivation Realm has been short – less than five years. For any Cultivator, five years of time wasn’t really long.

On the other hand, when the Machine Field’s people saw that Zhao Hai was being buried in layers upon layers of formations, their complexion couldn’t help but change. Zhao Hai was currently the Machine Field’s hope. If Zhao Hai was defeated, then the Machine Field would suffer elimination in the tournament.

The people from the other realms were also looking at Zhao Hai with a trace of worry in their eyes. In their minds, Zhao Hai was most likely to win the tournament, and they also wanted him to win. Although Zhao Hai had nothing to do with them, one shouldn’t forget that they all share the same hatred for the Cultivation realm. The enemy of an enemy is a friend. If someone you don’t know hits your enemy, you would feel great and even develop favorable impressions towards that person. This was the same case for the other realms as they looked at Zhao Hai.

Besides the Devil Realm that saw Zhao Hai as a potential enemy, the other realms wanted to see how Zhao Hai slaps the faces of the Cultivators. So now that Zhao Hai was trapped in the formation, they couldn’t help but worry.

Different people were having different thoughts. On the other hand, Zhao Hai and Yao Guang weren’t thinking of much. Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about Yao Guang’s formation while Yao Guang was too focused on assembling his formations.

Although Zhao Hai was just standing there and would release a formation once in a while to attack the eight dragons, his mind was actually exchanging information with Cai’er.

The formations that Yao Guang arranged were very special. They were arranged from the inside to the outside. Each formation formed would immediately activate. And with each formation, the pressure that Zhao Hai felt would increase. It can be said that the formations were being layered. When all of Yao Guang’s formations finish forming, it’s certain that their pressure would be huge. Its strength would naturally be uncommon.

However, one shouldn’t think that once they break this formation, then everything will go down. Yao Guang’s formations were composed of numerous smaller formations. Even if someone destroys some of them, the others could still attack. So after Cai’er’s analysis, it was found out that unless one-third of the formations were destroyed, then the offensive power of the entire formation wouldn’t be reduced.

Zhao Hai was no longer attacking the eight golden dragons, this was because he was no longer required to attack them. At this point, the dragons were now attacking him, no longer just retaliating. Moreover, the attacks of these dragons had gotten stronger. In the beginning, the attacks were as strong as 100-layer formations, but now it was equivalent to 700 to 800-layer formations. It was also because of this that the spectators expected Zhao Hai to fall soon and that Yao Guang’s victory was close.

Everyone knew that as soon as Yao Guang finished his formation, he would immediately use all of its might to attack Zhao Hai. Formations that attack on their own have different strengths compared to formations that were controlled to attack. Therefore, everyone began worrying about Zhao Hai upon seeing that Yao Guang was about to finish.

But what everyone didn’t know was that Zhao Hai was waiting for Yao Guang to be done. Once Yao Guang finishes and Zhao Hai experiences the might of the formations, only then would he proceed to destroy it.

Why was Zhao Hai confident in breaking Yao Guang’s formation? Naturally it’s because of the existence of Liquid Silver. Liquid Silver’s needles had attached themselves to Yao Guang’s flags and disks. As long as Zhao Hai gave the order, these needles could destroy these flags and disks. Although the flags and disks were offensive items and had also been inscribed with formations, their main attacking power would only manifest when the formation was activated. Also, they don’t have a lot of defensive capabilities. As long as they’re attacked by the silver needles, they would immediately be destroyed. In turn, this would also destroy the formation. Therefore, Zhao Hai was very confident.

It can be said that formations were the least reliable means of dealing with Zhao Hai. And illusion formations were the most useless formations to contain ZhaoHai. Zhao Hai has the Space which makes all illusions useless. Zhao Hai also has Liquid Silver that can turn into a thousand flying needles which have strong destructive capabilities. No formation could compare to them.

A team of Formation Cultivators took great pains to create these flags and disks in order to deal with Zhao Hai. However, Zhao Hai could just use his silver needles to destroy everything. The painstaking effort made by these Formation Cultivators became useless.

At this time, Yao Guang finished preparing his entire formation. Zhao Hai asked Cai’er and discovered that Yao Guang had arranged several hundred small and large formations. The formation disks used numbered more than 100, while flags used shot past 200. Without the support of a Great Sect, could a less than 5-year Ascender have all of these? Even if he sold his soul, he wouldn’t be able to get all of these resources.

Once Yao Guang was done setting everything up, he couldn’t help but breathe out. He was afraid that Zhao Hai would destroy the formation. If that happens, then every effort he made would be in vain. But at the same time, there has been no action from Zhao Hai, which made him puzzled.

Chapter 1267: Breaking the Formation

Zhao Hai was still calmly standing in place. At this point, he was using 1000-layer formations to defend. It was also at this time that the people from the Machine Field and the Cultivation Realm discovered how formidable he was.

People from the Cultivation Realm were also very familiar with the Machine Field’s Magic Theory. After all, this method wasn’t a secret in the World of Cultivation. Additionally, computers were used to varying degrees in other realms. It can be said that Magic Theory can be cultivated by anyone in the World of Cultivation.

It was precisely because of their understanding of Magic Theory that nobody in the World of Cultivation practiced it. Although magic formations could be used as spells and were more powerful, the energy consumption needed to operate it was greater than the formations of the Cultivation Realm. Although spells were also used in the Cultivation Realm, it wasn’t the main method of attack. Compared to magic artifacts, it still falls short.

Spells weren’t valued in the Cultivation Realm, let alone Magic Theory. The main reason why the Cultivation Realm had some understanding about Magic Theory was because this would allow them to suppress the Machine Field more effectively.

Since the energy consumption of Magic Theory was very big, those in the Machine Field who could release 1000-layer formations were among the realm’s top experts. These people wouldn’t suffer a loss when fighting against a Core Formation Expert from the Cultivation Realm.

However, even those who can use 1000-layer formations in the Machine Field wouldn’t use these formations for a long time. The energy consumption was just too big, they wouldn’t dare consume all of their energy.

But now, Zhao Hai can actually use 1000-layer formations with ease. He wasn’t even using any items, yet he can cast them instantaneously. This caused everyone in the Cultivation Realm to be startled.

Yao Guang was also observing Zhao Hai. Like others, he has some understanding about the Machine Field’s Magic Theory. And since he understood the system, he knew that Zhao Hai was formidable. But Yao Guang believes that Zhao Hai wasn’t going at full power. At the very least, he hasn’t used his weapon. Yao Guang doesn’t believe that Zhao Hai’s weapon was useless. He heard that Zhao Hai was both a Mage and a Warrior. Moreover, his weapon was a silver-white staff. Now, Zhao Hai doesn’t have his staff with him, this meant that he wasn’t at his full power.

Although Yao Guang doesn’t know why Zhao Hai was holding back, he doesn’t have time to think about it too much. Yao Guang immediately used his secret art to control the entire great formation.

All Cultivators have some understanding about formations, but only some know how to arrange them. And even if they understood how to arrange a formation, that doesn’t mean they understood how to operate it.

Operating a formation is a very technical task, but most Cultivators don’t necessarily have to learn it. It’s just like in the Machine Field. People in the Machine Field couldn’t live without magic formations, but they don’t necessarily know how to use it.

As soon as Yao Guang used his secret art, the entire great formation lit up. The formation is now under Yao Guang’s control. To be honest, controlling such a huge formation wasn’t easy. But if he doesn’t control it, then Yao Guang wouldn’t be able to defeat Zhao Hai.

Although Zhao Hai was still trapped in the formation, Yao Guang was sure that if he didn’t control it, then it would only be a matter of time before Zhao Hai would break out.

Once he was able to control the entire formation, Yao Guang was relieved. He now felt that he had the strength to defeat Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai was still calmly standing inside the formation, he was still able to see Yao Guang’s movements through the Space. Not only was he not afraid, he was even secretly happy. He really wanted to see how powerful this formation was.

As soon as Yao Guang controlled the formation, Zhao Hai immediately felt the sharp increase of pressure around him. The eight golden dragons had also become more solid and their shapes becoming more vivid. At the same time, their offensive strength increased. Each golden dragon could now attack using spells, not only their claws and breath. These spells were very strong, at about the same level as 500-layer formations

Zhao Hai’s eyes slightly shrank. Now that the formation has been unleashed, Core Formation Experts trapped within it would certainly have a very bad time. Yao Guang was showing the might of this entire formation.

However, Zhao Hai believes that the formation was far from displaying it’s true power. Since the formation was controlled by a Foundation Establishment expert, it’s impossible for it to fully function. If Yao Guang was stronger, then the formation’s pressure would be greater. When that time comes, then even Nascent Soul Experts wouldn’t be able to find a way out.

Now that he saw the formation’s capability, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel satisfied. He knew that he would definitely build up his own influence in the future. And since he couldn’t let others know about the Space, then he would need a base. And since it’s a base, it would need protection. In the Cultivation Realm, each major sect has a wide-scale defensive formation. These formations were the most powerful defensive means of a sect. It can be said that a sect’s power was directly related to the quality of their wide-scale defensive formation.

If one wanted to attack a sect, then they would first need to deal with the sect’s defensive formation. If you can’t destroy the formation, then you can’t do anything. It was at this aspect that the Machine Field wasn’t doing very well. Although the power of magic formations wasn’t small, it was still much worse than those sect-protecting formations of the Cultivation Realm.

And in the Cultivation Realm, blueprints of sect-protecting formations are strictly kept secret. Even Sect Disciples would be treated as traitors if they were caught sniffing around about it.

Since Zhao Hai doesn’t have any means to collect this information, he can only study and analyze formations with this crude method. Although he really wanted to kill Yao Guang now and turn him into an Undead to interrogate him, Zhao Hai knew that he couldn’t do that. At this point, the Cultivation Realm’s eyes were on him. If he killed Yao Guang, then the Cultivators might forgo all courtesies and tear him up. When that time comes, not to say Core Formation Experts and Nascent Soul Experts, even stronger Cultivators might deal with him.

After weighing the advantages and disadvantages, Zhao Hai decided not to kill Yao Gang. He cannot touch the Cultivation Realm’s bottom line.

Seeing that it was time and that Cai’er had recorded everything that could be recorded, Zhao Hai decided to begin. He waved his hand as Liquid Silver appeared.

When Yao Guang saw Zhao Hai taking his staff out, he couldn’t help but get anxious. He immediately operated the formation to go at full power. He was preparing to use the most powerful attack for Zhao Hai.

But at this moment, Yao Guang suddenly felt that something was wrong. His expression changed as he took out a pill and then threw it into his mouth. As the pill’s effects began to manifest, energy filled up Yao Guang’s body, supplementing the lost energy.

At this moment, Zhao Hai waved his staff as a dense number of magic formations appeared next to him. Although the formation wasn’t large, its sheer number of layers caused people’s scalp to numb.

Zhao Hai waved his staff as the formation burst out. A flash of light flickered causing everyone to unconsciously close their eyes. Once they opened their eyes, everyone saw that Zhao Hai was already standing in front of Yao Guang, his staff on Yao Guang’s throat. All of the formations in the arena were destroyed, nothing was left.

Everyone was greatly startled. They didn’t expect the 10,000-layer formation that Zhao Hai used to have this much destructive power.

Yes, everyone knew that Zhao Hai used a formation that had 10,000 layers. However, they didn’t expect the power of this formation to be this great.

Actually, the formation that Zhao Hai used wasn’t that powerful. The formation flags and disks were already destroyed by the silver needles. The 10,000-layer formation was released just to make people close their eyes.

Yao Guang also recovered at this time. He looked at Zhao Hai who had his staff pointed at his throat. Yao Guang smiled faintly and said, “Mister Zhao Hai is truly strong. I admit defeat.”

Zhao Hai received his magic staff, then he smiled faintly at Yao Guang and said, “Your formation is also very strong. Thanks for letting me win.” Then his body flashed as he returned to his seat.

It was only after Zhao Hai returned to his seat that the people spectating the arena responded. The spectator seats are in an uproar. They didn’t expect the situation to be overturned this quickly. One moment, people thought that Yao Guang was about to win. Then in the next, Zhao Hao broke the formation and Yao Guang admitted defeat.

Everyone in the Cultivation Realm couldn’t help but stare at the arena. They were startled. They didn’t expect Yao Guang to lose. Zhao Hai used one move to break the formation that Yao Guang painfully arranged. What made them surprised even more was the strength of the 10,000-layer formation that Zhao Hai released.

After some time, the disturbance stopped. Then Zhao Hai suddenly felt cold gazes going straight towards him. However, he didn’t care and just sat there smiling. At this time, Ma Rulong turned to Zhao Hai and whispered, “Little Hai, did you allow Yao Guang to finish his formation?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he smiled faintly and said, “I want to see how powerful his formation is. To be honest, the formation is very strong. If he was stronger, then he would be able to create a much stronger effect and I wouldn’t have been able to easily break out. It seems like the Cultivation Realm’s formations are indeed formidable.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Ma Rulong couldn’t help but bitterly smile as he said, “Your courage is too big. Only you would dare do that. If it was anyone else, then they would no doubt be killed. Don’t do something like this anymore. It’s too dangerous. You’re the Machine Field’s hope after all.”

Zhao Hai smiled and nodded. At this time, the next round of participants were being drawn. However, everyone’s attention was still fixed on Zhao Hai!

Chapter 1268: Zhongli Qiang

Besides those fighting Tu Mietan and Zhao Hai, the other Cultivators were basically just fighting amongst themselves. And at most, these fights would be spars. Because of this, nobody cared about the next round of combatants and they just gave more attention towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai’s performance was without a doubt outstanding. Everyone could see the formation that Yao Guang arranged. Even if they weren’t Formation Masters, they knew that being trapped in such a formation was just courting death.

Because of this, although the Cultivators didn’t know the subtleties of Yao Guang’s formation, its power was evident just by looking at it. Zhao Hai even had to use 1000-layer formations to combat the attacks made by the eight gold dragons. These 1000-layer formations were known to be equal to attacks made by Core Formation Experts. One could see from this point how strong Yao Guang’s formation was.

However, even with how strong the formation was, Zhao Hai only used one move to destroy it. How much strength does he have? Cultivators began to discover that they needed to reevaluate how they see Zhao Hai’s strength.

In fact, this thought wasn’t only common among those from the Cultivation Realm. Those from the Devil Realm were also reevaluating Zhao Hai’s strength. The Devil Realm wanted to swallow the Machine Field. They had been trying to deal with Zhao Hai but they had yet to succeed. They still don’t know that Zhao Hai was aware of their intentions, but they have to recalculate how to deal with him.

The Devil Realm needed to fight for resources, and people were also a type of resource in the World of Cultivation. However, for the Devil Realm to swallow the Machine Field, it would need to get rid of geniuses like Zhao Hai. Otherwise, their path would be troublesome.

But now, they found out that their trouble was much greater than what they imagined. The cost to eliminate Zhao Hai was higher than the benefits. They need to think this through well.

On the spectator seats of the Devil Realm was the team leader of the Devil Realm’s delegates. He was also an Elder from the Sacred Blood Sect. Since Tu Mietan was the realm’s champion, then it’s natural for the Sacred Blood Sect to lead the team.

There were currently a lot of people from the Devil Realm that came to watch this time. Besides the Elder from the Sacred Blood Sect, there are also a lot of guards who came with them as well as people from other Sects. All of them were here to ensure Tu Mietan’s safety.

The Sacred Blood Sect’s Elder had a two-character surname being Zhongli, and a single-character first name being Qiang. Back in the Devil Realm, he was given the nickname Boundless Blood Sea Devil. He studies a famed Cultivation Method of the Sacred Blood Sect called the Country Drowning Blood Sea. But this Cultivation Method needed to coordinate with a certain devil artifact. This devil artifact is known as the Blue Blood Gourd.

The Blue Blood Gourd’s origin traces itself back to the founding of the Sacred Blood Sect. When the Sect was being built, countless mortals were killed for their blood. This blood was concentrated into a huge blood pond. Because the sect was built on top of a yin vein, the yin energy coming out of it would be absorbed by the huge blood pond. Not only would the blood pond not dry up, but because of its location, it contained a dense amount of yin energy. This would in turn help the sect’s disciples to practice.

But without anyone knowing, a gourd vine just grew out from the blood pond. As the gourd vine grew, the yin energy and blood energy of the blood pond concentrated around it, turning the vine into the blue blood gourd vine. This blue blood gourd vine would open once every 100 years and produce a blue blood gourd.

Since it has grown in that special environment, the blue blood gourd became a very powerful artifact. Once it was refined, it would become a top-quality artifact. People from the Sacred Blood Sect aspire to have the blue blood gourd as their life source weapon.

But among the rest of the blue blood gourd, the one in Zhongli Qiang’s hands was very special. Since his family was one of the founding clans of the Sacred Blood Sect, the blue blood gourd that Zhongli QIang has been using has been passed down through generations of their family. It was the same blue blood gourd that was used by their first Patriarch. This blue blood gourd has been nourished by many people causing the degree of the blood inside the gourd to be very high. This specific blue blood gourd was among the top artifacts of the Sacred Blood Sect.

Blue blood gourds were filled with profound yin blood, which was the blood in the underground blood pool of the Sacred Blood Sect. This blood was harvested from people and had received the nourishing of yin energy to become a weapon that could corrode magic artifacts. However, this blood was much worse than Zhao Hai’s blood ponds. And there was no way for it to compare to the profound yin water inside Zhao Hai’s Space.

And just like his gourd, the profound yin blood in Zhongli Qiang’s gourd was more special. This profound yin blood has also been passed down through generations. Because of this, the profound yin blood inside the Zhongli Qiang’s blue blood gourd has very potent corrosive properties.

The profound yin blood was kept inside the gourd for a long time wasn’t because it wasn’t being used. In fact, it has been used numerous times. Otherwise, Zhongli Qiang wouldn’t have earned his nickname Boundless Blood Sea Devil.

There were a lot of Cultivators that thought that the blood inside blue blood gourds would run out. But in fact, it doesn’t. Since the blue blood gourd was a devil artifact, this meant that the blood inside it also had mystical properties. After going out and attacking, the blood would return to the gourd to be reused. Unless the blood has been destroyed to a certain extent, then even if it was dispersed, it could still be used.

It was precisely because of this that the Devil Realm allowed Zhongli Qiang to be the team leader of their delegation. The people from the Devil Realm clearly understood what the Cultivators were like. In fact, those people were as shameless and ruthless than anybody else. If the Devil Realm doesn’t send someone strong, then the Devil Realm’s delegation would be eaten up with not even the bones remaining.

At this time, Zhongli Qiang was frowning. Then he asked, “Everyone, this Zhao Hai, we need to deal with him. Do any of you have any ideas?”

Zhongli Qiang was a bit unsure about how to proceed. Zhao Hai was just too strong. If they left Zhao Hao for too long, then he might kill Tu Mietan. The moment they saw Zhao Hai killing Jiang Tian, they knew that Zhao Hai wasn’t easy to deal with,

Everyone was silent for a while. To be honest, they were having some problems in proceeding. Zhao Hai was that formidable. If Tu Mietan cannot kill Zhao Hai, then without doubt Zhao Hai would kill him.

Tu Mietan was still smiling and didn’t say anything. And he doesn’t have any right to speak at this time. With his strength, it’s better for him to shut up.

After some time, a guard said, “Leader, I think we shouldn’t make a move now. Zhao Hai is strong and it’s bad for us if he retaliates. Tu Mietan is our Devil Realm’s most talented genius in several decades. It’s not worth it if he dies here. We can just send someone to the Machine Field to kill Zhao Hai.”

Another guard coldly snorted as he said, “Do you think we can still kill Zhao Hai once we return to the Machine Field? If the Machine Field is so easy to infiltrate, then we wouldn’t have failed so much. I think we should kill him in the arena. And we need to go all out in killing him. I have some more yin thunder mines here, I can give them to Tu Mietan. I can see that Zhao Hai is starting to become complacent. When he fought with Yao Guang, he held back certainly because he wanted to try the Cultivation Ream’s formations. He wouldn’t kill his enemy immediately. And if he’s like this, then he would certainly try to see the methods of the Devil Realm. As long as Tu Mietan finds an opportunity to use these yin thunder mines, Zhao Hai will be dead for sure.”

Yin thunder mines are very cruel weapons of the Devil Realm. This weapon looks like a jade charm. It’s a consumable item that has very potent energy stored inside. If it explodes, its might is no worse than an attack from a Core Formation Expert. Additionally, these mines have the lightning attribute, making them lethal to most Cultivators. It can be said that these mines were one of the Devil realm’s weapons against the Cultivation Realm.

However, these yin thunder mines weren’t easy to manufacture. The methods to produce them were very harsh. Not only do these mines require high-quality materials, they also need to be engraved with numerous formations. And after carving the formations, one must find yin lighting to store inside the mines. Only then would the mines be completed.

In this process, engraving formations was difficult, but there were a lot of formation masters that could do it. The most tedious part of this process was finding the yin lighting. Almost all lightning have yang attributes. This was the reason why ghosts that were yin were afraid of lightning.

However, if yang exists, then yin exists as well. Even if yin attribute lightning was difficult to find, they were present. Also, capturing yin lightning was very dangerous. It’s even more dangerous than capturing yang lightning. Since yang lightning was more common, more people used it, making methods of its capture relatively known. On the other hand, since yin lightning is very rare, only a small number of people know how to handle it. In turn, this makes the process of capturing lightning very difficult.

Due to all of these considerations, yin lightning mines were rare weapons. No matter who has yin lightning mines in hand, they would always use it as a deterrent and rarely used it. If one has 3 to 5 yin lightning mines, they would live quite a safe life. Even Nascent Soul Experts wouldn’t dare make a move on them.

Now that someone offered a large number of yin lightning mines, everyone immediately turned their focus to him. The person wasn’t polite as he turned his hand, taking out 7 yin lightning mines. These seven mines were as large as a walnut and looked like black iron balls. Then he turned to Zhongli Qiang and said, “Take these seven mines. If it can deal with Zhao Hai, then I’m fine with losing all of them.”

Chapter 1269: Top Three

Although not everyone from the Devil Realm has these yin lightning mines, their insight made them recognize that the mines in front of them were the real deal.

Zhongli QIang looked at the person in confusion as he said, “Lin Jiang, why do you have so much yin lightning mines? Did you find a way to make them?”

The man named Lin Jiang forced a smile as he said, “Like it’s that easy. I got these mines a long time ago. Back then, I was searching for plants on a green planet and came across a cave with a dead Cultivator inside. I don’t know for how long the bones have been there but there are these 7 yin lightning mines as well as devil artifacts.”

Upon hearing Lin Jiang, everyone lamented on his good fortune. But Zhongli Qiang didn’t immediately take the yin lightning mines. Instead he turned to Tu Mietan and said, “Mietan, can you deal with Zhao Hai?”

Tu Mietan smiled and said, “Elder, rest assured. I’ll take care of him. I thank Uncle Ling, I’ll be impolite and take these mines.”

Lin Jiang threw his mines over and said, “I hope that these mines can help destroy Zhao Hai. That guy is too dangerous. He will be a huge threat to our Devil Realm.”

Zhongli Qiang nodded and said, “If Zhao Hai is allowed to return to the Machine Field, it would be more difficult to get rid of him. Don’t forget, he just ascended less than a year ago. He accomplished all of these in one year. He is a monster.”

Everyone was silent. Tu Mietan carefully put away the yin lightning mines. Then he turned back to watch the battles in the arena.

But what the people from the Devil Realm didn’t know was that their conversation was being eavesdropped. Zhao Hai was now aware of the existence of the yin lightning mines.

After listening to Laura about what yin lightning mines were, Zhao Hai felt the killing intent welling up inside him. Since the other party wanted to deal with him, then he doesn’t need to be polite. The Devil Realm already tried to kill him once, if he doesn’t retaliate, then he could no longer be called Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai exhibited his domineering side because he discovered that Nascent Soul Experts could walk sideways in the World of Cultivation. As long as they don’t offend any huge sect, then they don’t have to fear anything. Nascent Soul Experts were in no real danger unless they met unfortunate circumstances.

Zhao Hai currently has Nascent Soul-level strength. In fact, most Nascent Soul Experts couldn’t defeat him. In addition to his Liquid Silver, Zhao Hai also has astral qi. He’s more powerful than most Nascent Soul Experts.

Nascent Soul Stage was a bottleneck for Cultivators. As long as they successfully get through their tribulation, then their lifespan would be greatly improved along with their physical body. The body of Transcending Tribulation Experts return to their youth. It wasn’t uncommon for Transcending Tribulation Experts to revert their appearance to their younger years.

It was also because of this that Transcending Tribulation Experts treasure their own lives and would normally close up. Only when matters regarding the life and death of the sect would these people come out. Therefore, it was close to impossible for a Transcending Tribulation Expert to come and deal with Zhao Hai.

Transcending Tribulation Experts, Severed Soul Experts, and those above them could only be counted on ones hands. Such people were very secretive in their actions and most Cultivators wouldn’t even know them. Even major sect leaders couldn’t just meet them whenever they wanted.

Since he knew about this, Zhao Hai decided to show his strength. Therefore, even if the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm wanted to deal with him, they would have to think properly. Unless they give up on courtesies and send a large number of experts to kill Zhao Hai, then once he returns to the Machine Feild, then they would lose any opportunity to deal with him.

Although the Machine Field was the weakest realm in the World of Cultivation, they were still able to defend against all other realms for many years. Naturally, this meant that they had their strong point. If the Cultivators and the people from the Devil Realm sent small amounts of people to the Machine Field, then it’s highly probable for these people to not return.

For many years, the Machine FIeld didn’t have any great talents appear. But now that there was Zhao Hai, the Machine FIeld would definitely go all out in defending him.

Naturally, Zhongli Qiang’s group was aware of this. Therefore, they decided to have Tu Mietan kill Zhao Hai in the arena. They didn’t even hesitate to take out treasures like yin lightning mines. They think that with Zhao Hai’s present strength, he would hold back in dealing with his opponents. But they didn’t expect that Zhao Hai wouldn’t dare treat this matter lightly. Zhao Hai knew that even lions go all out in dealing with a rabbit.

The Cultivators in the arena were still sparring. Their battles weren’t interesting. One would win while the other lost, the battles continued on. The constant boring fights caused people to feel sleepy.

After all battles had concluded, Zhao Hai expected that they would be given time to rest before the next round began. But what he didn’t expect was that the committee didn’t pause. They immediately announced the beginning of the next round of battles.

At this point, only 24 participants were left and 12 battles remaining. The opponent that Zhao Hai has drawn with was someone from the Cultivation Realm. Although the Cultivator was quite strong, he was still defeated by Zhao Hai.

Tu Mietan was also able to smoothly enter the top 12. His opponent turned out to be Qin Zhang, one of the Cultivation Realm’s top 10. He was a person who specialized in fire spells. But in the end, he wasn’t able to last long against Tu Mietan.

Actually, Qin Zhang’s strength wasn’t inferior to Tu Mietan. He was only defeated because of the gap in artifacts. In addition to his three artifacts, Tu Mietan also took out a ghost hook and a halberd. These two artifacts have strength that was comparable to the three artifacts. Because of these two artifacts, Qin Zhang was constantly held back before he was forced to surrender.

This wasn’t surprising since Qin Zhang was just one of the top 100 of the Cultivation Realm. It was impossible for the entire Cultivation Realm to support him alone. The only support he had was the support he got from his sect.

On the other hand, Tu Mietan was the Devil Realm’s last participant in the competition. His position in the Devil Realm was the same as Zhao Hai’s position in the Machine Field. Naturally, he would have the support of his entire realm. Because of this, the artifacts he had in hand were richer compared to the other participants.

After the top twelve has been determined, it was time to decide the top 6. The person that Zhao Hai faced this time was Yi Shuihan. This caused Zhao Hai to feel strange. Besides Su LIancheng and Qin Zhang, Zhao Hai had faced all the top 10 in the elimination round. According to this pattern, it was highly probable for him to meet Su Liancheng the next round.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wasn’t polite. Although Yi Shuihan tried his best, he was still defeated by Zhao Hai. Fortunately, Yi Shuihan didn’t follow Jiang Tian’s path. Therefore, Zhao Hai didn’t take his life.

The Cultivators also discovered that if one wasn’t excessive towards Zhao Hai, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t kill them. This caused the Cultivators to pause before starting to make a move.

How strong was Zhao Hai? If the people from the Cultivation Realm order their participants to go all out on Zhao Hai, then it’s possible that Zhao Hai would kill them. This wasn’t good for the Cultivation Realm. After all, those who participated in the competition were geniuses. Losing just one of them would be bad.

Most importantly, they had to consider the impact of this action to the Ascenders. If the people from the Cultivation realm forced the participants to go all out against Zhao Hai, then Ascenders in the Cultivation Realm would think that the Cultivation Realm don’t treat their lives as important.

One must know that the Cultivation Realm’s Ascender situation was different compared to the Machine Field. In the Machine Field, Ascenders don’t have much status and power. On the other hand, Ascenders in the Cultivation Realm have a much higher status compared to Ascenders in the Machine Field. There would be no benefit for the Cultivation Realm if this matter goes bad. So even if the Cultivation Realm instructed their participants to go all out against Zhao Hai, they didn’t tell them to go desperate in order to win.

Tu Mietan also defeated his opponent. But this time, it was evident that he used a lot of effort to do so. And in addition to his five artifacts, he also used some paper talismans.

Zhao Hai knew that the Devil Realm was saving the yin lightning mines for him. Zhao Hai was also paying more attention to them. He believes that Tu Mietan doesn’t only have yin lightning mines prepared to deal with him. He surely has more methods that were hidden.

Zhao Hai knew that the competition in the Devil Realm was much more brutal than in the Cultivation Realm. Unlike the Cultivation Realm, resources in the Devil Realm were scarce. Coupled with how ruthless the people in the Devil Realm were, this resulted in an environment were the strongest tower over the weak. With this treacherous environment as his origin, Tu Mietan certainly has aces that he had yet to reveal.

And who was Zhao Hai? He was now deemed to be the most powerful rookie in the entire World of Cultivation. His position certainly attracts hate and envy. Those who can defeat him would gain instant fame and status.

Tu Mietan might be the current most influential rookie in the Devil Realm, but there were a lot of people who were vying for his position. If he was beaten by Zhao Hai, then his position would certainly be in peril. Therefore, not only would Tu Mietan eliminate Zhao Hai for fame, he would also do it in order to gain more resources from the Devil Realm.

If a person of lower status wanted a higher position in a short period of time, then the easiest method would be killing someone higher up and stepping on their corpse to ascend. With how highly Zhao Hai was being looked upon, those who could step on his corpse would certainly be able to rise smoothly.

Since he knew of this point, Zhao Hai didn’t dare take Tu Mietan lightly. Tu Mietan exerted some effort to defeat his latest opponent without taking the yin lightning mines out. This meant that he was saving the mines for Zhao Hai. But if Tu Mietan has something other than the mines, then things would be more troublesome.

When the six battles ended, the top three were determined. These three were Zhao Hai, Tu Mietan, and Suo Liancheng. This time, they would no longer use the tournament format. Instead, they would use points to determine their place in the competition.

This so-called point system was actually very simple. Zhao Hai, Tu Mietan and Suo Liancheng would fight each other. If they won, then they would get a point, and if they lost, then the other party would get the point. The one with the highest point would be the champion.

In other words, one of them would get no points, one would get two points, and one would get one point.

Naturally, it’s possible for each of them to get one point each. However, the probability of this was very small. After all, this battle was mainly determined by strength. If Zhao Hai lost to Suo Liancheng but won against Tu Mietan, then this proves that Suo Liancheng was stronger than Zhao Hai and even stronger than Tu Mietan.

But if the three were to tie, then they would fight once again until the tie is broken. But everyone knew that a second round of fights would never happen.

After drawing lots, Zhao Hai was drawn along with Suo Liancheng. Upon seeing the result, Zhao Hai didn’t hesitate and immediately flew towards the arena.

Suo Liancheng also appeared in the arena. His sword was still strapped on his back. Back when he was fighting Cultivators, he didn’t reveal much of his strength. It can be said that he was able to smoothly progress towards the top three.

However, Suo Liancheng wasn’t happy because of this. What he wanted was to fight Zhao Hai. He didn’t expect to face him in the last battles of the tournament. This caused Suo Liancheng to be somewhat depressed.

When the two stepped on the arena, Zhao Hai looked at Suo Liancheng and then smiled faintly as he said, “Suo Liancheng, I’ve been looking forward to facing you. I didn’t expect to meet you this late.”

When Suo Liancheng heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but laugh as he replied, “That’s what I was about to say. You’re strong, so I want to test my skills against you. In the eyes of sword cultivators, every enemy is an opportunity to hone our blades.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Then please.” Suo Liancheng took out the golden sword at his back. Then the golden sword flashed for a moment before it pierced towards Zhao Hai.

The sword was very fast. Moreover, it brought with it a strong aura. One could see that Suo Liancheng was utilizing all of the sword’s power. He was showing how sharp his sword was.

Zhao Hai waved his hand as he released a 100-layer formation in front of him. Then the formation turned into a shield to block the incoming sword.

However, since the sword has the metal-attribute, it was very sharp. The golden sword punctured through Zhao Hai’s shield and went straight for his throat!

Chapter 1270: One Move, One Fist

Zhao Hai looked at the sword that was quickly approaching his throat, he couldn’t help but praise it in his heart. At this point, he wouldn’t be able to evade the sword without using the Space since it’s too close. It was also too late to use a magic formation. This was the peak of Suo Liancheng’s sword. Once it’s out, you die! There’s no return. The only thing to do was face it head on!

Zhao Hai’s throat could feel the sharp aura coming out of Suo Liancheng’s sword. His hair couldn’t help but rise up.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s situation, Ma Rulong and the others stood up. Zhao Hai’s current situation was too dangerous. He couldn’t evade nor could he defend. He could only stand there to wait for death. Suo Liancheng’s sword was too savage.

Almost everyone in the spectator stands stood up, not only the people from the Machine Field . They were also startled by Suo Liancheng’s sword. The sword was too fast. It hasn’t been long since Zhao Hai invited Suo Liancheng to begin. Moreover, Suo Liancheng’s timing was just right. He attacked when Zhao Hai wasn’t fully prepared.

Everyone wanted to look and see if Suo Liancheng could break Zhao Hai’s unbeatable myth. They were even wondering if he could kill Zhao Hai.

But just as Suo Liancheng’s sword was about to piece Zhao Hai’s throat, Zhao Hai’s hand moved and grasped forward. The next moment, Suo Liancheng’s sword stuck firmly between Zhao Hai’s thumb, index finger, and middle finger. Because Suo Liancheng’s sword was travelling too fast and was suddenly stopped, the sword body couldn’t stop shaking violently.

One should know that Suo Liancheng’s sword wasn’t ordinary. It was Ten Thousand Sword Sect’s most known weapons. It was also built excellently. When this sword shook, it rang as though it was a fragile bell.

Everyone was stunned. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to just catch the sword barehanded. One could see the sword’s power by looking at how violently it shook. But in the end, Zhao Hai just caught it with three fingers.

When Suo Liancheng saw that Zhao Hai had grabbed his sword, his complexion changed. He immediately used a secret art to retrieve his sword. However, the sword just shook violently and couldn’t break out of Zhao Hai’s grip. Zhao Hai’s fingers were like iron casts, grasping the sword firmly.

Zhao Hai looked at Suo Liancheng and then smiled, “Alright. Suo Liancheng, you’re truly worthy of being a sword cultivator. Your sword is very sharp. However, I’m a Warrior as well. This sword cannot deal with me. You should surrender.”

If he was against other Cultivators, then Zhao Hai might not be able to tell them to admit defeat. But since Suo Liancheng was a sword cultivator, he doesn’t have any other magic artifact. Most sword cultivators wouldn’t use artifacts other than their swords. All of them were focused on their sword skills and to make it as sharp as possible. Suo Liancheng was the same.

When he saw Zhao Hai’s calm appearance, Suo Liancheng knew that it was already impossible for him to win. Suo Liancheng nodded, his voice solemn as he said, “Mister is correct. Since my sword can’t do anything, then this Suo Liancheng admits defeat.”

Zhao Hai laughed and then let go of Suo Liancheng’s sword. The golden sword hastened back to return. Then it flew around Suo Liancheng looking like a son who was complaining to his father about being bullied.

Suo Liancheng extended his hand and rubbed his sword, comforting it. Then after some time, the sword returned to its sheath on Suo Liancheng’s back.

Seeing Suo Liancheng’s action, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Suo Liancheng, it seems like you already have a grasp on the sword dao. You’re truly talented.”

Suo Liancheng smiled faintly and said, “Mister Zhao Hai is too polite. Mister is the true talent. You were able to reach this level of strength less than a year after ascending. This one is envious.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “To be honest, there are only a few Cultivators that have my respect. You’re one of them. I hope that we can meet again after this and become friends.”

Suo Liancheng looked at Zhao Hai deeply before heading down the arena. Since Zhao Hai won, then he would stay in the arena since he would have to fight Tu Mietan. But even if he lost, he would have to stay to accept Tu Mietan’s challenge.

One shouldn’t say that this was unfair to Zhao Hai. There are only a few things that’s fair in this world. The competition has rules, and these rules needed to be implemented. In fact, this was the rule that the Cultivation Realm prepared for him. In their minds, Zhao Hai was already strong. With his strength, victory was almost certain. As long as Zhao Hai won, then he would have to fight the second person immediately. This would give the other person a greater chance to defeat Zhao Hai.

But they didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be so strong and defeat Suo Liancheng in one move. He didn’t consume too much energy in the fight. This caused them to be surprised.

However, at this point, there was no way for them to change the competition’s rules. Therefore, they can only look at the arena to spectate Zhao Hai’s battle against Tu Mietan. The spectators didn’t have much expectations towards Tu Mietan. Although Tu Mietan was indeed strong, his strength could only be on par with Yi Shuihan or Yao Guang.  He would not be able to win against Suo Liancheng. Moreover, Suo Liancheng was the Cultivation Realm’s undisputable strongest rookie.

It was because of this that the other participants from the Cultivation Realm looked at Suo Liancheng with respect. After all, Suo Liancheng’s strength was the real deal. But Suo Liancheng was defeated by Zhao Hai in just one move. This meant that it would be very difficult for Tu Mietan to defeat Zhao Hai.

While Zhao Hai was waiting in the arena, he heard the sound of clothes ruffling before Tu Mietan stepped on the ground. Tu Mietan still wore his everlasting smile, then he gave Zhao Hai a salute as he said, “Tu Mietan has met Mister Zhao Hai. Mister Zhao Hai has great talent and strength. It’s an honor for me to fight you today.”

Zhao Hai returned the courtesy and said, “Mister Tu Mietan is too polite. I was also able to see Mister Tu Mietan’s strength in the past few days. To be honest, Mister Tu Mietan is strong as well. This Zhao Hai admires your strength. However, since we are in the arena, Mister will have to excuse me for being impolite.”

Tu Mietan felt somewhat strange. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be polite to someone like him. Moreover, Zhao Hai was more polite than him. But he quickly recovered and replied, “Mister is too polite. Mister, please.”

Zhao Hai gave a very polite bow. If this interaction didn’t happen in the arena, then the spectators might believe that they are seeing two friends greeting each other.

Upon seeing this scene, those from the Cultivation Realm couldn’t help but feel disappointed. They thought that the Devil Realm would make Zhao Hai their enemy. On the other hand, those from the Devil Realm were ecstatic. Seeing Zhao Hai being polite, this meant that he wasn’t worried about the fight. As long as Zhao Hai wasn’t worried, then the plan regarding the yin lightning mines might succeed.

The two people stood opposite to each other. Tu Mietan already took his blade and ghost face shield out. He didn’t take his flag out in the meantime. It seems like he’s trying to make Zhao Hai lower his guard.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai just stood there, he didn’t even take his magic staff out. Everyone  knew that Zhao Hai’s staff was an extraordinary weapon. If Zhao Hai took his staff out, then Tu Mietan wouldn’t have any chance of winning. Seeing Zhao Hai not equipping any weapon, this made Tu Mietan think that Zhao Hai has lowered his guard. The people from the Devil Realm were also becoming more confident in their victory.

At this time, Tu Mietan began to move. His blade cut towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai also took a step forward and punched.

Everyone stared. They haven’t seen Zhao Hai use his fist to attack his enemy before. But after Zhao Hai punched out, everyone’s expression changed. The speed of Zhao Hai’s punch was much faster compared to Suo Liancheng’s sword. A very short time after he punched out, the fist had already hit the ghost face shield.

Dang! Hao! The fist hit the ghost face shield. When the two collided, the shield screamed out before disintegrating. However, the fist didn’t lose momentum as it continued towards Tu Mietan. When it hit Tu Mietan’s body, Tu Mietan coughed out blood before his body was slammed to the ground. He was no longer breathing, he was killed by one fist.

Zhao Hai waved his hand as a clump of gas surrounded Tu Mietan’s body. Then as the gas disappeared, so did Tu Mietan’s corpse. Everyone spectating the battle couldn’t help but gawk upon seeing this outcome. Zhao Hai used the same method to deal with Jiang Tian. But at that time, Jiang Tian had used his life essence blood with the intention of killing Zhao Hai. This time, Tu Mietan didn’t even release a hint of killing intent. Zhao Hai’s response was too strange.

When Zhongli Qiang saw this, his eyes shook. He immediately stood up and said, “Zhao Hai, you dare!”

Zhao Hai turned his head towards Zhongli Qiang as he sneered and said, “And why shouldn’t I dare, Zhongli Qiang? First, you tried to poison us in Seamount City, and now you took out yin lightning mines to deal with me. Do you think that this Zhao Hai is an idiot? Hahaha. Isn’t Tu Mietan your once in a hundred years genius? Then this grandfather will make him into his Undead. Everyone who offends this Zhao Hai will pay the price!”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Zhongli Qiang calmed down. He looked at Zhao Hai with a cold gaze as he said, “Good, Zhao Hai, good. I didn’t expect you to make this move. Good, good. My Sacred Blood Sect will remember this.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “This Zhao Hai has a lot of enemies, what is one more? If you want revenge, then come at me! I will certainly entertain you.”

Zhongli Qiang coldly snorted and then sat down and closed his eyes. He was afraid that looking at Zhao Hai for long would force him to make a move.

Chapter 1271: Green Pine Swordsman

Zhao Hai looked at Zhongli Qiang and coldly sneered. His gaze swept the people from the Devil Realm and the Cultivation Realm before he returned to his seat among those from the Machine Field.

The battle for top three was finished. However, nobody thought that the tournament would be finished in this manner. It was too fast!

Moreover, Zhao Hai made everyone understand why he decided to kill Tu Mietan. As it turned out, the Devil Realm already made a move on Zhao Hai. No wonder Zhao Hai immediately killed Tu Mietan.

But there were some Cultivators whose eyes shone when they heard Zhao Hai. They shared their hatred for Zhao Hai with the Devil Realm. Now, the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm have been offended by Zhao Hai. The two realms now share a common enemy. Moreover, this enemy was currently in the Cultivation Realm.

For the Cultivators, dealing with Zhao Hai was the most important thing right now. The grievances and graciousness that they had with the Devil Realm would take too long to understand. Although the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm had some friction, this didn’t mean that the two hadn’t cooperated before. The Devil Realm shouldn’t reject cooperating with them in dealing with someone.

Some Cultivators looked at each other and saw that they all had the same idea. Then they all discussed in a low voice.

But it didn’t matter as to what they were discussing. Now that the battles have ended, the only thing left was the conclusion to the competition. Actually, this discussion didn’t have much to do with Zhao Hai. After all, he wouldn’t be able to obtain a lot of things, only two magic artifacts. To someone like Zhao Hai, two magic artifacts was nothing. What people were discussing were the Machine Field’s rewards.

What the Machine Field obtained this time was very rich. The several mineral mines as well as ore planets were things that the Machine Field needed.

The Cultivation Realm wouldn’t dare renege on giving the Machine Field their rewards. If they treated this matter unfairly, then it wouldn’t only affect the Machine Field, the other realms would also expect them to be unfair in the future. Nobody would join the competition anymore and then everyone would go back to fighting for resources.

Therefore, Zhao Hai and the others weren’t worried about the rewards. Zhao Hai doesn’t even need to be present for it. As long as Ma Rulong was there, then everything’s fine.

When Zhao Hai returned to the spectator seat, Ma Rulong immediately went to his side and said, “Little Hai, what do you want to do next? Those people from the Devil Realm wouldn’t let you off easily.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Team Leader, rest assured. Those people from the Devil Realm can’t do anything to me. You don’t have to worry about me. I think you should go and accept the Machine Field’s prize. Then you should return to the Machine Field alongside the others from the realm. Leave these people to me.”

Ma Rulong stared, then the color of his face changed as he said, “That’s no good. Little Hai, I can’t do that. Leaving you behind is too dangerous.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t worry, these trash can’t do anything to me. Also, if you stay behind, you won’t be able to do anything. Don’t forget, this is the Cultivation Realm. If you get in conflict with the Cultivators, it would give them justification to confiscate our rewards. Moreover, a lot of those from the Machine Field are from the realm’s powerful families. If they suffer an accident, then the relationship between Cultivation Realm and the Machine Field might get heated. Therefore, you should leave as soon as possible. I can stay here and deal with these people. I can just leave whenever I want. Don’t forget, I can also use space magic.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Ma Rulong kept silent for some time before he nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll listen to you. But Little Hai, you need to survive. I’ll wait for you in the Machine Field.” Zhao Hai nodded. Then Ma Rulong turned to talk to the other team leaders.

The team leaders also understood Zhao Hai’s intentions. They understood that if they continued to stay beside Zhao Hai, then they would only plunge themselves in danger. If they leave, then the Cultivators wouldn’t do anything to them. After all, they don’t have any enmity with them. But Zhao Hai would be in grave danger.

These people have known Zhao Hai for some time. Although they haven’t had much contact with each other, they had a good impression of him after exchanging drinks with him a few times. They were touched when Zhao Hai decided to face danger alone for them.

But what these people didn’t know was that Zhao Hai had another reason for making them leave. In addition to not pulling them into danger, Zhao Hai also made them leave so that he can enter the Space at any time. If these people were present, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t be able to enter the Space whenever he wants. With these fellows present, Zhao Hai had a lot of means that he couldn’t use.

Zhao Hai doesn’t want a lot of people to know of his secrets. He didn’t even tell Xiong Li and the others about his secrets, not to say about these people.

The actions on Zhao Hai’s side were seen by other people. They saw that Ma Rulong and Zhao Hai discussed for a while before Ma Rulong took the team leaders and left, leaving Zhao Hai alone on the participant’s seats. When they saw this scene, people from the other realms were confused. They don’t know what the Machine Field was doing.

The other realms didn’t expect Ma Rulong to give up on Zhao Hai this way. Although Zhao Hai had offended both the Devil Realm and the Cultivation Realm, he also made a lot of contributions towards the Machine Field. If the Machine Field gave up on Zhao Hai, then this would affect the entire realm’s morale.

Zhao Hai didn’t actually care too much about what was happening around him. He just calmly sat on his seat. Now that Ma Rulong and the others left, he was the only one left. But at this moment, Cai’er was reporting about what the other realms were doing.

Cai’er told Zhao Hai that the Devil Realm and the Cultivation Realm have been talking in secret. They were also prepared to deal with him. This wasn’t surprisig for Zhao Hai.

At this moment, the prizes were beginning to be distributed. It wasn’t Zhao Hai and the others that received the prizes but instead the representatives from their respective groups. Naturally, Ma Rulong represented the Machine Field.

The awarding ceremony ended quickly. At this point, the Cultivation Realm wouldn’t cheat anyone. Moreover, the prizes were very good. The property rights of mineral mines and ore planets were given to the Machine Field. However, these were mere papers that would lose their value come five years. In the past, these deeds were being passed on inwardly among the Cultivators. This was the first time where the deeds fell into the hands of the other realms.

After Ma Rulong received the prize, he immediately brought the other team leaders towards the spectator stands. The others from the Machine Field had yet to leave. They were planning on sharing a cup or two with Zhao Hai after the competition. After all, Zhao Hai won, so there was a reason for celebrating.

When Ma Rulong arrived, he immediately told everyone about what Zhao Hai plans to do next and then urged them to leave. Everyone couldn’t help but get stuck in their seats as they turned to look at Zhao Hai, their hearts couldn’t bear leaving. They were core members, the elite of great families. Therefore, they were moved by Zhao Hai’s action.

However, none of them thought about staying behind and dying with Zhao Hai. Firstly, this was because they weren’t that close with Zhao Hai. And secondly, even if they stayed, they didn’t have the strength to aid Zhao Hai. Their best course of action was leaving this place as soon as possible.

Everyone agreed and then they proceeded towards the transmission formation. After that, they took another transmission formation to go back to the Machine FIeld. When those from the Cultivation Realm were about to make a move, Ma Rulong’s shadow could no longer be seen.

Just now, their attention was on Zhao Hai and not on Ma Rulong. They thought that Ma Rulong wouldn’t give up on Zhao Hai. They expected Ma Rulong and the others to join Zhao Hai after they received their award. However, they didn’t think that Ma Rulong would immediately leave. This caused the Cultivators to react too late.

At this point, the Cultivars knew that they had been tricked by Zhao Hai. However, they weren’t too angry about it. This was because the Machine Field’s rewards would just last for five years. They wouldn’t be able to increase their strength in such a short time. Also, they couldn’t do anything to Ma Rulong unless they wanted to attract the resentment of the entire World of Cultivation. For them, it was fine as long as Zhao Hai stayed behind. He was their main goal after all.

Zhao Hai seemed to be unaffected as he just sat there and observed the other realms. The Elves, Sprites, and Demons were beginning to leave. As for the Cultivators and the people from the Devil Realm, only a part of them left the arena. The rest remained.

The other realms knew that something was about to happen, therefore they hastened their departure. When everyone else had left, the people from the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm surrounded Zhao Hai.

The one heading this group was Devil Realm’s Zhongli Qiang as well as a Core Formation Expert from the Cultivation Realm. Actually, this Core Formation Expert was the one that Zhao Hai had a conflict with earlier.

This Core Formation Expert was Jiang Tian’s master, Fu Yishan, also known as the Green Pine Swordsman. Fu Yishan was a wood-element Cultivator. Most wood-element Cultivators wouldn’t take up the sword since their nature wasn’t compatible with sword techniques. They would often make use of wooden artifacts as well as poison in battles. These materials weren’t suitable for making a sword.

However, Fu Yishan was a lucky man. During an expedition, he came upon an uninhabited mountain that had a thin pine tree that was about a meter tall. When he found this tree, Fu Yishan saw a lot of dead monster bones on its base. The bones of these monsters were green. One could see at first sight that they were poisoned.

This caused Fu Yishan to be curious about the mountain. After careful research, he discovered that it was the pine tree that had caused this phenomenon. It had turned everything around it poisonous. Moreover, its body had turned firm like steel. Because of this, he was able to fashion the pine tree into a sword.

Fu Yishan spent a lot of effort on the mountain as he refined the tree. In the end, he was able to refine the poisonous green pine sword and make it his Life Source Weapon. This sword also gave him the nickname Green Pine Swordsman.

Chapter 1272: Brutal Attack

Fu Yishan looked at Zhao Hai with a vicious gaze. He hates Zhao Hai not because he killed Jiang Tian. Jiang Tian was just one of his disciples, and he hasn’t even been promoted into a formal disciple. Although Fu Yishan felt some pain when Jiang Tian died, it wasn’t a pressing situation for him.

Fu Yishan hated Zhao Hai because Zhao Hai publicly slapped his face. For the Cultivators, face was as valuable as their lives. Therefore, at this point, he wanted to eat Zhao Hai’s meat and drink his blood.

Standing not far away from Fu Yishan was Zhongli Qiang. The Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm had united to deal with Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai continued sitting calmly as he looked at the two groups of people. Then after a moment, he began to laugh. Fu Yishan looked at Zhao Hai’s reaction and couldn’t help but snort as he said, “Zhao Hai, you’re still laughing even though you’re about to die. I admire your courage.”

Zhao Hai looked at Fu Yishan and then replied, “I didn’t expect the righteous Cultivators from the Cultivation Realm to cooperate with the Devil Realm. You have given this Zhao Hai huge face.”

Zhongli Qiang coldly snorted and said, “Zhao Hai, there’s no need for you to buy time. Those people from the Machine Field wouldn’t be in any danger, but they also won’t be able to come back to save you. The transmission formations have already been closed. All you can do now is die.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Zhongli Qiang, you’re too naive. You think I’m hoping for them to come back? Let me tell you the truth, I asked them to leave. Otherwise, would they just give up on me? If they left me behind, then the Ascenders in the Machine Field would revolt. When the time comes, even three-year olds would know how much trouble it would bring.”

Zhongli Qiang and Fu Yishan looked at each other. They believed what Zhao Hai was saying. In fact, they found it strange when Ma Rulong left with everyone else from the Machine Field. Losing Zhao Hai here wouldn’t bring any advantage to the Machine Field. Even if they obtained the mines and the ore planets, losing the trust of the people as a tradeoff wasn’t worth it. Ma Rulong should be smart enough to know about this.

But Ma Rulong actually left, this caused the two to be puzzled. So after hearing Zhao Hai, they immediately knew that it was true. Only Zhao Hai could make Ma Rulong leave like that, otherwise Ma Rulong would have stayed.

At this time, the two couldn’t understand why Zhao Hai would do this. Not only would this disadvantage him, it would place him in extreme danger. Was Zhao Hai a selfless person? Fu Yishan and Zhongli Qiang wouldn’t dare believe so.

It doesn’t matter if they were from the Cultivation Realm or the Devil Realm, all of them were innately selfish. It was impossible for them to sacrifice their lives for others. If they can’t win, then they would have other people die in place of them.

Seeing the appearance of the two, Zhao Hai immediately knew what they were thinking about. He smiled faintly and said, “You two can’t understand why I would do that? Letting others go while I stay behind to brave the dangers isn’t something a wise person would do right?”

Seeing Fu Yishan and Zhongli Qiang turning silent, Zhao Hai laughed and said, “I stayed behind because I’m going to kill some people. Some people need to die so that others would be afraid of me. I want people to know that if they want to plot against me, then they need to make sure that their necks are hard enough!”

Zhao Hai’s words were filled with a very thick killing aura. Zhongli Qiang and Fu Yishan didn’t expect Zhao Hai’s plan to be like this.

When they were hit with Zhao Hai’s killing aura, the two couldn’t help but be a bit frightened. Although these two had seen great storms, this was the first time they saw someone like Zhao Hai.

Although people from the Devil Realm were in a constant state of murder, they just kill people for their cultivation. Moreover, what they killed were mostly civilians. The teachings in the Devil Realm were different. In the eyes of the people from the Devil Realm, these commoners were not humans at all. They were farm animals that could be slaughtered whenever they were needed. Would a butcher feel bad about killing a pig? Because of this, practitioners from the Devil Realm had no psychological burden when killing commoners.

However, practitioners from the Devil Realm treat other practitioners as people. And they wouldn’t easily make a move against them. When Zhongli Qiang heard Zhao Hai, he felt that Zhao Hai wasn’t treating them as humans at all. He just wanted to kill. That’s why Zhongli Qiang was startled.

Zhao Hai looked at those present as he laughed and said, “You look startled. Do you think that this Zhao Hai is a good man? Hahahaha. All of you are going to die today. If you don’t believe me, then take a look for yourself.”

When Fu Yishan and Zhongli Qiang looked around them, their faces couldn’t help but change color. This was because they had been surrounded by a dense number of Undead. These Undead filled up the entire vicinity of the void arena. Even they couldn’t count how many Undead there were.

Most importantly, the void arena’s transmission formations have been occupied by the Undead. In other words, those present here wouldn’t be able to escape. Moreover, they could no longer get any reinforcements. They can only stay here and fight against Zhao Hai.

Seeing all of the Undead around them, Fu Yishan and Zhongli Qiang couldn’t help but feel their scalp tingle. The sheer number was terrifying.

At this time, Zhao Hai loudly said, “Brothers, reveal who you are. Let our guests open their eyes.” Along with his command, the Undead all roared as their skeletal frame began growing flesh and blood. Before long, the Undead wore their human appearance.

This change caused those from the Devil Realm and the Cultivation Realm to be surprised. They have never seen Undead act like this. Moreover, they knew some of them.

There were people standing beside Zhao Hai. There’s Helian Da, Jiang Tian, and also Tu Mietan!

These people were too familiar to them. They even saw them being killed by Zhao Hai. But now these people were standing beside Zhao Hai. How could they not be surprised.

However, they were quick to discover that these Undead didn’t become alive. They were Zombies.

There were a lot of zombies in the World of Cultivation. Some of these zombies appear naturally. These zombies could cultivate themselves after being born. As for zombies that were created, they were treated like weapons for battle. Naturally, those who use zombies were generally Ghost Cultivators or people from the Devil Realm.

However, even if one wasn’t from the Devil Realm, they were still quite familiar with zombies. Sometimes, zombies from the Devil Realm would find a way to go to the Cultivation Realm. There were also times when zombies were seen in clashes against the Devil Realm. Since they weren’t that uncommon, people were quick to recognize that Helian Da and the others had been turned into zombies.

Zhao Hai revealed a lot of his strength this time. Aside from the beast-shaped Undead, he released nearly 200 million Undead. All of these Undead stood firmly and were equipped with the bone armor. In their hands were weapons that were made by the Space. And these weapons each had a weapon shattering formation inside them. It can be said that the Undead were fully armed.

The Void Arena wasn’t a huge asteroid field. If the Void Arena was as large as the Rainbow Meteorite Field, then even the most powerful Cultivators wouldn’t be able to transform it. Therefore, the 200 million Undead were able to fill the arena.

Additionally, besides the weapon made by the Space, some of the Undead also had something else on their other hand. These looked much like yin lightning mines!

These yin lightning mines were newly made by the Space. After getting the ones in Tu Mietan’s hand, Cai’er detonated one and then collected all data pertaining to it. Then the mines are deconstructed by the processing machine and then reconstructed once more. After that, the mines were analyzed by the scanner to see the formations inside. And since the Space has generated the materials needed to construct the mines, it could now produce it whenever.

However, since Zhao Hai had the yin lightning mines for a short time, the materials available only allowed the manufacture of 1000 mines. Then these mines were distributed among the Undead.

At this time, the Cultivators and the people from the Devil Realm got closer to each other as they faced the Undead surrounding them. Their weapons were already out, prepared to attack at any time.

Zhao Hai was still sitting on his seat, looking at these people with a cold gaze. Zhongli Qiang and Fu Yishan fell back to the middle of the group, their weapons also held in their hands.

Then suddenly, Zhao Hai’s cold voice was heard, “In the World of Cultivation, the bigger your fist, the less you need to talk. Everyone, kill them all!” Then along with Zhao Hai’s command, the Undead moved and went straight to killing.

Fu Yishan and Zhongli Qiang’s group immediately used their magic artifacts and retaliated against the Undead. All kinds of artifacts flew into the air. However, the Undead arranged themselves in a neat formation as they sent attack after attack.

The Undead were currently in cube formations as they pressed towards the Cultivators and the Devil Cultivators. The Cultivators and Devil Cultivators started out with a spherical formation. But in the end they had been pressed down and forced to flatten their formation.

Offensive and defensive artifacts flew constantly as the Cultivators fought off the Undead. But because they didn’t have a unified command structure, their fighting style was chaotic.

Zhongli Qiang and Fu Yishan were quick to discover this point. Therefore, they immediately took command and coordinated everyone. Some Cultivators were assigned for defense while others were in charge of offense.

However, the coordination between the Undead was flawless. And with Lizzy and Megan in command, the flow of the battle was soon grasped by the Undead. Although the artifacts of the Cultivators and Devil Practitioners were strong, the Undead casualty wasn’t a lot. They gradually pressed towards the Cultivators and the Devil Practitioners.

The Cultivators and the Devil Practitioners began to grow more anxious. Zhao Hai’s Undead were too formidable. They weren’t easily broken when attacked and they even have armors that give them powerful defense.

When the Undead reached a certain distance away from the Cultivators, they all stopped at the same time. Then those with yin lightning mines went forward and threw the mines towards the circular formation. These mines weren’t larger than walnuts. And as they reached the formation, they detonated at the same time.

Purple colored lightning lit up the circular formation. These were the yin lightning mines that were quite famed in the World of Cultivation.

Although the Cultivators and Devil Practitioners had a lot of artifacts in hand, they still couldn’t perfectly defend against this many yin lightning mines. When the mines exploded, the formation immediately broke. Cultivators and Devil Cultivators did their best to defend themselves from the destructive power of the yin lightning mines.

The Cultivators and Devil Practitioners that were left behind after the explosion weren’t a lot. In the beginning, there were more or less 100 of them. Although these people were very strong, the yin lightning mines were very formidable. Once the purple lightning vanished, Zhao Hai looked at the formation and couldn’t help but get terrified.

The circle formation was reduced to a scant number of people. All around them were dozens of corpses, while the others were erased from sight.

Brutal, too brutal! This was more than 100 Foundation Establishment Experts as well as Core Formation experts. All of them vanished, their artifacts reduced to fragments. The explosion was just too savage.

There were some Cultivators and Devil Practitioners who managed to survive due to sheer luck. They also couldn’t believe that 100 Foundation Establishment Experts and Core Formation Experts would vanish just like that. Even in the Cultivation Realm, such a group of people couldn’t be underestimated. But now, all of these people were reduced to a very few – most of them turned into ash.

But what rang loudly inside the minds of these remnants were the weapons that the Undead used. These were yin lightning mines! And it wasn’t only one or two, but more than a thousand!

Chapter 1273: Modified Yin Lightning Mines

These were yin lightning mines, not ordinary stones from the roadside that you can just throw at passersby. Yin thunder mines were famed in the World of Cultivation not only because of its lethality, but also because of how difficult they were to make.

But now, Zhao Hai took out a thousand yin thunder mines. Were these mines trash in his eyes?

Zhao Hai was very satisfied with his victory. But what he was unsatisfied about was the lack of harvests. To be honest, Zhao Hai didn’t expect the yin thunder mines to be this destructive. It killed about 100 people, and these were experts who have defensive artifacts.

At the same time, Zhao Hai was happy about the Undead’s performance. Their coordination was already very good, but now that they have yin lightning mines, their strength has increased by one layer.

Zhao Hai was initially worried about the Undead’s strength. Currently, the Undead have strength equal to Qi Condensation Cultivators. In the World of Cultivation, they were still really weak. Although they were now studying Cultivation Methods, increasing their strength in a short time was impossible.

The blood lightning beads might be a powerful weapon in the lower realms, but they can’t do much in the World of Cultivation. Even low-level Cultivators couldn’t be damaged by the blood lightning beads. Because of this, the main method of the Undead’s offense has been rendered useless.

Now that there’s the yin lightning mines, this weakness has been taken care of. As long as they were given time, all of the Undead would be equipped with yin lightning mines. This will enhance the strength of the Undead once more.

Zhao Hai wasn’t polite and ordered the Undead to eradicate the survivors. The Cultivators and Devil Practitioners that were left had already lost their confidence. In this case, it was easy for the Undead to clean them up.

Once the fight was over, Zhao Hai turned the dead Cultivators and Devil Practitioners into Undead. Then he commanded the Undead to clean up the surroundings. At the same time, all traces of energy around the area needed to be erased.

Zhao Hai remembered what he saw back in the bug caves. Upon analyzing the remnant energy of the battle, Suo Liancheng was able to restore the fight scene. This time, Zhao Hai wouldn’t make such a careless mistake. The battlefield has been cleaned up and the energy traces have been smoothed out.

If Zhao Hai doesn’t clean up the battlefield, then others would see that he had used a lot of yin lightning mines in the battle. Zhao Hai doesn’t want others to know that he had this much ying lightning mines. If the others knew, then they would be prepared, reducing the impact of the mines in the battlefield.

Zhao Hai wasn’t satisfied because the yin lightning mines killed a lot of his enemies. He was happy because even if the mines killed the Cultivators and Devil Practitioners, it wasn’t too destructive by itself.

If the Cultivators and Devil Practitioners weren’t huddled up at that time and instead scattered themselves, then the yin lightning mines wouldn’t be able to kill a lot of them. It was because they were close to each other that the yin thunder mines were able to display a lot of might.

If the yin lightning mines were truly powerful, then Lin Jiang wouldn’t have handed them over. And the Devil Realm shouldn’t have made Tu Mietan use it sneakily. One could see the limitations of the yin lightning mines from this point. Only when there’s a large number of them would they exert their formidable power.

After everything has been processed, Zhao Hai teleported to the Space. As for the transmission formations in the Void Arena, he placed seals on it so that reactivating them in a short time would be impossible.

Upon entering the Space, Zhao Hai discovered that Laura and the others were busily discussing the data collected from the battle. The scene looked like they were having a conference.

They could look for weak points through this post-battle analysis. This way, they wouldn’t make the same mistake the next time.

Presently, the Universal Processing Machine was making yin lightning mines. These mines would definitely be very useful for the Undead. It has more utility compared to magic artifacts and paper talismans. Although these mines were known for being difficult to mass-produce, the Space was an anomaly that could do the impossible. And once the Space gains the ability to mass-produce these yin lightning mines, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t need to fear anybody.

The usage of yin lightning mines this time brought out several issues. The first issue was the distance where the mines could be used. Yin lightning mines were different compared to most magic artifacts. In the World of Cultivation, things like the yin lightning mines were considered to be hidden weapons. People only cared about their power and not how to control them.

When controlling magic artifacts, Cultivators would use their spiritual force and tap into the artifact’s core. Then they would control the artifact through this core. This way, even if the artifact was damaged, the spiritual force used to control it wouldn’t be affected too much. And since magic artifacts rarely get destroyed, Cultivators weren’t too worried about damaging their spiritual force.

However, consumable weapons like yin lightning mines were different. These weapons wouldn’t have formation cores so they couldn’t be controlled with much flexibility. But if they were equipped with formation cores, even if they can be controlled better, once they explode the spiritual force of the user would be heavily damaged.

When ordinary artifacts get destroyed, they were crushed from the outside to the inside. And since these artifacts were most often made with quality materials, their formation cores would have good defenses and would protect the user’s spiritual force.

On the other hand, yin thunder mines were exploding artifacts. These artifacts start to explode from inside out. If there was a formation core, then the user’s spiritual force would no doubt be damaged. Once the yin lightning mines explode, the first to be damaged wouldn’t be the enemy, but the user. Because of this, exploding artifacts like the yin lightning mines don’t have any system for flexible control. They would only be made to be as powerful as possible. Because of this, yin lightning mines could only be used during sneak attacks or large-scale like what the Undead did. Only through these methods could the yin lightning mines display their true power.

The yin lightning mines’ greatest problem right now was control. So what Zhao Hai needed to do was find a way to fix this problem as well as reduce its threat to the user’s spiritual force.

After undergoing the analysis of the scanner, Zhao Hai managed to obtain a diagram for a modified yin lightning mine. Originally, a large part of the formations inside the mines were for sealing yin lightning inside while the others were used for activating the mine as well as increasing its explosive might.

But in the diagram that Zhao Hai obtained, new magic formations were added to the mines. These formations could seal the yin lightning while also increasing the mine’s explosive might. More importantly, these magic formations allowed the existence of a formation core.

This formation allowed the control of the artifact. Ordinarily, this formation core shouldn’t be placed inside the mine. But in the diagram, this formation core had an additional formation that has only one function, and that was to delay the mine’s activation.

This delay would activate once the user activates the yin lightning mine. It would delay the explosion by a fraction of a second. Even if it was just a moment’s time, this delay would allow the user to evacuate their spiritual force from the formation core. This way, the user wouldn’t be injured by using the yin lightning mines. This would also provide the user with a firm control over the mines.

One shouldn’t underestimate this simple modification. If it weren’t for the scanner, then even if someone spent hundreds of years researching, they wouldn’t be able to find the compatible formations and magic formations to achieve this feat.

After obtaining this diagram, Zhao Hai immediately ordered its production. These yin lightning mines would definitely become great weapons for the Undead.

Just like Zhao Hai, the Undead have never used magic artifacts before. If they were equipped with magic artifacts that they weren’t familiar with, then it would take some time for them to use it. The Undead needed to be taught the Cultivation Realm’s cultivation methods and then practice it. Only then would the Undead become Cultivators. In the future, they wouldn’t be different to the Cultivators from the Demon Realm.

In the World of Cultivation, Demon Cultivators don’t only refer to plants or beasts that were able to cultivate. These Demon Cultivators also include Zombies and Ghosts. However, even if these Zombies and Ghosts cultivate their own cultivation methods, they could still be considered to be Cultivators.

The Undead inside the Space were heading towards this direction. Zhao Hai was heavily advocating for this to be pushed through. In the future, the Space’s Undead would become a powerful influence in the World of Cultivation.

……….

While inside the Space, Zhao Hai wasn’t only researching new ideas. He was also paying attention to the Machine Field’s situation. Naturally, when Ma Rulong and the others returned to the Machine Field, they were met with a hero’s welcome. However, upon seeing that Zhao Hai wasn’t with them, the entire realm went into an uproar. There were several powers in the Machine Field that wanted to go to the Cultivation Realm to save Zhao Hai. However, they didn’t succeed since the transmission formations had been closed. And if they use battleships to head to the Cultivation Realm, then this would be taken as a declaration of war.

Because of this, the Machine Field could only protest the Cultivation Realm to open the transmission formations as soon as possible. However, the Cultivation Realm didn’t answer. It was as though they were delaying for time.

Chapter 1274: Becoming a Celebrity

Actually, the people from the Cultivation Realm felt strange. The Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm knew that Fu Yishan and Zhongli Qiang were taking care of Zhao Hai back in the Void Arena. And to prevent people from rescuing Zhao Hai, they blockaded the transmission formation.

However, how long has it been? The Cultivators knew that there were more than 100 people who remained to deal with Zhao Hai. Although most of them were Foundation Establishment Experts, these experts were still at the top of their level. As for geniuses like Suo Liancheng, they all returned to their sects since they still need to cultivate.

In the minds of the Cultivators, dealing with Zhao Hai shouldn’t be dangerous and there’s no need for that many people to remain in order to deal with him. A lot of those experts who remained did so for their reputation. They would be able to boast later on that, “Remember the Machine Field’s genius Zhao Hai? He was killed by us!” Nobody was thinking that they would fail.

Naturally, Zhao Hai knew about all of these. However, he didn’t want to return to the Machine Field yet. Those were more than 100 experts. If he went back now and those experts go missing, then wouldn’t that be terrifying? When the time comes, even Transcending Tribulation Experts would come deal with him. He wasn’t prepared for that kind of trouble yet.

Zhao Hai wasn’t idling inside the Space. He was studying Yao Guang’s formations. These formations need flags and disks to function, but Zhao Hai doesn’t need to worry about them. He has liquid silver that could transform. Whether it was a flag or a disk, it can replace them.

Zhao Hai knew that he had offended the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm for real this time. People from these two realms would certainly find trouble with him in the future. And there would definitely be formation experts among these people. The World of Cultivation was a very unusual place. So even if he has the Space, he couldn’t depend on it for safety all the time. Moreover, Zhao Hai doesn’t want to reveal the Space’s secret. Revealing it would only bring him even greater trouble. Because of this, he wanted to understand as many formations as possible. Therefore, even if he doesn’t use the Space, he could still break out of formations. Only then could he keep the Space a secret.

The Machine FIeld and the Cultivation Realm were at a stalemate while Zhao Hai was hiding inside the Space. At the same time, the people in the Devil Realm weren’t saying anything. For a time, it was as if everyone had forgotten about the Void Arena.

Zhao Hai stayed inside the Space for about seven or eight days. During this period of time, the Cultivation Realm began to react. They couldn’t understand what’s taking so long. And after seeing that the Void Arena’s transmission formations have been sealed, they were even more confused. Some groups immediately sent some people on transportation artifacts to the Void Arena to break the seal on the transmission formation.

People from the Devil Realm also felt that something wasn’t right. However, they don’t believe that Zhao Hai could do anything to Zhongli Qiang and the others. What they were afraid of was the Cultivators taking the opportunity to attack the Devil Realm’s people. Therefore, they also sent people to the Void Arena to check the situation.

Because this matter was a joint operation between the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm, the Cultivators didn’t stop them. Several groups were rushing over to the Void Arena.

Of course, Zhao Hai noticed this situation from inside the Space. Although he hasn’t been to a lot of places in the Cultivation Realm, he at least knew the situation in Seamount City. There were all kinds of rumors circulating inside the city at this moment. It was through these rumors that Zhao Hai became aware of what happened. He also knew that it was time for him to return.

After saying goodbye to Laura and the others, Zhao Hai’s body disappeared from the Space and reappeared just outside the Ashley Family’s building in Machine Field Planet.

At this time, the family’s office was very busy. Zhao Hai chose to appear in this place because Margaret was currently here.

Naturally, Margaret was only here officially. She still spent most of her time inside the Space. Some time ago, Margaret had to go back to Dark Demon Planet. But now, under the reason that she was waiting for Zhao Hai, she relocated to Machine Field Planet. However, she spent most of her time inside her room and declined all visitors. She just went to the Space and played around with Laura and the others.

As soon as Zhao Hai appeared outside the Ashley Family’s building, he immediately noticed that there were a lot of people from the family’s External Halls present. These people weren’t young. All of them were Ascenders with close to zero chance of breaking through. Therefore, they looked for work. And since the Ashley Family was expanding, their headquarters in the capital planet needed personnel to greet the guests as well as to guard the building. This gave the people from the External Halls slots for new jobs.

Zhao Hai appeared very suddenly. People were able to see him but they had yet to process who they saw. Zhao Hai just nodded at them as he walked towards the building.

It was also at this time that people recovered. They had just seen Zhao Hai. They immediately flew towards the building, even overtaking Zhao Hai as they yelled, “Zhao Hai’s here! Zhao Hai is here!” The voices were too loud that people might even think that someone was coming to rob the place.

Zhao Hai stared, then he smiled bitterly as he shook his head. He had already seen the Machine Field’s attitude towards him while he was inside the Space. People from External Halls were already regarding him as their idol. Knowing that he had yet to come back, they were the first people to stage a protest, requesting the realm’s higher-ups to retrieve him. Under the pressure, the Machine Field’s higher-ups had to get into conversation with the Cultivators. However, they still don’t have the courage to go to war.

Now that he was back, it was given that the entire Machine Field would be in a stir. At this time, Margaret flew down from her room and dashed towards Zhao Hai. Seeing Margaret’s appearance, Zhao Hai laughed and said, “I just bid goodbye to you inside the Space, you already miss me?”

While being in Zhao Hai’s embrace, Margaret whispered, “It’s an act. Sister Laura said to accompany you.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Really? So you aren’t thinking of me?”

Margaret squeezed her grip on Zhao Hai, but she didn’t say anything. In the eyes of other people, they looked like two lovers who haven’t seen each other for a long time. So naturally they didn’t see anything wrong.

At this time, Desbarres and Luke flew out of the building. Desbarres has been in Machine FIeld Planet for a while now. On one hand, he was waiting for Zhao Hai. And on the other hand, he was helping Luke since the office had been too busy because of the Ashley Family’s expansion. There were now more jobs on the planet so Luke needed an experienced person like Desbarres to help him.

After a while, Margaret let go of Zhao Hai and then stood behind him. When they saw this, Desbarres and Luke walked over. Zhao Hai looked at Desbarres and gave a salute as he said, “Camp Lord, I’m back.”

Desbarres looked at Zhao Hai, his eyes were a little red. He hugged Zhao Hai for some time before releasing him, then he patted Zhao Hai’s shoulders vigorously as he said, “Alright, you’re back, good, good. Hahaha. It’s good that you’re back.”

Luke also gave Zhao Hai a firm hug. Then he led Zhao Hai to walk into the building. But at this time, more and more people were encircling them. Zhao Hai was now the hero of the Machine Field, so all of them wanted to come over to greet him.

Majority of these people have seen Zhao Hai, and they wanted to go over and say hello. Zhao Hai responded to them all. Moreover, he called them with their names. When these people heard their own names being called, they couldn’t help but feel very lucky. There were also some new people who had yet to meet Zhao Hai. Naturally, Zhao Hai couldn’t neglect them. So he met them one by one and listened to their introductions.

In this case, Zhao Hai could hardly enter the building. And more and more people were arriving. Zhao Hai didn’t expect everyone to be this enthusiastic, he was stuck on wondering what to do for a moment.

Among the people who crowded the place was a beautiful woman wearing work clothes. Behind her was another person holding a small device. The light on the device was covering Zhao Hai’s body. When he saw this, Zhao Hai didn’t put on guards, he knew that this must be the cameras of the Machine Field. It seems like these people were from the news agencies.

Sure enough, the beautiful woman pointed a microphone towards Zhao Hai and then asked a question, “Mister Zhao Hai, welcome back. How did you come back to the Machine Field? Is it true that you have been chased by the Cultivators?”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel proud, he didn’t expect someone from the news agencies would come and interview him. He cleared his throat and then said, “I used space magic to return. And I didn’t encounter any Cultivators. I just had something to do after the competition, so I asked Team Leader Ma Rulong to excuse me.”

This was the excuse that Zhao Hai thought of beforehand. He wouldn’t admit that he had met an attack. In this case, the Cultivation Realm and the Demon Realm would have no reason to go look for him for trouble. Oh, you have more than 100 people missing? What does that have to do with me? I don’t know them, I haven’t even seen them, so why are you asking me? I have something to do and I just took care of it. What did I do? Why should I tell you?

Even if everyone knew what he did, he would never admit it. If he did, then this would give the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm an excuse to deal with him fairly. People from the two realms would unite and put pressure on the Machine Field. This wasn’t something that Zhao Hai wanted to see.

Both the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm wanted to swallow the Machine Field. But since everyone had some reservations, nobody wanted to make the first move. If Zhao Hai admits what he did, then the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm would be given the opportunity to unite. If these two realms cooperate, then the Machine Field would be in grave danger. Even if they were able to repel the two realms, the losses they would suffer wouldn’t be small. And Zhao Hai doesn’t want the Machine Field to go to war yet.

Chapter 1275: Do You Believe It?

Zhao Hai was sitting in a room drinking hot tea. Margaret was sitting beside him while Desbarres and Luke were on the opposite side. They had just finished dealing with the visitors and finally got the opportunity to go inside a room.

Desbarres looked at Zhao Hai and laughed as he said, “Little Hai, you’re famous now. Look at all the people outside. Every one of them is crazy to meet you. Hahaha. I’m somewhat jealous.”

Zhao Hai grumpily replied, “Camp Lord, how could this be good? Have you seen their faces? It seems like they want me to stay there forever.”

Desbarres and Luke laughed. Then Luke smiled and said, “We also want to get the same treatment. Unfortunately, even if we deliver ourselves to be interviewed, they would still ignore us.”

Zhao Hai chuckled, then he shifted the topic, “Camp Lord, why is the office so crowded today? Is there a party going on?”

Of course, Zhao Hai knows what’s happening. He just asked since he shouldn’t know about it. This was, he wouldn’t be too suspicious.

Desbarres smiled and said, “The family borrowed your light. Now these people have come to manage our businesses. The family has undergone a great transformation. It’s in a much better state than before. I really can’t describe it in a few words. So how about you? Why did you only return now?”

Zhao Hai placed his teacup down, then he smiled faintly and said, “I’m afraid that Team Leader Ma Rulong and the others would be in danger while returning with the deeds. So I stayed behind to take attention away from them. Then I fought with people from the Cultivation Realm and Devil Realm before coming back.”

Desbarres’ expression changed, he immediately replied, “You really fought? Did the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm work together to deal with you?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Right. Didn’t I kill their participants during the tournament? Those guys are unbearably angry about that. They wanted to keep me from leaving the Cultivation Realm. Unfortunately, they failed.”

Luke looked puzzled as he asked, “But didn’t you say that you didn’t fight anyone? Why…” But before he could continue, he was interrupted by Desbarres.

Luke turned to Desbarres who smiled and said, “This matter cannot be told to anyone. This way, even if Little Hai has come back, the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm couldn’t do anything about it. Am I right, Little Hai?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Camp Lord really knows me. Now, they’ll have no reason to deal with me. This time, I killed more than 100 people, all of them have all kinds of backgrounds. Therefore, this matter cannot be known. Or else, not only would I be in trouble, I’ll also be taking the Machine Field with me.”

Upon hearing this, Luke couldn’t help but breathe in cold air. Desbarres was also greatly surprised. Although he expected that Zhao Hai had dealt with those people from the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm, he expected it to be a small group. However, upon knowing that there were more than 100 people, he couldn’t help but be astonished.

However, the two were also people who had seen their fair share of storms, so they were able to quickly recover. Then Desbarres said, “Did anyone escape?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Camp Lord can rest assured, I made sure that nobody escaped. So as long as I don’t admit it, nobody would have any evidence.”

Desbarres relaxed, then he nodded and said, “Alright. Who else knows about this? Does Ma Rulong know?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I haven’t told him about this matter yet, you can rest assured. After I killed those guys, I immediately returned here. Besides you two, nobody else knows about this. However, I reckon this thing will catch wind sooner or later. But since the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm have no evidence, they can only bite air. They can’t attack me deliberately either since they wouldn’t have any reason to do so. Moreover, even if they proceed, they would still be publicly berated by the other realms. So there’s no need to worry. Everything should be alright.”

Desbarres nodded, “Then that’s good. I’ll report this matter to the Patriarch, but don’t tell anybody else about it. Right, what’s the matter with Xiong Li and the others? Why did they immediately close up? Are they injured?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “They’re fine. Right, since we’re on this topic, I have something to tell you. Camp Lord, Mister Luke, have you heard about the Six Realms Battlefield?”

As soon as Desbarres and Luke heard Zhao Hai, the color of their faces changed. The two looked at each other, then Desbarres turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Did Ma Rulong tell you?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Right, Team Leader Ma told me. He asked me to go to the Six Realms Battlefield with Xiong Li and the others for a period of time. I agreed.”

Desbarres frowned as he sat there. He didn’t make any noise for some time. Luke was silent as well. It’s clear that the two knew about the Six Realms Battlefield.

After some time, Desbarres sighed and said, “It’s fine to go to the Six Realms Battlefield for practice. Although the place is too dangerous, you shouldn’t have any problems there given your strength. You can go there and see for yourself.”

Luke nodded and said, “You should take a look. It seems like Ma Rulong is favoring you. Once you come back from the Six Realms Battlefield, nobody from the Machine Field would be able to underestimate you.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Right. But I still have another thing to tell you. After I come back from the Six Realms Battlefield, I’m planning to go independent along with Xiong Li and the others. What does Camp Lord think about this?”

As soon as Desbarres heard Zhao Hai, he didn’t look even a bit surprised. He looked at Zhao Hai, then he sighed and said, “I expected this day to come, but I didn’t expect it to come this early. I’ll pass it to the Patriarch, he also thought about this. But Little Hai, I hope that you can remember that you are from the Bone Symbol Camp and Margaret is also from the Ashley Family. If the Ashley Family is in trouble, please lend us a hand.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “There’s no need to worry about it, Camp Lord. Margaret is the Ahsley Family’s princess, and I’m also someone from the family. Even if I go independent with Xiong Li and the others, how could I forget the Ashley Family? Rest assured.”

Desbarres nodded, then he said, “It’s a good thing to go independent. But there are a lot of things that needed to be taken care of. First of all, you will need a base. Do you need my help to find you one?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s fine Camp Lord, I’ve already found a place. I’ll take a look at it when the time comes.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Desbarres nodded and said, “That’s good. You just came back today, I’m afraid there would be a lot of people who would want to see you. How about this, let’s have a party tonight so that you can meet everyone. Let those people know that you’re not an impostor. Those people from the Cultivation Realm would never think that you would kill so many of them.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, I’ll leave everything to you. I’ll take a short rest first.”

Seeing Zhao Hai’s smile, Desbarres and Luke couldn’t help but smile slightly as they gave Margaret a glance. Then they stood up as Desbarres said, “Alright, then take a rest. We’ll be heading out to prepare. I’ll call you later.” Then the two turned around and left.

Margaret looked at Desbarres and Luke’s smiles and knew that the two had misunderstood. When the two left, Margaret hit Zhao Hai as she said, “Brother Hai, why did you say it like that? Look at their smiles, I’m embarrassed.”

Zhao Hai just laughed and said, “This is to erase any suspicions that Camp Lord might have. We haven’t seen each other for a long time, so we should be longing to be with each other.”

Naturally, Margaret wasn’t convinced with this. But since he can’t do anything about it, Zhao Hai laughed once more then he said, “Alright, please prepare some tea. Team Leader Ma is here.”

When Margaret heard Zhao Hai, she immediately complied and prepared some tea. Margaret knew how much Zhao Hai respects Ma Rulong.

Sure enough, just as Margaret stood up, a knock was heard on the door. Then a robot’s voice came in, “Mister Zhao Hai, Mister Ma Rulong is looking for you.”

Zhao Hai stood up and walked to the door before opening it. A robot stood outside the door with Ma Rulong standing beside it.

When Zhao Hai saw Ma Rulong, he immediately smiled and said, “Team Leader, come in, come in.” Ma Rulong nodded and then entered the room.

As soon as he entered the room, Ma Rulong quickly noticed Margaret. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Team Leader, this is my wife Margaret. Margaret, this is team leader Ma. He took good care of me back in the Cultivation Realm..”

Margaret immediately gave Ma Rulong a salute, “Margaret has seen Team Leader Ma. Thank you for taking care of Zhao Hai.” Ma Rulong politely returned the salute. Then Zhao Hai asked him to sit down.

After Ma Rulong had sat down, Margaret immediately offered him a cup of tea. Ma Rulong expressed his gratitude before taking a sip of tea. But it was clear that his thoughts weren’t on the tea. He just took a sip as a formality.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Can I ask why Team Leader Ma is looking for me?”

Ma Rulong took a glance at Margaret. When he saw this, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Team Leader, Margaret is my wife, she knows everything about me.”

Ma Rulong nodded, then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I just heard someone say that you haven’t been attacked by the people from the Cultivation Realm and the Devil realm? Is this true?”

Zhao Hai replied, “I did say those things. But Team Leader, you should know about the situation at that time. Do you really believe that what I said is the truth?”

When Ma Rulong heard Zhao Hai, he paused for a moment then he laughed. After some time, he stopped. Then he looked at Zhao Hai and whispered, “How many?”

Zhao Hai chuckled and said, “I didn’t count them, but there should be less than 200. In any case, Fu Yishan and Zhongli Qiang are gone. And none of them were able to run away.”

Ma Rulong nodded and said, “Don’t tell this to anyone. You already told everyone that nobody attacked you, so nobody attacked you. Even if they come up with some reason, as long as you don’t admit it, they can’t do anything. Does anyone else know?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Camp Lord Desbarres knows about it. But rest assured, nobody else will find out. Right, Team Leader, the Six Realms Battlefield, how is it?”

Ma Rulong smiled and said, “Rest assured, I’ll take care of it. There’s no need for you to worry. When the time comes, I’ll inform you.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Then I’ll wait for you. Right, Team Leader, we’re going to hold a party tonight. You should participate, call everyone else as well.” Naturally, by everyone else, Zhao Hai meant the other team leaders. Although these people were also called team leaders, all of them were led by Ma Rulong.

Ma Rulong nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll call them. But just to let you know, before you returned, those fellows haven’t been living great lives. They don’t dare go alone and instead they just waited for you to return. To be honest, those guys have gotten through a lot. The protests are extremely bothersome.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Then this only means we need to celebrate. Right, Team Leader, what prize did I win? Shouldn’t I get some?”

Ma Rulong laughed and said, “Rest assured, you will get them. If there’s anything lacking, then people will protest once more. Just wait a few days and they will be sent to you.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I don’t know what I won, but Team Leader, just know that I only accept good things.”

Ma Rulong laughed once more, “Don’t worry, everything will be good. Alright, I’ll head back and call everyone over.” Then he stood up. Zhao Hai also stood up and led Ma Rulong to the door.

After sending Ma Rulong off, Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, what prizes do you think they would send? It would be best if they send things that the Space doesn’t have.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “After all my efforts, giving me materials for a prize is too little. Although the Space has a lot of good things, how much of it is really useful right now? Also, it would be harder to upgrade the Space in the future. We would still need to collect more valuable things for the Space. It’ll be best for us if they let me choose other kinds of rewards.”

Margaret smiled and said, “That’s true. You have given a great contribution this time. Nobody from the Machine Field has given a greater contribution in the past hundred years. Brother Hai, if you can choose, what kind of reward do you want?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It really depends on what they decide on. But If I were to choose, maybe I’ll want a planet that nobody wants. We can build a base there and have the island be our secret base. What do you think?”

Margaret nodded and said, “That is also good. Otherwise, we could only establish a base in the Rainbow Meteorite Field. And that place is too boring.”

Zhao Hai knitted his brows and said, “Does the Machine Field really have planets that nobody wants? How is that possible? If a planet is somewhat useful, then shouldn’t they be taken by the families?”

Margaret stared at Zhao Hai and said, “Who says there are no vacant planets in the Machine Field? Not only do these planets exist, but there are a lot of them.”

Chapter 1276: Turning on Each Other

Zhao Hai became interested, so he asked, “Is that true? Tell me more.”

Margaret smiled and said, “Brother Hai, let me ask you. If you’re given land, would you prefer one that not only can be farmed, but also has minerals to mine, or something that is basically a desert?”

Zhao Hai immediately replied, “So you mean nobody bothered to claim those bad planets? It isn’t because they are uninhabitable?”

Margaret nodded, “Correct. Most of the unclaimed planets are actually habitable. However, only those with strong bodies could survive in them. The environment is too bad that improving it for normal habitation is too expensive. Therefore, nobody wanted them. Everyone would rather squeeze into a good planet than relocate to one with a bad environment.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he could understand. Although the Machine Field Planet was just one of the habitable planets, its population wasn’t any less than Earth. This meant that people preferred to live in good environments. Compared to Machine Field Planet, other planets with worse environments weren’t as crowded.

Margaret looked at Zhao Hai and said, “There’s another thing about those planets that people don’t want. It’s the location. It isn’t good. Generally, these planets are located at the edge of the Machine Field. There are no main lines of communication towards those planets and products would take a long time to be transported there. It can be said that those places are wastelands. But that isn’t a problem for us. We have the Space and we can also change the environment bit by bit. We can claim those planets as our territories, we can even make the people inside the Space live in them.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Those planets will be very useful to us. However, it would be too eye-catching if we populate them with the people directly from the Space. We should think about other ways to move people from other places. We don’t have to worry about the population for the time being, we can take care of it slowly. If I’m able to receive a planet as a reward, then I’ll have to hand its management over to you since I’ll be heading to the Six Realms Battlefield. I’m afraid I won’t have the time to manage it.”

Margaret nodded, “I’ll discuss this with Sister Laura and the others. You don’t need to worry about this.”

Zhao hai nodded, “Talk to Grandma Merine about this as well. Our situation in the Black Wasteland is the same as this. We managed to change the environment there bit by bit. I’m sure we can do it again in the Machine Field.”

Margaret laughed softly, she couldn’t help but love Zhao Hai more. She was aware of what Zhao Hai went through. To be honest, Margaret couldn’t imagine how Zhao Hai was able to get to his current status.

Although she saw the magical abilities of the Space, Laura and the others told her that it was because the Space has undergone multiple level ups.

Zhao Hai and Margaret chatted for a while before Desbarres sent someone to tell them that the party was about to begin. Zhao Hai immediately got up and went to the party’s location.

Since a lot of people were invited to the party, the event could only happen outside. All sorts of people attended the party. Those who watched the competition in the Void Arena were also present. Since they were already acquainted with Zhao Hai, they naturally came over to greet him. Zhao Hai also greeted them one by one.

There were also some people from External Halls, but they weren’t able to get close to Zhao Hai. This was because surrounding him were the Core Juniors of Great Families. Even if these people from External Halls forced themselves in, they still wouldn’t be able to get through.

Everyone knows that Zhao Hai’s status could only go up at this point. Moreover, it’s clear that the Ashley Family wouldn’t be able to keep him. Everyone knew about his relationship with Margaret but they don’t believe that Zhao Hai would stay because of her. Now, Zhao Hai has prestige, reputation, and money. What he needed right now was contacts and connections.

People become someone’s subordinate because they wanted a comfortable life, but this doesn’t mean that everyone was willing to be subservient to another person. Zhao Hai had great strength, skills, and was now building up his connections. Adding all of these things up, it was only a matter of time before Zhao Hai became an unstoppable force in the realm. Therefore, it was much better to establish a relationship with him now than in the future.

And those people who establish a connection with Zhao Hai would also benefit from him. It can be said that this relationship would bring mutual benefit.

After receiving toasts from people in Machine Field Planet for five days, Zhao Hai took Margaret back to Dark Demon Planet. Now that everyone knew that Zhao Hai can use space magic, there was no need to hide his ability. So he just took Margaret with him and went straight to the planet.

Although Zhao Hai has returned to the Machine Field, he was still paying attention to the situation in the Cultivation Realm. After all, he killed a lot of Cultivators and Devil Practitioners. At this time, the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm were stuck on how to deal with him. If Zhao Hai’s wasn’t careful, then he might give them a reason to make a move.

Both the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm weren’t good to provoke. And this time, he made a huge wave that might attract the Great Sects. They would pay close attention to Zhao Hai. And if allowed, they would strike with speed that’s as fast as lightning. Zhao Hai needed to prevent them from doing so.

The Cultivation Realm’s reaction was within Zhao Hai’s expectations. His arrival in Machine Field Planet was immediately known by the Cultivation Realm. Upon receiving this news, the people from the Cultivation Realm paused for a moment. Then they immediately appointed more manpower to send to the Void Arena.

Naturally, they weren’t able to find anything. All traces had been cleared up by Zhao Hai. More than 100 people disappeared into thin air.

Additionally, Zhao Hai threw smoke into the situation by saying that he wasn’t attacked. Nobody could believe Zhao Hai’s words. But in the end, they remembered that a lot of people remained in order to deal with him. Nascent Soul Experts wouldn’t be able to survive under the assault of so many people. Even Immortals wouldn’t be able to return unscathed.

But now that Zhao Hai returned to the Machine Field in such a relaxed manner, the Cultivators couldn’t help but believe that he wasn’t attacked. But if this was the case, what happened to all those Cultivators and Devil Practitioners? Did they just vanish?

The Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm’s investigation intensified. They scoured the entire Void Arena but they were unable to find anything. The more than 100 experts that wanted to deal with Zhao Hai seemed to have vanished into thin air. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai was safe and sound back in the Machine Field.

This matter got more and more noisy in the Cultivation Realm. Originally, the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm made a temporary alliance in order to deal with Zhao Hai. But now that the more than 100 experts had disappeared, the people from the Devil Realm began accusing the Cultivators of killing their experts and then hiding the perpetrators.

At the same time, the people from the Cultivation Realm accused the Devil Realm of killing their experts. The two sides began blaming each other.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect this situation to happen. He expected the two realms to immediately plot against him. Who thought that the two would instead turn on each other.

When he saw the situation develop into this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but shake his head as he smiled bitterly. It seems like the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm couldn never have any amicable relationship. He was worried over nothing.

Seeing the Cultivation Realm being restless, Zhao Hai felt relieved. After he and Margaret returned to Dark Demon Planet, they immediately met Cadjo and then the Patriarch.

Thunder didn’t say anything. He wasn’t too enthusiastic in meeting Zhao Hai nor was he indifferent towards him. This was a bit unexpected for Zhao Hai, but he didn’t mind it. To be honest, he doesn’t have much of a relationship with Thunder Ashley. He doesn’t owe Thunder anything. On the contrary, he helped the Ashley Family rise up, so it was the Ashley Family who owes him.

However, no matter what, Margaret was Thunder’s daughter. Because of this, Zhao Hai was polite towards the Patriarch. Although the two weren’t amicable, their relationship wasn’t bad.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai’s relationship with Cadjo was very good. The two were very close. When Cadjo saw that Zhao Hai was back, he was naturally glad.

After meeting with Cadjo, Zhao Hai and Margaret returned to the Bone Symbol Camp. It must be said that inside the Ashley Family, Zhao Hai was familiar with the Bone Symbol Camp the most. As soon as Zhao Hai and Margaret returned to the Bone Symbol Camp, the entire camp erupted in celebration. Everyone immediately went out to greet them.

Although Desbarres was still the Camp Lord, the Bone Symbol Camp’s management has been turned over to Tie Shen and Tao Wang. Needless to say, Zhao Hai’s relationship with the two was very good.

Due to Zhao Hai’s exploits, the Bone Symbol Camp was very proud of him. And because of his relationship with the camp, there’s nobody in the Machine Field that doesn’t know about Ashley Family’s Bone Symbol Camp. Once people from the camp go on a mission, other people would immediately be polite to them.

Everyone from the Bone Symbol Camp certainly knew that everything they enjoyed right now was because of Zhao Hai. Now that Zhao Hai was back, they were naturally happy. Tie Sheng immediately gathered everyone to the cafeteria. Food was also being prepared.

Zhao Hai was also met with a surprise in the camp. Barlett and the others were here. After they graduated from the Ascender Academy, they officially joined the Bone Symbol Camp. But since the time they joined wasn’t that long, when they heard about Zhao Hai’s situation, they couldn’t help but be surprised.

Zhao Hai was also very happy seeing them. He exchanged a few words with the group, much to the envy of everyone else in the camp.

Chapter 1277: Take Us With You

Zhao Hai can be regarded as someone returning to his hometown with great achievements. Naturally, this requires a celebration. Just as Tie Sheng was preparing the food and drinks in the cafeteria, the other Camp Lords also arrived. It doesn’t matter if these people had some problems with the Bone Symbol Camp before, all of that has vanished. Zhao Hai was now the hero of the entire Machine Field and the biggest contributor to the Ashley Family. It’s stupid to not form any good relations with him at this time.

Zhao Hai was also very polite to the Camp Lords. Even Diya, the Camp Lord of the Ghost Symbol Camp who had a bad relationship with the Bone Symbol Camp before was greeted the same way. Zhao Hai gave them a proper greeting without showing any arrogance.

The celebration was naturally jovial. When evening arrived, Zhao Hai and Margaret returned to their villa and then they immediately entered the Space to sleep. Noon of the next day arrived and after eating his meal, Zhao Hai left Margaret inside the Space as he went out and had a robot lead Barlett and the others over. He wanted to chat with them.

Before long, Barlett and the others arrived. They have known Zhao Hai for about a year now, they knew him even before Zhao Hai knew Margaret. But since Zhao Hai left a month after he Ascended and they needed to finish their education, it has been a long time since they had last seen each other.

Zhao Hai gave them magic staffs and he even made the Bone Symbol Camp take care of them. They were very grateful for this. So when they entered the Bone Symbol Camp, they wanted to meet Zhao Hai to thank him. However, Zhao Hai was already attending the competition. Moreover, it seems like he became the Machine Field’s Hero. This caused them to be a bit dizzy. This development was too fast, they didn’t expect it.

Now that Zhao Hai was looking for them, it’s natural for Barlett and the others to comply quickly. They knew Zhao Hai’s position in the Machine Field. There were innumerable people who wanted to flatter him but were unable to. In this case, they wouldn’t dare to neglect his invitation.

Although they were wizened people and had powerful status in the lower realms, coming to the Machine Field made then understand a lot of things. In the past year, they didn’t only adapt to the spiritual qi of the Machine Field, they were also able to somewhat stabilize their mentality.

Barlett and the others were Zhao Hai’s friends. But even if Zhao Hai put on airs in front of them, they still had to accept it.

Under the robot’s lead, Barlett and the others entered Zhao Hai’s room. They didn’t see Margaret inside but they didn’t say anything. Zhao Hai quickly welcomed them. When the group gave him a salute, Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Come in quick, take a seat. I wasn’t able to talk properly with you yesterday since there’s a lot of people. So I called you over today for a chat.”

When Barlett and the others saw that Zhao Hai was so enthusiastic in meeting them, they couldn’t help but be moved. Zhao Hai doesn’t need to care about people like them, now with his stellar reputation. However, Zhao Hai chose to be warm to them. They saw how Camp Lords were very cordial towards him yesterday. These Camp Lords were even speaking respectfully towards Zhao Hai, this showed how high Zhao Hai’s current status was.

Zhao Hai talked with them yesterday for a while, and even then he showed great enthusiasm. Barlett and the others thought that Zhao Hai was polite to them yesterday for the sake of his reputation. Zhao Hai was now a legendary figure in the Machine Field. Because of this, his history was uncovered by people. Therefore, people were aware that he had relationships with a few people back in the Ascender Academy. If Zhao Hai didn’t say hello to them yesterday, then other people would think that Zhao Hai was an ingrate. This would heavily damage his reputation.

But today was a private meeting. There was no need for Zhao Hai to be cordial since nobody was looking at them. Moreover, nobody would listen to Barlett and the others if they complained. Because of this, when they were invited over by Zhao Hai, they already acted extremely respectful.

However, they didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be very polite. When they heard Zhao Hai, their hearts immediately filled up with happiness. It seems like Zhao Hai was indeed a true friend.

The group entered the living room and sat down. Then the robot began serving them tea. Zhao Hai looked at Barlett and the others, then he smiled and said, “How are you? Is the camp treating you well?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Barlett smiled and said, “Thanks to you, the Bone Symbol Camp has been treating us well. Although we’re given tasks, they weren’t very dangerous. We’re having a good time here.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That’s great. There’s no need to be very polite with me. You can keep calling me Little Hai like before. I got some food and wine prepared, let’s eat.” Then everyone went to the dining area to eat. The robot had already prepared them some food and wine.

After inviting everyone to have a seat, Zhao Hai lifted his wine glass up and said, “Come, let’s drink. We haven’t seen each other for some time. We have a lot of catching up to do!” Barlett and the others were also very happy. So they raised their classes and drank with Zhao Hai.

Upon downing one glass, everyone began to loosen up as they chatted. Barlett and the others were naturally interested in the Cultivation Realm. So Zhao Hai retold his journey to them. The room’s atmosphere became warmer.

After drinking a few more glasses of wine and eating a few dishes, Zhao Hai suddenly said, “Everyone, I invited you in today because I have something to tell you.”

As soon as they heard Zhao Hai, Barlett and the others knew that it was time for proper business. The group immediately adjusted their seating position as they waited for Zhao Hai’s next words. Seeing everyone turn serious, Zhao Hai smiled faintly but he didn’t stop them. Then he continued, “Even if I just returned to the Machine Field, I will have to head out again to do a mission. And after I’m finished with this mission, I might be leaving the Ashley Family to go independent.”

Barlett and the others weren’t very surprised with Zhao Hai’s words. In fact, they had been hearing rumors flying around about this, especially in the Bone Symbol Camp. Everyone believed that Zhao Hai would go independent. Moreover, it seems like it would be soon.

Therefore, upon hearing Zhao Hai, Barlett and the others weren’t shocked. They just nodded. Seeing them nod, Zhao Hai added, “Me, Xiong Li, Lu Dingtian, Dongfang Yu, Li Kuangren, and Sun Fei are going to go on our own. And since I have gained a large merit this time, I will certainly be rewarded greatly. I want to use this opportunity to ask for a planet.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Barlett and the others were stunned. All of them looked at Zhao Hai in surprise. As soon as he saw their reaction, Zhao Hai immediately knew what they were thinking about. They didn’t know that there were still unclaimed habitable planets in the Machine Field. But upon explaining it to them, Barlet and the others understood that there were habitable planets that nobody wanted.

Barlett nodded and said, “This rumor has been circulating in the Bone Symbol Camp. Everyone knows that you will go independent. However, nobody thought that you would take a planet. Little Hai, let me just say, if you want to operate a planet, then you will have to make a huge investment.”

As soon as he heard this, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “This is not a problem, don’t worry about it. But if I want to go independent, then I would need people to help me. I wonder if you’re interested in coming?”

When they heard Zhao Hai, Barlett and the others were stunned. Then they looked at each other, visibly confused. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to invite them to come with him. It was truly unexpected.

Barlett and the others have been in the Bone Symbol Camp for some time. They had also understood their present situation. Aged Ascenders like them had no status in families. Barlett and the others were among the lucky ones since they were taken care of by the Bone Symbol Camp. They would be given easy tasks and money every year. This way, their lives wouldn’t be bad. However, that was it.

Other Aged Ascenders weren’t as lucky as Barlett and the others. They generally won’t be given missions so they don’t have any money. And if they were given tasks, the tasks they were given were dangerous. There was a high chance for them to fall in those tasks. Therefore, there weren’t a lot of aged ascenders left in the External Halls.

Zhao Hai looked at their expressions, then he smiled faintly and said, “I might go out to do a mission soon, but I’m sure that I would get the reward before then. I believe it shouldn’t be a problem for me to ask for a planet that nobody wants. However, transforming that planet would be a top priority. Although I asked Margaret to take care of this matter, she’s still young after all. There will be a lot of things that she wouldn’t be able to deal with. So I thought of you. Don’t worry, money, materials, and other resources will not be a problem. So what do you think?”

Barlett paused for a moment and then said, “Alright, I agree. In any case, we wouldn’t be able to progress far in the Bone Symbol Camp. We might as well help you. What do you all think?”

The others agreed as well. People like them used to hold high status in the lower realms. But in the Machine Field, they were demoted to useless old men. It would take a long time for them to fully adapt to this situation.

Originally, they were dejected with their current state. They thought that they would rot and die in the Bone Symbol Camp. But now, Zhao Hai came to invite them for exciting work.

Seeing them agree, Zhao Hai immediately lifted his wine glass and said, “Alright, then when I get the planet, I’ll depend on you to take care of it.” Barlett and the others lifted their wine glasses up as well and gave Zhao Hai a toast. Then everyone downed their wine. But this time, the old men felt that the fire they had in their youths was reignited.

Chapter 1278: The Brothers Get Together

Zhao Hai returned to the Space after sending Barlett and the others off. Laura and the others were currently on their computers. They were looking for appropriate planets to choose. As it turns out, these unwanted planets were put up for sale at fairly low prices. However, no one bought them. Operating such planets would need high investments. And even if great efforts were made, the planets could only produce fruits and plant products. There weren’t many profits to them at all. Unless made for human habitation, there was no point to developing these planets.

In this case, why would anyone buy them? In the eyes of the families, they might as well use the money to make more battleships. The more battleships you have, the more power you can use, and the more benefits you can fight for.

Because of this, Zhao Hai was assured that nobody would complain if he were to take one of these planets for himself. They might even be happy if he were to take them all off of their hands.

When Laura and the others saw that Zhao Hai had arrived, they immediately waved towards him to come over. Zhao Hai walked over in front of a large screen. Displayed on the screen was a star map of the entire Machine Field. Most planets and meteorites were shown with white dots. These white dots were the uninhabitable planets. There were also meteorites and planets that were red, which indicated that people were living in them. And then there were more than 300 meteorites and planets that were green, these were the planets that nobody wanted.[1]

As he scanned the star map, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get stunned. He said, “The Machine Field has so many unclaimed habitable planets? I didn’t expect that.”

However, Zhao Hai also noticed that these planets were on the edge of the Machine Field – on the side far from the Cultivation Realm. Looking at this setup, Zhao Hai had a realization. Since these planets were in the outskirts of the Machine Field, and even far from the Cultivation Realm, it was natural that the Machine Field wouldn’t expand towards them. If these planets were close to the Cultivation Realm, then even if their environments weren’t good, people would still fight madly for them. This was because these planets could be used as stopover stations for supplies and commodities going to and from the Cultivation Realm.

Zhao Hai sat on the sofa as he turned his head to Laura and said, “Have you settled on which planet to choose?”

Laura smiled and then she pointed towards the large screen. A red circle appeared on the screen, a planet in the middle of it.

This place was very far from the center of the Machine Field. It was also near to a meteorite belt. And in the vicinity of the planet were six white colored dots. It seems like these were the planet’s moons.

The screen quickly changed its image, allowing Zhao Hai to have a careful look on the planet. From the star map, this planet was called Yalei 2. It was separated from the Machine Field by the meteorite belt. This meteorite belt wasn’t very dangerous, but it still blocked large-scale ships from passing through it. The planet had six moons, named Ave 1 to 6. It was clear that this planet wasn’t very popular judging by how simple its name was.

Then on the side of the screen was an introduction to Yalei 2. This planet can only be defined as a waste planet. The planet’s ratio between land to water was four to six. Land accounts for 4 while the oceans account for 6.

It must be said that the land of Yalei 2 was very huge. But because it was quite distant from any stars, the temperature of the planet was lower than normal. In the planet’s land, besides moss, there were extremely few plants that grew. Moreover, the planet’s seawater was too salty, completely incapable of nurturing life. Therefore, the planet’s entire ocean was like the Dead Sea. A person could float on its surface without even moving.

The Machine Field appraised Yalei 2 as a planet that’s not suitable for human housing. Only people with strong physique could survive in this place. But even if someone wanted to invest in developing this planet, doing so would be close to impossible because the planet couldn’t be reached with large-sized ships. Therefore, nobody wanted the planet. Its price was also astonishingly low. One could buy the planet for as low as seven million machine coins. In the Machine Field, seven million machine coins amounted to a single small battleship. It can be said that the planet was priced the same as a small ship.

But even though it was dirt cheap, nobody bought it. In their minds, at least a small ship had some uses compared to the waste planet.

However, Zhao Hai understood Laura’s intention upon seeing the planet. Yalei 2 was indeed suitable for him. First of all, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about the planet’s environment. There were plenty of plants in the Space that could emit heat. Once they’re planted on the planet, it wouldn’t be long before the planet’s temperature rose. And as long as the temperature rises, icebergs frozen for thousands of years would melt, diluting the ocean water. This will reduce the water’s salt content, allowing for animals to live in it.

Although Yalei 2 was far from a star, this doesn’t mean that it doesn’t receive light. Plants could still perform photosynthesis with the amount of light hitting the planet. And the increasing temperature would only benefit plants on the planet. When the time comes, Yalei 2 will be greatly improved.

As for the six planets outside Yalei 2, bases could be constructed there, providing the planet with a net of security. Additionally, the meteorite belt that was close to the planet could become a shield for the planet.

Zhao Hai understood that he would pay a high price in order to transform Yalei 2. However, he didn’t really intend to use it as a base. Actually, all of this investment was for the Ashley Family.

Even before they met Zhao Hai, the Cultivation Realm and the Devil Realm were already coveting the Machine Field. If the two worked together, then the Machine Field would be hard-pressed to win. Margaret already asked Zhao Hai to help the Ashley Family when such times arrive. And since Zhao Hai can’t send them to the Space, then he could only send them to Yalei 2.

Zhao Hai was very satisfied with the planet, he nodded and said, “Good, let’s take this planet. Even if we can’t request for it, we’ll buy it. However, we need to set up a transmission formation on the planet. Although it’s just for cover, it might be useful in the future.”

Laura nodded. Then Zhao Hai had Meg invite Merine and Green over to discuss how to transform Yalei 2 Planet.

Green and Merine’s current state was very good. They have started to practice cultivation methods and it has brought great results. Although their combat strength didn’t increase by much, it was already good that their lifespan increased. And the longer they live, the more they can cultivate.

At this time, the two were either studying magic formations or doing something with the Hundred Spirit Tree. They also grow a few plants on the side to entertain themselves. They were living quite leisurely.

The two already understood that Zhao Hai was powerful enough that nobody can move him anymore. Therefore, they no longer have any worries.

Zhao Hai told the two elders about the outside situation and the two immediately agreed. But now, they no longer needed to direct it outside. They can now do it from the Space. The grunt work would be taken care of by the Undead.

After arranging these things, Zhao Hai had nothing else left to do other than releasing silver needles and have Cai’er control it towards Yalei 2.

Zhao Hai brought Margaret to stroll around the Bone Symbol Camp or Dark Demon Planet once in a while. However, they spent most of their days being busy. There’s just a lot of people who want to see them.

Besides his hectic schedule, Zhao Hai was also waiting for news about his reward. And the Machine Field didn’t make him wait too long. Ten days after Zhao Hai returned to Dark Demon Planet, Cadjo came to inform him to go to Machine Field Planet to receive his reward.

Zhao Hai took Margaret with him to Machine Field Planet. But just as they arrived at the Ashley Family’s office building, Zhao Hai was surprised to see Xiong Li and the others there. It seems like they had already gone out of seclusion.

When Xiong Li and the others came out of their seclusion, then immediately went to Machine Field Planet. And upon knowing that Zhao Hai had returned, they came looking for him.

Zhao Hai immediately welcomed his brothers to his room. Then he scanned through Xiong Li and the others before he nodded and said, “Good, all of you became stronger. Hehe. It seems like you’ve gained a lot during your seclusion.”

Xiong Li laughed and said, “Kid, you’re the one who’s strong. You’re making us lose face. But we did become stronger. I’m now more confident in going to the Six Realms Battlefield.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Why are you thinking about the Six Realms Battlefield when it hasn’t been decided yet? You’re worrying too early.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Dongfang Yu couldn’t help but frown as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, don’t you know? Team Leader Ma notified us that we have five days to prepare after receiving the reward. After that, we will enter the Six Realms Battlefield.”

Zhao Hai was shocked, he didn’t receive this news. Zhao Hai looked at his brothers and said, “When did Team Leader Ma tell you this? Why am I not informed?”

Dongfang Yu replied, “He informed us when we came out. But since you haven’t closed up, I believe Team Leader Ma planned to tell you when you arrive here.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “That’s possible. Right, I have some good news. I found our base. Come and take a look.” Then he took out his computer.

Zhao Hai turned his computer on and then opened the star map. After that, he pointed towards Yalei 2 and said, “This is Yalei 2. This is where I plan to have our base constructed.”

Xiong Li and the others immediately checked the information regarding the planet. But as they read through the material, they couldn’t help but get terrified. It can be said that Yalei 2 was truly a bad planet.

After reading the information, Xiong Li looked at Zhao Hai in confusion as he asked, “Little Hai, is this a joke? What are we going to do on that planet? Didn’t you read the information? That planet is not a place for human habitation.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s fine. I already thought about what to do with it. As long as we take care of this planet, it’ll be ours in the future. I already asked Margaret for help along with other people. They will transform this planet once we head to the Six Realms Battlefield. It should be a different place once we return.”

These words didn’t change what Xiong Li and the other felt. This was because the information on the computer about Yalei 2 was just too bad. In their minds, it would still be a trash planet after its transformation.

Seeing their expression staying the same, Zhao Hai lowered his voice and said, “Actually, Yalei 2 is just a cover. Our real base wouldn’t be there. Come, let me show you.”

As soon as they heard Zhao Hai, the group immediately gathered. They knew that Zhao Hai was about to use space magic. Seeing that everyone had gathered, Zhao Hai smiled, then with an intention white light covered the group. The next moment, the group appeared on an island in the Endless Desert.

When the white light vanished, Xiong Li and the others began to look around them. Upon sensing the environment, they couldn’t help but be dumbfounded. This island was very good. It was much better compared to other places that Xiong Li and the others had been to.

Moreover, since Xiong Li and the others had experienced the environment of the Cultivation Realm, they knew that the spiritual density on the island was on par with the Cultivation Realm. This caused them to be startled.

While Xiong Li and the others were curiously looking around, Zhao Hai said, “Brothers, I need to tell you this in advance. You can only do your activities within the island. You must not go beyond the outside shield. Otherwise, even gods wouldn’t be able to save you.”

Xiong Li and the others turned to look at the horizon and saw that there was a bright yellow shield surrounding the island. Seeing this, Xiong Li couldn’t help but ask, “Little Hai, how did you find this place? What’s outside the shield?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Brothers, try to guess.” The group shook their heads. The Machine Field was too large and they had only been here for a few years. Moreover, the island’s environment was too special. They don’t even know where to start guessing.

Seeing their response, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s a famous place. However, people only know about what’s outside the island. Actually, nobody knows about this place.”

The brothers got more curious upon hearing Zhao Hai. Seeing his brothers staring at him, Zhao Hai stopped making them guess as he said, “Outside this island is the Endless Desert. The place we’re in now is the center of the desert.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others were startled. Then they looked at each other, visibly shocked. Xiong Li turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, is the Endless Desert you’re talking about the same desert that is a forbidden area in the Machine Field? The place that produces Ancient Eternal Sand? That desert?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Where else could you see a vast desert in the World of Cultivation? We’re at the center of it.”

Li Kuangren exclaimed, “Impossible. If we really are at the center of the Endless Desert, then how did you find this place?”

But Zhao Hai just smiled, “You don’t have to worry about how I found out about this place. So how is it? Are you satisfied with our base?”

I was wondering if ‘meteorites’ were supposed to be ‘moons’. But

Chapter 1279: Rewards

Satisfied, of course they’re satisfied. They were beyond satisfied!

If Xiong Li and the others were unsatisfied with the island, then there’s no place in the world that would satisfy them. As soon as they heard Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others laughed then they flew around to examine the island.

Zhao Hai saw their actions and didn’t mind it. The island’s vitality has already been improved. Zhao Hai raised some fishes and prawns in the island’s waters. Naturally, these fishes weren’t for consumption, they were for viewing.

Before long, Xiong Li and the others returned to Zhao Hai’s side. They had already examined the entire island. They couldn’t believe how beautiful the island was. They were all happy.

Seeing his brothers smiling, Zhao Hai smiled as well as he said, “Alright, let’s head back. It wouldn’t be good if we disappeared for a long time.” Then with a wave of his hand, the group returned to his room in the Machine Field Planet.

Even after sitting down, Xiong Li and the others couldn’t hide the excitement on their faces. Xiong Li muttered, “I didn’t expect something so beautiful to exist. Moreover, it’s our base! I couldn’t help but smile when I think about it.”

Dongfang Yu and the others nodded. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s good that you like it. However, we still need to take care of Yalei 2. You shouldn’t underestimate that planet. Pay attention to the planet’s location and you’ll understand why I chose it.”

As soon as they heard this, Xiong Li and the others immediately opened their computers and pulled up the star map. Almost immediately, they understood what Zhao Hai meant.

When they settled down once more, Dongfang Yu said, “I failed to see Yalei 2’s surroundings before. As long as we develop the planet, it would certainly become a very good base.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I’ve recruited some people to help Margaret in transforming Yalei 2. I believe we can see a different Yalei 2 upon returning from the Six Realms Battlefield.”

Dongfang Yu and the others were glad. After all, it was also their base. They could not see a situation where they couldn’t get the planet. They saw Yalei 2’s situation and to be honest, it was too easy to get the planet given their contribution. The Machine Field might even feel that they were giving an unfair reward.

As the group were discussing Yalei 2, a robot’s voice was heard outside, “Mister Zhao Hai, Mister Ma Rulong is here to see you.”

Zhao Hai quickly said, “Invite him in immediately.” Then the robot opened the door and led Ma Rulong inside the room.

Seeing Xiong Li and the others inside, Ma Rulong smiled and said, “It seems like you’re already aware that you will be going to the Six Realms Battlefield five days after receiving your reward. Do you need help preparing?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I have nothing else to prepare. But Team Leader, can I ask what our rewards are?”

Ma Rulong smiled and said, “Actually, it’s nothing to ponder much about. Everyone in the Machine Field knows that we have a Realm Arsenal. Inside this arsenal are weapons of the Machine Field. Your reward is choosing items inside this arsenal. Little Hai can choose ten while Xiong Li and the others can choose three. Naturally, this isn’t all. All of you will also receive 10 million machine coins each. Also, you’ll get a thousandth of the income from the mines and ore planets.”

Zhao Hai and the others stared. This didn’t mean that they thought that the reward was small. On the contrary it was too high. The other things were good, but the best one was the one thousandth income from the mines and ore planets.

The Machine Field obtained a lot of valuable mines and ore planets. The resources mined on these places would all be sent to the Machine Field. The mined minerals would be of great use to the realm. A thousandth of all of these minerals was a very remarkable amount. Rewarding them with such an amount was beyond Zhao Hai’s expectations.

Seeing Zhao Hai and the others’ expression, Ma Rulong smiled and said, “This matter has already been decided, it can no longer be changed so you can rest assured. Also, if it weren’t for you, the Machine Field wouldn’t have gotten its hands on those mines. Giving you this much is normal. The Machine Field has never been stingy in rewarding people with great contributions. Right, do you have any requests? If there’s anything you want, just tell me and I’ll see what I can do. As long as it isn’t an excessive request, of course.”

When Zhao Hai heard Ma Rulong, he smiled and said, “Team Leader, I have a request.”

Zhao Hai’s words caused Ma Rulong to be interested. He knew that Zhao Hai rarely asked for anything. Now that Zhao Hai has made a request, Ma Rulong was surprised. He immediately said, “Alright, tell me.”

Zhao Hai replied, “Team Leader, we brothers plan to go independent after going to the Six Realms Battlefield. Because of this, we want to set up a base on a planet.”

Ma Rulong replied, “You want a planet? You really want a planet? That’s…”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Team Leader, the planet we want isn’t that extraordinary. In fact, the Machine Field put it up for sale. It’s called Yalei 2.”

Ma Rulong raised his brows and asked, “Yalei 2? Where is that? Why haven’t I heard of it?”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but roll his eyes. Then he gestured to the computer and said, “Team Leader, you can go take a look.” Ma Rulong nodded and immediately opened the computer. He pulled out the star map and found Yalei 2.

Upon reading the information regarding Yalei 2, Ma Rulong turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, this is the place you want? Even birds won’t defecate here.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I also want something good, but I reckon nobody would agree. Yalei 2 is still acceptable. If I have it, then I can use it to raise crabs.”

“Crab?” Ma Rulong quickly responded, “Are those the huge crabs we ate? You can grow them in Yalei 2?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Team Leader, you can rest assured. It could support the crabs. The planet doesn’t even need to be transformed that much.”

Ma Rulong nodded and said, “Alright, this shouldn’t be a problem. It’s a planet that nobody wants. Those guys might even be happy to hand it over to you. Right, Little Hai, since I came over, how about treating this old man to some drinks?”

Zhao Hai laughed as he immediately led the group to the dining area before taking out food and wine.

Zhao Hai and the others waited in Machine Field Planet for two days before receiving their rewards. The Awarding ceremony was actually very troublesome. The first part was held in an assembly hall. Speeches came one after the other. After several hours of speeches, only then were the group taken to the Realm Arsenal.

The Realm Arsenal was very famous in the Machine Field. Unlike the secret treasuries of the families, the Realm Arsenal belonged to the public. Various Families would bring over weapons and other items every year in order to enrich this arsenal.

The existence of this arsenal serves two purposes. The first was to award prizes to those who made contributions to the Machine Field like Zhao Hai and the others. The second purpose was to use it as a huge logistics base. If the Machine Field goes to war with another realm, then the weapons and resources of this arsenal would be used to defend against the enemy. Only after this arsenal gets emptied would the Great Families open their own arsenals.

It might sound ridiculous, but this was what the Machine Field implemented. Moreover, Families were required to enrich it every year. Because of this, the arsenal has undergone numerous expansions.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t too hopeful about the arsenal. The Families certainly wouldn’t store valuable weapons and items here. They kept the good items for themselves.

And just like what Zhao Hai thought, he saw nothing great upon entering the arsenal. The weapons can only be described as above average. This caused Zhao Hai to be somewhat disappointed.

Fortunately, the arsenal doesn’t only have weapons. It also had plenty of ores and various resources. Seeing the unique ores inside, Zhao Hai talked to Xiong Li and the others and asked them to not choose a weapon and instead choose the ores. In turn, Zhao Hai would take care of their weapons for them.

Naturally, Xiong Li and the others agreed. They were more confident in Zhao Hai’s weapons than the weapons inside the arsenal. Additionally, they weren’t looking for Machine Field weapons at this moment. After all, they were now practicing the Cultivation Realm’s methods. In this case, the weapons they needed to use were weapons from the Cultivation Realm. So under Zhao Hai’s request, Xiong Li and the others chose different ores to take. Zhao Hai also took some ores for himself.

The choice made by Zhao Hai and the others caused other people to be confused. After all, the ores sent weren’t that valuable. And even if the ores were valuable, they still need a good weaponsmith to make them into weapons. Majority of people entering the arsenal wouldn’t choose ores.

However, since this was what Zhao Hai and the others chose, nobody said anything. At this time, Zhao Hai introduced more than 20 new ores to the Space. This meant that he would be able to make more weapons and with greater quality as well.

Besides entering the arsenal, Zhao Hai and the others were also rewarded with 10 million Machine Coins as well as the promised one thousandth of the income from the mines. To be honest, Zhao Hai didn’t really care much about these. Money was what Zhao Hai lacked the least.

As for Yalei 2, this matter proceeded smoothly. Nobody wanted it and its price was also very low. And since it was Zhao Hai’s group, the Machine Field’s higher-ups decided to just give it to them. Moreover, they weren’t only given Yalei 2, but the surrounding planets as well. In other words, Zhao Hai and the others would also rule the area surrounding Yalei 2.

Chapter 1280: Destination, Six Realms Battlefield

Zhao Hai was currently sitting inside a ship along with Xiong Li and the others. Ma Rulong was also with them. They had just left Machine Field Planet and were headed to a certain location. Other people were clueless about their destination. However, Zhao Hai and the others knew that they were going to the Six Realms Battlefield!

With a serious expression, Ma Rulong looked at Zhao Hai and the others and said, “Little Hai, you should all be very careful. The Six Realms Battlefield isn’t like any other place. All who go there are experienced experts. Nobody is easy to deal with. Don’t trust anyone besides those from the Machine Field. Although it’s only you six that are going, once you arrive there you will be sent to a 50-person team. Your Commander will be someone named Buddhist Warrior Yuan. He is originally a member of the Jingang Sect of the Cultivation Realm. However, he offended a powerful elder of his sect so was kicked out. Additionally, that elder posted a bounty on his head. He didn’t have a choice but to run to the Machine Field. In his stay here, he managed to contribute greatly to the realm. He is nicknamed the One-eyed Buddhist because he lost one eye when he was chased down by his Sect. He’s a strong expert and a friend of mine. I’ve asked him to take care of you.”[1]

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Thank you Team Leader. I also heard about the One-eyed Buddhist. He’s a famous character in the Machine Field. However, he seems to have disappeared. People thought that he’d been assassinated by someone. I didn’t expect him to be in the Six Realm Battlefield. And it looks like he’s been there for some time”

Ma Rulong nodded, “Correct. He’s been there for several years already. Although he’s only a Captain of a small team, nobody dared to underestimate him in the Six Realms Battlefield.”

Zhao Hai nodded. At this time Xiong Li said, “Team Leader, is Buddhist Warrior Yuan really that powerful?”

Ma Rulong nodded and said, “Of course he’s powerful. Yuan isn’t an Ascender. His mother and father were commoners on the planet where Jingang Sect is. He managed to learn a minor version of the sect’s cultivation method when he was young. Because of his talent and strength, he became suitable for the sect’s Cultivation Method. It didn’t take long for him to become an inner disciple of the sect.”

After speaking up to this point, Ma Rulong sighed. Then he looked at everyone and continued, “You should have seen the Cultivation Realm’s situation. And even if you haven’t seen it, you should have heard of it. When Yuan became an Inner Disciple of the Jingang Sect, the status of his parents naturally improved. They were admitted to the sect and were given a residence. However, there were some from the Jingang Sect who looked down on them and would spread some baseless humors once in a while. Fortunately, Yuan’s parents knew their place, so they endured.”

Zhao Hai and the others could almost guess what happened next, but they didn’t speak and just listened quietly. Ma Rulong went on, “One day, Yuan came home and heard that his mother had died. Yuan looked at his mother’s remains and saw that his mother was killed. He asked his father what happened. Initially unwilling to tell Yuan about what happened, his father finally relented and told Yuan everything. When Yuan’s mother went to fetch some water, she unintentionally spilled some of it on an Inner Disciple of the Jingang Sect. This Inner Disciple got angry and killed Yuan’s mother. And it was known that this Inner Disciple was a grandson of a sect elder.”

“Yuan was a very filial son, so how could he bear this injustice? But since he still had control over himself, he didn’t immediately look for revenge. Instead, he endured and waited for an opportunity. Finally, Yuan was given the chance to kill that person during a sect mission. Naturally, he wouldn’t declare that he killed the man. He just said that the man was killed while doing the mission.”

“However, the sect elder didn’t believe Yuan that easily. And after his circumstances were found out, Yuan ran away. His father was unable to escape and was burned alive by that elder. Then the elder began to offer a bounty for his capture. Yuan could no longer stay in the Cultivation Realm so he went to the other realms. But with his strength, it was difficult for Yuan to ensure his own safety. He was afraid that the other realms would capture him in order to gain favor with the Jingang Sect. In the end, Yuan ended up in the Machine Field. He gave the Machine Field his Cultivation Method in exchange for protection. The Machine Field’s higher-ups agreed and he stayed in the Machine Field since then.”

“Because of his hatred towards the Jingang Sect, he has always been merciless towards the people from the Cultivation Realm. But since he only learned a part of the Jingang Sect’s Cultivation Method, his control over magic artifacts wasn’t very good. However, this fellow is still very strong. In addition to cultivating the Jingang Sect’s method, he also placed great attention to his body. This caused his defense to be very formidable. After years of refining his body, Yuan became a human beast. This allowed him to get positive results in the Six Realms Battlefield.”

“I met him in the Six Realms Battlefield. At that time, I was one of his men. While on a mission, he was seriously injured while the rest of the team were killed. Only the two of us were left. I took him back with me as we were being hunted. I hid and hid until reinforcements arrived. After that, we became lifelong friends. But let me tell you this first, you should listen to him properly. That fellow’s temperament isn’t very good.”

Zhao Hai and the others nodded. Zhao Hai smiled at Ma Rulong and said, “Team Leader, rest assured. We’re honest and good-natured people. We will never cause any trouble.”

Ma Rulong snorted and said, “Kid, you had never been honest. But fortunately, your temperament is compatible with his. You’re kind to your allies and ruthless to your enemies, that fellow is the same.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Good man. Haha. Working with him will certainly be great.” Ma Rulong looked at Zhao Hai and couldn’t help but smile bitterly. He doesn’t know what to say.

The ship proceeded smoothly before stopping two days later. Much to Zhao Hai’s surprise, the ship’s location wasn’t that far away from Dark Demon Planet. There were many factions on this planet and it wasn’t any different to any other place in the Machine Field. This planet was called Apte.

Zhao Hai heard about Apte Planet before. To be honest, he just ignored it at that time. He didn’t expect the ship to stop at this place. And much to Zhao Hai’s surprise, the ship didn’t park outside the planet. Instead, it directly flew inside towards a fairly big island on the planet.

This island was the territory of a family on the planet. This family was the strongest influence in Atpe. This island along with other surrounding islands were under this family’s control. The ships coming and going from this place looked very normal, much like the civilian ship that Zhao Hai and the others were in. Because of this, the ship where Zhao Hai and the others were in didn’t look suspicious.

The ship entered a secret base upon reaching the island. After landing, Ma Rulong led Zhao Hai and the others out of the ship. It must be said that without the silver needles Zhao Hai wouldn’t have known that this was Apte Planet.

The group followed Ma Rulong out of the ship and soon discovered that they were in an underground cavern. This cavern had plenty of robots both active and inactive. They numbered approximately 1000.

Ma Rulong looked at these robots and then whispered, “Don’t underestimate these robots. Inside their bodies are small nuclear bombs. If all of these robots explode at the same time, then even Little Hai wouldn’t be able to escape. You’re guaranteed to die on the spot.”

As soon as they heard Ma Rulong, Zhao Hai and the others couldn’t help but be surprised. They didn’t expect these robots to be this deadly. If these robots explode at the same time, the damage they can inflict would certainly be dangerous. Zhao Hai was even certain that they could destroy the entire planet.

Ma Rulong didn’t mind the robots as he walked towards a cave. This cave was enormous. It had rocks and stalagmites everywhere that were arranged beautifully.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t in the mood to admire the sight. This was because he discovered that besides the robots, there were also a lot of Mages and Warriors protecting the place. There were about a hundred of them. All of them were hidden with some even hiding behind magic formations.

Upon seeing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but look at Ma Rulong. But Ma Rulong’s expression made Zhao Hai somewhat puzzled. It seems like Ma Rulong wasn’t aware of the existence of these people.

Before long, the group arrived at their destination. Then Ma Rulong looked at Zhao Hai and the others and said, “I can only accompany you up to here. Go on ahead. Someone will receive you on the other side.”

Zhao Hai and the others nodded as they stepped on the transmission formation. Ma Rulong looked at Zhao Hai and the others until a white light flashed. The next moment, Zhao Hai and the others were no longer in sight.”

Seeing the transmission formation empty, Ma Rulong sighed as he muttered, “Kid, you need to survive.”

….

There was a flash of light inside a huge metal room, then Zhao Hai and the others appeared inside it. Upon appearing, ZHao Hai and the others couldn’t help but stare. This was because this scene was very familiar. A giant room that was made entirely of metal, numerous magic formations on the walls, ceiling, and floor – Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel that time had flown backwards. It was like he ascended once more.

Jingang(金刚), known as Buddha’s Warrior Assistant.

Chapter 1281: Shocking Discovery

It wasn’t only Zhao Hai who felt this, the same was true with Xiong Li and the others. The place where they ascended looked almost the same as this. So upon seeing the metal room, they were also surprised.

After some time, Li Kuangren muttered and said, “What’s this? Did we ascend once more?”

Li Kuangren’s words caused Zhao Hai and the others to recover. Then they looked all around in confusion.

At this time, a door appeared on a wall before several Mages and Warriors appeared. Leading the group was an old Mage. When the Mage saw Zhao Hai and the others, he laughed and said, “Everyone, welcome to hell!” His laughter sounded like an insane grandmother’s laugh. It was chilling.

Zhao Hai and the others looked at each other as they didn’t understand what was going on. The Mage then said, “Come with me.” Then he turned around and walked out. Naturally, Zhao Hai and the others followed behind.

Outside the metallic room was a long corridor. What surprised Zhao Hai was that this corridor was also made of metal. It was also wide enough to allow two people to walk side by side.

After walking through this corridor for about 150 steps, Zhao Hai and the others arrived at a hall made out of metal. The hall was about 10 thousand square meters. What attracted Zhao Hai and the others’ attention was that everything in the hall was made entirely out of metal. The table, chairs, pillars, walls, everything was metal.

There were a lot of Mages and Warriors in the hall who were resting, groups of two or three were chatting, and there were also people just sitting down and drinking tea. There were also a lot of robots in the hall that provided services.

Upon seeing these people, Zhao Hai’s pupils shrunk. The bodies of each Mage and Warrior exuded a strong killing aura. One could see at a glance that these people were walking the line between life and death. Such people would be very difficult opponents.

While Zhao Hai was looking at these people, they were also sizing Zhao Hai and the others up. Their gazes weren’t very friendly, there was even a hint of hostility.

Then at this moment, a person in the hall attracted Zhao Hai’s attention. This person was just standing in the hall yet he appeared like an iron tower. This person had dark skin, a bald head, and a scar on his face that spanned from his left ear and through his left eye. This scar made the man look terrifying.

This man was very tall with his height surpassing 2.5 meters. He towered among everyone in the hall. He was a crane among chickens. His eye was currently closed as he stood there like a statue.

But when Zhao Hai saw him, his eyes involuntarily flashed a cold light. This was because the man’s killing aura was very strong, which aroused Zhao Hai’s own killing aura. Zhao Hai already knew who this man was, he must be Buddhist Warrior Yuan.

And sensing Zhao Hai’s gaze, Yuan opened his eye and looked at Zhao Hai. Naturally, he only had his right eye since his left was gone. A cold light flashed through his right eye. He obviously felt Zhao Hai’s killing aura.

Seeing that Yuan was looking at him, Zhao Hai just smiled as he withdrew his entire killing aura, showing complete control over it. Then he gave Yuan a salute.

The other people in the hall couldn’t help but gawk when they saw Zhao Hai’s performance. Everyone in the hall simultaneously made an impressed “Hoh!” sound.

These Mages and Warriors were surprised to see Zhao Hai’s attitude towards Yuan. Buddhist Warrior Yuan was an ominous presence in the Six Realms battlefield for many years. The battles he had fought easily reached the thousands with dozens of those being life and death battles. But even if he was heavily injured in those battles, he always returned. It was said that he was as resilient as a cockroach.

Because of this, Yuan had the strongest killing aura here. Most rookies who come here would urinate under Yuan’s killing aura. But Zhao Hai actually received it with a calm approach. This showed Zhao Hai’s strength.

When Yuan saw Zhao Hai’s attitude, his eyes lit up. Then he walked over, his steps were very heavy. With each step Yuan made, the ground sounded like drums.

Yuan arrived in front of Zhao Hai and the others, completely ignoring the old Mage. He looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Are you Zhao Hai?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I am. Is Mister Buddhist Warrior Yuan? This one has seen mister.”

Yuan burst out laughing, then he said, “Good, good. Truly a man praised by Ma Rulong. I also heard about what you did. Great job. You can’t be lenient towards those fellows from the Cultivation Realm. Well done, well done!”

Zhao Hi smiled faintly and said, “It’s not a big deal. I just killed someone from the Cultivation Realm as well as the Devil Realm.”

Yuan laughed once more when he heard this. Then he patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder as he turned to the old Mage and said, “I’ll be taking care of them.”

The Mage was evidently scared of Yuan. So when he heard him, he immediately nodded and said, “Please. The command has already been sent down for them to be sent to you. However, don’t forget to give them their recorders.”

Yuan nodded and said, “I know. How could this Yuan forget about that. Alright, let’s go.” Then he led Zhao Hai and the others towards a machine beside the hall.

This machine looked like an iron box with no special quality to it. Yuan stood in front of the machine and then said, “Walk in one by one and don’t move.”

Zhao Hai nodded and entered the machine first. As soon as he entered, the machine flashed with red light. This red light formed a flat plane on top of the machine and descended, scanning Zhao Hai from head to toe.

After the red light vanished, a metal wall in front of Zhao Hai opened up. Inside the opening was a wristband.

Zhao Hai extended his hand and then took the wristband before wearing it. The size of the wristband was just right. And it wasn’t heavy at all nor did it feel cold. It was actually comfortable to wear.

When Zhao Hai came out of the machine, Xiong Li followed in. The process went the same as Zhao Hai. Before long, everyone had a wristband on.

After this, Yuan looked at Zhao Hai and the others and said, “Don’t lose this thing. These things record your contribution during battles. These contributions will become points that you can exchange with anything you want. Alright let’s go. From now on, you’re part of my team.” Zhao Hai and the others nodded. Then they followed Yuan out of the hall. When they left the hall, they were once again inside a corridor. But as they walked, Zhao Hai and the others discovered that this corridor was more than a kilometer long.

A metal door was at the end of the corridor. When the group walked towards the door, it automatically opened. Then Yuan flew out with Zhao Hai and the others quickly following behind.

It was at this point that Zhao Hai and the others discovered that they were headed towards a spatial rift. The metal door actually connects to a spatial rift.

This rift wasn’t very big, it was only about three meters high and wide enough to let two people in side by side. Yuan didn’t hesitate and continued flying forward.

Zhao Hai and the others hastily followed behind. Before long, they appeared in front of another metal door. A red light flashed from the door and scanned everyone before it opened.

Yuan led Zhao Hai and the others across another corridor until they arrived at another metal hall. But this metal hall was much larger than the previous one. There were also more people here. The mixed sounds of chatting and quarrelling was heard in this hall.

At this time, they were surrounded by a group of people. The group had three Mages and four Warriors. One of them turned to Yuan and said, “Captain, is this them? Where’s Zhao Hai? Let me see him. Hahaha. He’s amazing, even daring to kill people from the Cultivation Realm. He’s certainly very strong.” The person who spoke wasn’t very tall but it was clear that he was very strong. He had messy hair and his skin was pale gold. He wore worn-out Warrior clothing but his body exuded a valiant aura.

But as this person was talking about him, Zhao Hai was stunned. He was the only one who was stunned in their group. This was because the Space had just issued a shocking prompt!

“Host has entered a subspace made by another person. Host may be discovered. Proceeding to disable tracking function. Tracking function has been disabled. The host can now move freely in this subspace.”

This prompt caused Zhao Hai to be startled and coldly sweat. Although the prompt was short, its contents were extremely terrifying. Zhao Hai was very clear that even if they were still inside a metallic room, they were already in the Six Realms Battlefield. And now the prompt just pointed out that the Six Realms Battlefield was a subspace that another person has made. This was an existence that was similar to his Space. This was scary information.

And as he thought about it more, Zhao Hai was even more startled. The Six Realms Battlefield had an entrance in every realm. When he first thought about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel strange. It’s too much of a coincidence. But now, upon knowing that the Six Realms Battlefield was someone else’s subspace, Zhao Hai knew that this was done on purpose.

The owner of the subspace opened a passage in every realm, enabling other people to enter the battlefield and kill each other.

But what was his purpose for doing this? The person who made this subspace must be an expert of extraordinary strength. There might not be such an expert in the entire World of Cultivation. The strongest person in the World of Cultivation were those legendary Immortals. However, Zhao Hai haven’t heard of Immortals having their own subspaces. Moreover, from what Ma Rulong said, the Six Realms Battlefield was enormous.

If nobody from the World of Cultivation was strong enough to do this, then who did it? Where did he come from? Why did he make the Six Realms Battlefield? What was his goal?

All of these issues passed by Zhao Hai’s mind, making him absent-minded. At this time, Zhao Hai felt a pat on his shoulder. Zhao Hai was just about to retaliate when he noticed that it was Yuan.

Zhao Hai quickly recovered. Yuan looked at Zhao Hai in confusion as he asked, “Little Hai, what happened? Why are you sweating so much? Is there a problem?”

Zhao Hai shook his head before he replied, “I’m fine. But I just thought of something so I was somewhat distracted. Captain, are these our brothers?” Zhao Hai also noticed the group that approached them.

Yuan nodded and then introduced everyone to Zhao Hai and the others. The Warrior who spoke first was surnamed Wu, Wu Yang. His metal-element body refining technique was said to be formidable. He was one of the experts in Yuan’s team.

The others were from Great Families of the Machine Field. In the Machine Field, the majority of practitioners were from External Halls that were filled with Ascenders. But in the Six Realms Battlefield, Ascenders were very rare. People sent here were mostly descendants of Great Families or Core Members of the family.

Zhao Hai and the others exchanged greetings with the other team members. After that, Yuan led everyone out of the metallic hall. Then after passing another corridor, Zhao Hai and the others went out of a metal door. Upon passing through the door, the group were met with the view of a forest. Zhao Hai and the others were currently flying above the forest..

Although Zhao Hai wanted to find out about the secret of the Six Realms Battlefield, he knew that it was impossible for him with his present strength. He might even bring danger to himself. What he needed to do was pretend that he didn’t know anything and just cultivate. He could resume his investigation when he gets stronger.

Because of this, Zhao Hai put the matter on the back of his mind as he inspected his surroundings. He discovered that the environment was indeed very good. Compared to the Cultivation Realm, the spiritual density here was thicker. It was a very good place for cultivation.

The forest where they were in can be called a virgin forest. The forest was so expansive that its end couldn’t be seen. Looking at the size of the forest, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel excited. With a forest this large, there would certainly be unique plants growing inside it. He wanted to explore the place to see if he could find something to send to the Space.

Originally, Zhao Hai wasn’t too anxious about upgrading the Space. But when he learned that the Six Realms Battlefield was a subspace of another person, he couldn’t help but feel a sense of crisis. He began to think about the security of his Space. If other people can create subspaces like the Six Realms Battlefield, then would it be possible for them to break into the Space? If that was the case, then Zhao Hai’s biggest advantage would vanish!

Chapter 1282: Core Battlefield

As Zhao Hai was looking at the forest, Yuan’s voice was heard, “Let’s go. I’ll let you see our Machine Field’s most magnificent creation. The Iron Bridge Fort”

Zhao Hai and the others were attracted by Yuan’s words. Then when they looked behind them, they couldn’t help but be dumbfounded. This was because in front of them was an enormous steel caste.

This giant steel castle was made entirely out of metal. But even so, it was miraculously floating in the air. But on the other end of the castle was a barrier that showed another similar-looking castle. If these castles were to accommodate people, then it wouldn’t be a problem for them to house ten thousand.

The outside castle was built in the style of a bastion. Its walls looked like an open flower. Placed on various places in the castle were all kinds of weapons. Each weapon certainly holds an enormous power in it.

Yuan looked at Zhao Hai and the others’ expression and said, “These two castles, one placed next to the other, guards the spatial rift. At the same time, it also acts as our headquarters, allowing us to rest peacefully. The two castles act as a bridge, with the spatial rift in between them. This is why the two castles are called the Iron Bridge Fort. Both the outside castle and the spatial rift’s castle are made manually. You should have seen that the spatial rift only allowed two people to walk in parallel. This meant that large equipment couldn’t pass through them. This limited the amount of resources that were sent over. People could only use spatial equipment to bring all kinds of materials so that the castles can be built. It took tens of years for the Machine Field to construct this fort. And ever since it was finished, our Machine Field was able to defend against the other realms.”

Zhao Hai and the others nodded. They didn’t really expect that the metallic hall they were just in was a castle.

Yuan continued, “Naturally, the Iron Bridge Fort is now acting as a rear headquarters for the Machine Field. People would only come here to exchange for rewards. Normally, other people would be stationed in other castles or bases. Later on, you will also only come here to rest. You can also use the contribution points you gained on the battlefield to exchange for rewards. Besides these things, there is also a lot of entertainment available in the fort. But if you want to use them, you will need to pay using your contribution points.”

Zhao Hai and the others nodded. They now understood more about the Six Realms Battlefield. It seems like the Machine Field had already established its own stable foothold in the Six Realms Battlefield. Otherwise, Iron Bridge Fort wouldn’t have been this peaceful.

Yuan looked at Iron Bridge Fort and then said, “Let’s go to our base.” Zhao Hai and the others nodded before they flew out with Yuan.

As they were flying, Zhao Hai looked at the scenery while also releasing silver needles. Since the Space had already masked its own presence, then the subspace wouldn’t be able to discover its existence. Even if Zhao Hai used the Space, nobody would be able to discover it.

Moreover, Zhao Hai doesn’t believe that the creator of the Six Realms Battlefield would pay any attention to him. It was like a person wouldn’t pay attention to any of his hairs.

And just as Zhao Hai was feeling a bit of a crisis, making him think of upgrading the Space as soon as possible, he immediately obtained an advantage upon entering the Six Realms Battlefield. The Space’s spiritual density has been upgraded to the Six Realm Battlefield’s level. The Space’s spiritual density was now much stronger compared to the Cultivation Realm. The density was almost approaching the level of a medium-grade spirit vein.

Although Zhao Hai was glad that the Space’s spiritual density has been upgraded, this also made him realize his disparity compared to the Six Realm Battlefield’s creator. His Space was already mysterious yet the Six Realms Battlefield was more powerful. Zhao Hai was now more vigilant with each of his actions.

The group flew quickly. It seems like Yuan wasn’t worried about encountering any dangers nearby. And since this was the case, there was no need for Zhao Hai and the others to care about it as well. The group flew nonstop for several hours before Zhao Hai discovered a small fort in the distance.

This fort wasn’t made out of metal but instead ordinary stones. However, this fort still had all kinds of magical cannons to provide it with defense. Moreover, magic formations were engraved on the entire fort.

However, Yuan just flew by that fort. As they were passing by, Zhao Hai looked at the fort and saw that there were also people guarding it.

Zhao Hai looked at Yuan in confusion as he asked, “Captain, which team does this fort belong to?”

Yuan looked at the fort and said, “It doesn’t belong to anyone. It’s just a relay station. It’s mainly used for communication and rest. Also, those without any identification will be attacked by the castle if they approach.”

Zhao Hai nodded and at the same time gained a deeper understanding of this subspace. The Six Realm Battlefield was indeed very large. They were flying quickly yet they only came upon a relay station. This meant that they were still quite a distance away from the frontlines. If this was the case, then how large was the Six Realms Battlefield exactly? Zhao Hai was beginning to wonder.

The group flew for a few more hours before resting inside a relay station. After two hours, they departed once more and flew continuously for three days before reaching the frontlines.

Upon arriving at the frontlines, Zhao Hai could immediately feel the tension in the atmosphere. Over the last three days, they mostly flew over forested areas. The rest were hills. And as long as there were hills, a fort would no doubt be constructed there. Relay stations weren’t the only things constructed. Radar stations were also made. These radar stations were constructed so that people from the other realms couldn’t sneak into the Machine Field’s territory and wreak havoc.

The frontline was a defensive position composed of a large mountain range. This mountain range was known as Lock Mountain Range. On the entire span of the mountain range were small forts dotted at certain places. Also, there were radar stations in each mountain peak. As long as a person other than those from the Machine Field enters the Lock Mountain Range, they would immediately be discovered.

Yuan’s camp in this mountain range was a small fort with around 50 guards inside. They were tasked with securing the nearby 100 li(50km). As long as an enemy appears on this 100 li distance, it was the camp’s responsibility to attack.

The fort wasn’t very large. It was also made like a bastion with magical cannons on its walls. Although Yuan’s team was strong, these magical cannons could still provide extra help.

Yuan settled Zhao Hai and the others down before he gathered everyone to introduce the newcomers. It must be said that the condition in the fort was very good. Although there were only 50 people in this fort, there were about 1000 robots serving them. Moreover, this fort was made to accommodate 500 people. Since there were only 50 here at this time, the fort was very spacious. There was ample space for everyone.

This fort has a dining hall, amusement room, and private rooms that were complete with household appliances – computers and all. One would often forget that they were in the frontlines of the Six Realms Battlefield.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect the situation here to be this good. However, Yuan also told them that beyond the Lock Mountain Range was no longer the Machine Field’s territory. It can be said that outside the Lock Mountain Range was the real battlefield where true chaos happens.

Past the Lock Mountain Range was a large forested area. This area was very fertile and spanned millions of square kilometers.

However, this region was owned by nobody. Anyone can go there to mine, pick medicine, and even murder other people for treasure. No matter what you did there, nobody would care.

This region was the core battlefield of the Six Realms Battlefield – the true Six Realms Battlefield. Yuan’s team’s job wasn’t only to defend their fort, but also to venture out to this battlefield in order to get plants and kill people.

The Six Realms Battlefield was just too large, this allowed each realm to hold on to their own territory. However, there’s a strange phenomenon wherein the resources within each realm’s territory wasn’t very diverse. There were treasures that could only be mined or grown on another territory. Each realm established strong defenses to protect their territories. But at the same time, the six realms wouldn’t dare attack another territory.

This was where the core battlefield became important. This was because this region had all resources that can be found in the other territories. Moreover, this was the only region that wasn’t unconquered.

Because the core battlefield had all the resources of the Six Realms Battlefield available, its output was naturally rich. Therefore, all realms wanted to take it for their own. But after several battles, they discovered that nobody could take this land. Therefore, the six realms reached a tacit understanding making the core battlefield a common territory. Everyone can head to the core battlefield to collect resources. However, one would need to depend on their own skill to survive. If they were killed, then they deserve it for being weak. This made the core battlefield into a huge meat grinder. Every year, countless deaths and injuries were incurred in this region. However, nobody was willing to give up on this region. At any point in time, someone was being killed in this huge territory.

Chapter 1283: Going Ou

t

Zhao Hai stood on the fort walls and looked at the hills in the distance. These hills were high. They had all kinds of plants growing on them, making them look beautiful.

Zhao Hai and the others had been here for three days. They had yet to encounter a fight in these three days. They only accompanied Yuan as they were getting familiar with the surrounding environment. And to be honest, there was nothing special in the vicinity.

The guarded area of Yuan’s camp wasn’t very large, only about 100li(50km) around the fort. Even if this area didn’t have a radar, powerful magic formation masters could still use their spiritual force to scan it.

Actually, there were almost no defending missions in the area close to Yuan’s camp. And even if there was something that needed to be taken care of, the two closest camps would take care of it. Yuan’s camp mostly went on hunting missions, killing people from the other realms in the core battlefield. Because of this, the camp’s defense was handed over to other people.

Along with getting familiar with the environment, Zhao Hai and the others were also taken to the other camps to make other people aware that they were the newcomers of Yuan’s camp.

After getting in contact with the other teams, Zhao Hai began to understand Yuan’s position. Although Yuan was only a captain of 50 people, it was clear that his influence extended to the entire Lock Mountain Range.

Buddhist Warrior Yuan has been on the frontlines of Lock Mountain Range for seven years. And he had been the person who fought the most and also the one who dared to fight the most. More than a thousand small and large battles, a few of them where he almost died – it can be said that the Machine Field’s Lock Mountain Range became peaceful because of Yuan.

Zhao Hai asked other people and heard that before Yuan arrived in Lock Mountain Range, people would come look for trouble every other day. And not to say about robbing, people were already lucky if they weren’t robbed while at their camps.

When Yuan arrived at the mountain range, he began to lead people to fight the other realms repeatedly. Once someone from the other realms attacked the mountain range, Yuan would quickly deal with them with ferocity. Even if the Machine Field lost 100 individuals to kill 35, Yuan would still trade to teach them a lesson.

In these battles, it’s natural that Yuan’s team had the most casualties. The team has been reinforced multiple times, and there have been cases where it was wiped out, with Yuan as the only survivor..

Even with such dire consequences, Yuan continued to fight. He went all out and held nothing back. There were multiple times where he was severely wounded, almost losing his life.

But such battle style actually brought advantages. Seeing that they were beginning to lose heavily against the Machine Field, the other realms slowly stopped attacking the Lock Mountain Range. This allowed Yuan to lead people into the core battlefield, giving the Machine Field the breath of air it needed.

But in this case, more conflict was inevitable. After many battles, Yuan managed to gain a reputation. It was also at this time that the other realms gave him the nickname One-eyed Buddhist.

Naturally, the people from other camps weren’t in the Lock Mountain Range from the very beginning. In fact, those from the Machine Field who battled here would stay for three years at most. Yuan’s seven-year stay was actually very unique.

While Zhao Hai was thinking about these things, he suddenly heard heavy footsteps approaching him. He doesn’t need to see who it was, it was certainly Yuan. Only Yuan would have such heavy footsteps.

As soon as Zhao Hai turned his head, he saw Yuan walking slowly towards his side. Then Yuan looked at the direction of the core battlefield and said, “What are you thinking about?”

Zhao Hai replied, “I’m just wondering why Captain stayed inside the Six Realms Battlefield for this many years. With your current contributions, you can be positioned at the rear and even return to the Machine FIeld. Your status would not be low. So why would you stay in this dangerous place?”

Yuan didn’t move, he still looked at the core battlefield in the distance. Then after a while, he said, “Many people asked me this question, but I haven’t told them. But I can tell you, it’s because of revenge!”

Yuan didn’t say much but Zhao Hai understood what he meant after recalling the story about Yuan’s life. Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, then I’ll help Captain with his revenge. By the way, Captain. You have been doing this for several years, so why haven’t you practiced a higher level Cultivation Method? Why are you practicing a low-level method?”

This wasn’t news to anyone in the Lock Mountain Range, so upon hearing Zhao Hai, Yuan turned to him and then smiled as he said, “You must be thinking that one couldn’t progress far if they practice low-level methods right?”

Zhao Hai was surprised when he heard Yuan, but he shook his head and said, “That’s not necessarily the case. I have also seen basic methods from the Cultivation Realm. They’re very clever and could make a person progress. However, the speed would be a bit slower. It was likely for their practitioners to die before they reached a higher level.”

Yuan nodded. “That’s correct. It seems like you have some experience. The progress of those cultivation methods are indeed slow, but there’s something good about that. This meant that there would be steady progress with close to no threat of being possessed by a devil. Moreover, there would hardly be any bottlenecks in such methods. As long as one practiced hard enough, they would progress. Although the speed is very slow, progress is gained through hard work and stability.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Yuan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, we’ll be heading out to hunt. Once you meet people from the other realms, you will understand what I’m saying.” Then after laughing, Yuan turned and left.

Although Zhao Hai didn’t understand what Yuan wanted to say, he didn’t mind it too much. In any case, he would find out about it tomorrow.

The next morning, after everyone had eaten, Yuan called the entire team over. Including Zhao Hai’s group, Yuan now had 50 people present. But even if this was a small team, everyone knew that only under Yuan could one earn merit very quickly. But this also meant that they were more likely to die in his command. Because of this, very few people joined Yuan’s group on their own decision.

Seeing his team, Yuan nodded and said, “We’ll be heading out today to hunt. 30 people will be left behind here, the rest will follow me. Little Hai and the other new recruits will come with me. As for the others, decide upon yourselves.”

Discussion was then heard in the dining hall. Nobody was thinking that they wouldn’t go along with Zhao Hai and the others. On the contrary, people wanted to come with him. But including Zhao Hai and his brothers, there were only 20 slots in this excursion. There was an unceasing debate about who these 20 people would be.

If this was any other team, then people would definitely hide when it came to going to the core battlefield. Very few people would go there. But Yuan’s team was different. All of these people had assimilated Yuan’s attitude. So upon hearing that they would be going to the core battlefield, everyone wanted to join the team.

After arguing for some time, the 20 people were finally decided. Those who were chosen were excited while those who failed to qualify were depressed. Seeing this situation, Zhao Hai smiled faintly. His favorable impression towards Yuan has increased by one point.

A flaming eagle will have a flaming nest. Because Yuan was belligerent, then the other people in his camp would naturally be influenced.

Seeing that the team has been decided, Yuan nodded and said, “Alright, we’ll head out soon, make preparations. Right, since Little Hai and the others are beginners, Wu Yang, you brief them.” Then after he said that, Yuan turned around and left.

Zhao Hai turned to Wu Yang and asked, “Brother Wu Yang, what is Captain talking about? What do we need to know?”

Wu Yang wasn’t selected this time, so he was quite dejected. But after hearing Zhao Hai, he answered. “Captain meant that you need to take some food and drinks along with you.” Xiong Li and the others were also beside Zhao Hai, so when they heard Wu Yang, they looked at each other and laughed.

Wu Yang looked at Zhao Hai and the others and said, “Why are you laughing? Go make your preparations.”

Xiong Li smiled and said, “Brother Wu, when it comes to drinks and food, then there’s nothing to prepare. Every time Little Hai goes out, he would bring a lot of food and drinks with him. Even if we stayed a year or longer outside, we still wouldn’t worry about starving. Hahaha. I can even say that when it comes to preparing food and wine, nobody can beat Little Hai.” Wu Yang stared, then he looked at Zhao Hai. He couldn’t really believe what Xiong Li said.

Zhao Hai laughed and then waved his hand as a giant crab appeared. He placed the crab on the table and then smiled as he looked at Wu Yang and said, “Brother Wu, I’ll give this to you. It’s freshly cooked, you can eat it directly.”

Wu Yang stared at the crab. This was the first time he saw a crab as large as this. A crab as large as this was certainly a magic beast. But this beast was now boiled and was sending out thick fragrances.

Zhao Hai glanced at Wu Yang before chuckling and leaving. When he went outside, those who were going with the mission had already prepared. After a while, Yuan also arrived. He was wearing the same clothes, he didn’t look like he was going to battle. His eyes swept through everyone and then nodded. He turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, are you ready? We aren’t going out for just a day, you should bring more food.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Captain, rest assured. I have everything ready.”

Yuan nodded, then he said, “Alright, let’s go.” After saying that, he flew and led the team towards the core battlefield. Zhao Hai and the others immediately followed closely behind.

Upon leaving Lock Mountain Range, the group immediately slowed down. They also took out their weapons and made formations.

Seeing the group being like this, Zhao Hai and the others became somewhat nervous. Xiong Li and the others also took out their weapons, only Zhao Hai remained unarmed. He just calmly looked at the scenery ahead. The other people in the team couldn’t help but look at Zhao Hai. However, Zhao Hai didn’t care, the same was true with Xiong Li and the others. In the minds of Zhao Hai’s brothers, if Zhao Hai took his weapon out, then it would just be bullying.

Chapter 1284: Thornweed and Mouse Demon

Yuan also noticed Zhao Hai, but he didn’t say anything. Yuan had received newcomers from the Machine Field before. All of these newcomers were arrogant when they first came here. But when they left, this arrogance was gone. Yuan also wanted Zhao Hai to learn a lesson.

Zhao Hai didn’t mind the gazes either. In fact, he wasn’t really that worried about this mission. In the last three days, his silver needles had already mapped the surrounding area as well as a large part of the core battlefield. It was basically impossible for other people to attack them without Zhao Hai’s notice.

At this time, Zhao Hai wouldn’t say anything. He continued to follow behind Yuan as they flew forward. He also had Cai’er pay attention to their surroundings.

In fact Zhao Hai wasn’t only paying attention to their surroundings, he was also scanning for things that he could get. He would find time in the future to procure them.

He had just arrived in the Six Realms Battlefield, so he can’t be too rampant. So even if he knew where good things were, he would have to wait some time so that he wouldn’t attract attention.

Yuan led the team forward nonstop. After flying for three hours, Yuan waved his hand to make everyone halt. Zhao Hai discovered that they had arrived in a patch of thornweed.

Thornweed was a very famous medicinal herb in the Six Realms Battlefield. Thornweed was an indispensable herb that was used for medicines that refine the body. And the older the herb was, the more valuable it is.

Thornweed doesn’t grow in the Machine Field. These herbs mostly grow on the Demon Realm’s territory. Nobody knows if this was intentional since the Demon Realm gives priority to refining the body. However, this thornweed was quite common in the Six Realms Battlefield.

As soon as Yuan stopped, he pointed towards the thornweed and said, “This is a patch of thornweed. This patch is also one of the Machine Fields more important sources of this herb. We come here once in a few days to check it out. Sometimes we would use magic water to make them grow. If people from the other realms try to steal these herbs, there will inevitably be a fierce battle.”

Just as Yuan was done speaking, Zhao Hai’s expression changed. Yuan noticed this change and said, “Little Hai? Do you have anything to say?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Captain, I just found a group of Demons. They are picking thornweed.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Yuan couldn’t help but stare. Then the color of his face changed. He confirmed, “Are you telling the truth? You should know that we have small-scale radars built.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “I can’t be wrong. Those who came here are earth-dwelling Demons. My feelings can’t be incorrect.”

When Yuan saw that Zhao Hai wasn’t lying, his expression finally turned serious. He immediately said, “Point the direction. Everyone, follow Little Hai.”

Zhao Hai quickly pointed towards the direction of the Demons and then flew towards it. Yuan and the others immediately followed behind him.

Yuan followed behind with a very serious expression. This wasn’t his first meeting with the Demon Race. But among the Demons, these earth-dwelling Demons were the most repugnant race there is. These Demons had inborn abilities to stealthily move underground. Although the Machine Field’s sensors were sensitive and could even detect most earthwalking techniques, these earth-dwelling Demons could actually hide from these sensors. Because of this, these earth-dwelling Demons could go into the Machine Field’s territory to steal any herbs they want – and the Machine Field couldn’t do anything about it.

Although it was called thornweed, it was actually a short vine. But it was a short plant nonetheless. A 100-year old thornweed was only a bit more than a meter high, with younger thornweeds being much shorter. It was precisely because of this that the thornweed was a rare herb in the Machine Field.

And even if the Machine Field installed sensors in the area, they actually weren’t that useful. This was because people from the other realms would destroy these sensors from time to time. And installing them again would take some effort.

In fact, the other realms also do this, not just the Machine Field. They would install their own sensors in their areas, particularly in places where they can harvest special products. However, installing these sensors was a constant struggle. A sensor might be built in one place, but another sensor would be destroyed in another.

Zhao Hai led the team towards the place where the Demons were currently lurking. The Demons might have discovered Zhao Hai and the others since they weren’t moving anymore. However, the patch of thornweed that they were in had already been harvested.

The age of these thornweeds wasn’t small, with the youngest one being ten years old. Although this age was usable, the people of the Machine Field required older thornweeds. Because of this, this patch of thornweeds had herbs that were almost 50 years old.

Thornweeds have a main root that would slowly spread around. As long as this main root survived, then the thornweed would continually grow. Because of this, people would just harvest the thornweeds in the core battlefield without destroying their main roots. And this was especially true with older thornweds. But if these main roots were destroyed, then the thornweeds in the core battlefield would become fewer and fewer and before long nobody would be able to obtain them.

The reason why the Machine Field hated earth-dwelling Demons was because these Demons could easily destroy thornweed patches. And once they destroy the main root, then that thornweed patch is finished.

Seeing their thornweed patch being harvested, Yuan’s expression couldn’t help but tighten. However, the Demons had already hid underground. And if they attack these Demons, then they might damage the thornweed patch even more. This wasn’t something that Yuan wanted to see. He couldn’t help but feel helpless, he couldn’t do anything at all.

Although the patch looked destroyed, there were still some roots that managed to survive. The Demons deliberately did this to make Yuan anxious about harming the rest of the roots. They were making Yuan angry.

Seeing this situation, Yuan couldn’t help but be incensed. He began to think about destroying this patch himself other than making the Demons benefit.

When Zhao Hai saw Yuan’s expression, he guessed what he was about to do. He immediately blocked Yuan and said, “Captain, wait a moment.” Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as a yellow ball of light appeared. Then he threw the ball of light towards the thornweed. Then the light went underground.

Although this was Zhao Hai’s first time in the Six Realms Battlefield, he wasn’t completely clueless about the resources present here. This was because they were given additional information in their computers about the Six Realms Battlefield. And because of this, Zhao Hai had some understanding regarding the thornweed plant.

This was also the reason why Zhao Hai stopped Yuan. He knew that if Yuan attacked, then the thornweeds would certainly be finished.

When Yuan saw Zhao Hai’s action, he couldn’t help but stare. Then he looked at Zhao Hai in confusion and asked, “Little Hai, what are you doing? We can’t have these bastards pick the thornweed.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Captain, rest assured. Not only can these fellows not get their hands on the thornweed, they will also leave their lives here. Just watch.”

Yuan nodded and said, “If it’s possible, don’t destroy the root. Otherwise, this patch will be wasted.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t worry about it. I’ll make sure to save the thornweed. Actually, it seems like the main root managed to survive. I’ve already made sure to protect it.”

After he said that, Zhao Hai pointed towards a place where the thornweed looked the most healthy. This was where the thornweed’s main root was. However, its surroundings were kept in good condition. These Demons knew how important a thornweed’s main root was, so they also knew not to destroy it. Otherwise, the Machine Field would go all out in pursuing them.

The earthen yellow light wasn’t actually offensive magic but instead it was a defensive spell. Its main function was to protect the main root from being destroyed. At the same time, Zhao Hai put some Undead underground to hunt down and kill the Demons. With the Space’s monitor present, it was impossible for these Demons to escape. The only thing they could do was to desperately fight the Undead. But no matter what they do, they wouldn’t be able to do anything to the thornweed main root.

The others looked at Zhao Hai. Actually, there were two Earth Mages among them. However, these Mages couldn’t do anything about the present situation. Earth Magic doesn’t have a lot of magic that could attack underground targets. Moreover, Earth Magic was mainly composed of wide-scale magic. It was impossible for them to make an attack lest they place the thronweed in danger. Therefore, like Yuan, they could only watch.

The group paid attention to the thornweed patch, waiting for results. The region was actually very calm. There were no vibrations detected from underground. However, this peace made those present relaxed as well as disappointed.

They were disappointed because they couldn’t see what was happening but they were happy that the thornweed wasn’t destroyed. And at this moment, the safety of the thornweed was their utmost concern.

Before long, not far away from the thornweed patch, a lump of earth emerged before the corpse of a mouse emerged from a hole.

This mouse had white fur and was five meters tall, not including its tail. If one included its tail, then the mouse would be ten meters long. It had hook-like claws and two sharp incisors. Its tail was like a steel whip. One could see how powerful this mouse was.

This was a Demon Mouse. These Demon Mice were innately skilled in traversing the earth. However, the strength of these Mice wasn’t good, otherwise they wouldn’t have been killed so soon.

Zhao Hai didn’t care as he waved his hand, causing black gas to cover the mouse. When the black gas vanished, the mouse had already vanished and was replaced by an undead. Then it returned underground to join in on the hunt.

There were more than one Demon Mouse who came to harvest the Machine Field’s thornweed patch. In total, there were five of them. One Mouse was at the Core Formation stage while the other four were at Foundation Establishment.

Just as the Foundation Establishment Demon mouse was killed, it immediately hunted its own kin. When the other Mice saw this, they couldn’t help but panic. They already had their hands full in dealing with the Undead. The Undead that were assaulting them were a variety of ground-dwelling beasts.

Although earthwalking was an innate ability of the Demon Mouse, this didn’t mean that they were the only ones who have it. These Undead Beast also possess the ability to move underground, albeit their skills couldn’t match the Demon Mice.

However, the Undead alleviated this weakness by using their numbers. There were only five Demon Mice while the Undead were uncountable.

After the Mice discovered that they were surrounded, they began to think about destroying the main root of the thornweed patch. However, they couldn’t do anything to it since it was being protected by a spell.

The four Foundation Establishment Mice were killed one after another. At this point, only the Core Formation Mouse was left. However, it was clear that it wouldn’t last long. When it felt that it was in a precarious position, the Demon Mouse began drilling upwards towards the surface.

As Yuan was looking at the ground, a white shadow suddenly flew out. Yuan didn’t immediately move since he wanted to see what this thing was.

Before long, the white shadow stopped. It was a thin Old Mouse that was wearing white robes. It’s eyes were black, but it gave off a sinister light.

The Old Mouse actually looked distressed. He looked at Yuan and gnashed its teeth as it said, “Yuan, we’re just snatching your thornweed. Why are you being so ruthless? You even killed four of my sons. What can you say about this?”

Upon hearing the Old Mouse, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. He hadn’t seen someone as shameless as this. The Mice were the ones who were stealing, but now it was Yuan who needed to explain?

Yuan didn’t hesitate as he laughed and said, “Hao Donglai, it turns out to be you. So what? The last time, you bullied us heavily. Did you really think that we are that easy to bully? What else could I do since you decided to steal our thornweed? Not to say about your four sons, even if forty of them came, we will still kill them. And since you came today, then don’t even think about leaving.”

When he saw that Yuan was serious, a hint of fear flashed before Hao Donglai’s eyes. However, he quickly responded, “Yuan, if you kill me, the Old Ancestor will certainly not let you off. Do you think you alone can deal with the Old Ancestor’s anger? If you let me go, then I’ll forget today’s matter. This will save you from being troubled by the Old Ancestor. What do you think?”

Chapter 1285: One Should Return As Good As One Receives

Hao Donglai was admitting defeat, yet he was also issuing a threat. When he heard Hao Donglai, Yuan laughed and said, “Hao Donglai, you’re too naive. Who do you think this Yuan is? Now that you fell into my hands, you want me to let you go? Why don’t you just tell me to kill myself?”

As soon as Hao Donglai heard this, his expression finally changed. He knew that Yuan wouldn’t let him go. So his face turned resolute as he said, “Yuan, don’t go too far. If I go all out, then I can take your teammates with me. I don’t believe that your subordinates aren’t afraid of death!”

Just as Hao Dongali said this, a loud laughter was heard. However, this laughter didn’t come from Yuan. Hao Donglai turned his head towards the group of newcomers. Yuan and the others were also stunned. Then they turned to see that Xiong Li and the others were laughing.

Zhao Hai also chuckled at the side. Naturally, he knew what Xiong Li and the others were laughing at. On the other hand, Yuan and the others had yet to know about Zhao Hai. The other members of Yuan’s camp were somewhat anxious. They knew that even if they weren’t weak, they were still much weaker compared to the Old Mouse.

Yuan looked at Xiong Li and the others who were laughing, then he knit his brows and said, “Xiong Li, why are you laughing?”

Xiong Li suppressed his laughter before he said, “Captain, I heard that the eyes of a mouse is small, but I believe it now. The Old Rat really wants to go all out against us? Hahaha. It’s so funny. We can’t count how many people like him Little Hai killed. And he wants to go all out as a threat? What a joke.”[1]

Yuan couldn’t help but look at Zhao Hai when he heard Xiong Li. Although they knew some things about the Six Realms Beginner Competition, the information available to them were basic. They didn’t have any good understanding about Zhao Hai’s strength. The only thing Yuan knew was that Zhao Hai was blatantly challenging the folks from the Cultivation Realm. And since Yuan had some enmity against the Cultivation Realm, he was glad to accept Zhao Hai. He really wasn’t aware of how strong Zhao Hai was.

Zhao Hai smiled towards Hao Donglai before saying, “I’ve been wanting to fight the Demon Race in the Six Realms Beginner Competition. But unfortunately, all the Demons have been eliminated by the Cultivators before I get the opportunity. Captain, I want to use this chance to try.”

When Yuan saw Zhao Hai’s confidence, he nodded and said, “Alright, but don’t destroy the thornweed.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Dealing with the old mouse isn’t too difficult. Don’t worry about it Captain.”

Hao Donglai was already incensed about his current state, so when he heard Zhao Hai he coldly snorted and said, “Kid, since you want to be crippled, then let me show you how fierce I can be.” Then he gave a roar as a 50 meter tall mouse appeared in front of Zhao Hai. Then the mouse waved its claws and sent two claw attacks towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then released two magic formations to block the two attacks. Then he looked at Hao Donglai’s real body and said, “It’s really a mouse spirit. Interesting. However, I hate mice.” Then he waved his hand and released a 1000-layer formation to attack Hao Donglai.

Hao Donglai saw this attack and immediately issued a high-pitched scream. Then a ball of sand flew out of his mouth and directly hit Zhao Hai’s formation, crushing it completely.

When Zhao Hai saw this, his expression changed. Then he smiled and said, “Very interesting. He’s much better compared to those other trash.”

This ball of sand was an ability of the Mouse Race. However, only variant members of the Mouse Race like Hao Donglai can use it.

The sand that Hao Donglai spat out wasn’t ordinary sand, but instead poisoned sand. It’s offensive strength was very powerful. After crushing Zhao Hai’s formation, the sands proceeded to attack Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai immediately released another 1000-layer formation to block it.

Hao Donglai didn’t hold back as he threw himself towards Zhao Hai. Upon seeing the situation, Yuan’s expression couldn’t help but change. He wanted to go forward to help but instead he was blocked by Xiong Li.

Yuan looked at Xiong Li and said, “Why are you blocking me? Little Hai is a Mage. He’s finished if Hao Dongali gets in close range.”

Xiong Li smiled faintly and said, “Little Hai is just playing around. With that Mouse’s strength, how could he get close to Little Hai? Little Hai is both a Mage and a Warrior. Captain doesn’t need to worry. If Zhao Hai wanted to deal with him then he would’ve already done it. I think Little Hai just wanted to experience the Demon Realm’s methods.”

Yuan stared. He had yet to see why Xiong Li and the others were so confident in Zhao Hai. He turned to look at Lu Dingtian and the others and saw that they had the same expression. It seems like they agree to Xiong Li’s words.

This made Yuan more curious about Zhao Hai’s strength. He felt that Xiong Li and the others’ confidence in Zhao Hai was too strange.

At this moment, Zhao Hai had already exchanged a few moves with Hao Donglai. Although Hao Donglai wanted to approach Zhao Hai, Zhao Hai didn’t give him the opportunity to get close. Zhao Hai’s 1000-layer formations weren’t easy to deal with. Because of this, Hao Donglai had yet to get in close-combat with Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai noticed that Hao Donglai was beginning to repeat his methods, so he knew that it was time to stop playing around. He waved his hand to release another 1000-layer formation, then he punched out immediately after.

The magic formation was a cover for Hao Donglai to focus on. The true killer strike was the fist.

And sure enough, Hao Donglai was attracted by Zhao Hai’s magic formation. He thought that Zhao Hai was a pure Mage so he moved his body and evaded Zhao Hai’s magic formation. But suddenly, he felt a fist-shaped energy coming towards him. The fist was so powerful that Hao Donglai already felt it before it reached him.

Hao Donglai’s white fur stood up as he screamed. Then a large phantom Mouse appeared outside his body. This was a type of defensive measure of the Demon Race, known as the Dharma Protector.

Dharma Protector was quite a famous defensive measure of the Demon Race. However, along with its powerful might, the technique also consumed a lot of energy. Using the Dharma Protector once will consume a fourth of the Demon’s energy. But this technique was indeed very powerful.

Zhao Hai’s fist connected just as Hao Donglai’s Dharma Protector appeared. A bang was heard before the Dharma Protector was destroyed. Then the fist hit Hao Donglai’s body and threw him up into the air. The old Mouse spit mouthfuls of blood which carried parts of his innards.

But since the bodies of the Demon Race were tenacious, this damage didn’t kill Hao Dongai. In fact, he used the force of the fist to launch himself as far as possible.

But how could Zhao Hai allow this to happen? When he saw that Hao Donglai was running, he vanished in place and appeared in front of the Mouse Demon. Upon seeing Zhao Hai appearing in front of him, Hao Donglai’s heart couldn’t help but tighten. He was now half-dead and he didn’t have any more strength to fight back. Moreover, Zhao Hai appeared very close to him, making escape close to impossible. Zhao Hai pointed and a bloody hole appeared in Hao Donglai’s forehead. Then the light slowly vanished from the Mouse Demon’s eyes before he finally died.

When Hao Donglai died, Zhao Hai immediately waved his hand and turned him into an Undead. Then he sent the Mouse Demon to the Space before flying back to where Yuan and the others were.

Yuan and the others were left dull standing in place. It was as if they had been petrified by a spell. It needed to be said that Hao Donglai had a minor reputation in the Six Realms Battlefield. He was given the nickname ‘Poisonous Sand Rat’. Yuan and Hao Donglai had also fought before. But at that time, Yuan was at a disadvantage. During that battle, Yaun had 20 people while Hao Donglai had 20 people as well. In the end, Yuan lost the battle and was forced to retreat to the Lock Mountain Range. Yuan lost quite a lot of people at that time. So naturally, Yuan knew how strong Hao Donglai was.

But now, this Hao Donglai actually fell after exchanging a few moves with Zhao Hai. Also, from what Yuan had seen, it seems like Zhao Hai was done playing around. Just as Xiong Li said, Zhao Hai wanted to see the methods of the Demon Race. And once he saw everything he wanted to see, Zhao Hai proceeded to go for the kill.

Yuan was shocked by the fighting strength that Zhao Hai displayed. One must know that Core Formation Demons were very strong. Even Yuan wasn’t certain that he would win one-on-one. But Zhao Hai just used a couple of moves to kill his opponent. Wasn’t he too strong?

When he saw Zhao Hai approaching the team, Yuan finally recovered. Then his eyes shone brightly as he laughed and said, “Good job, Little Hai. Great job. That was satisfying to see. I didn’t expect you to be that strong. Hahaha. Good, good. With your strength, you can go anywhere you want in the Six Realms Battlefield.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Captain is praising me too much. Right, Captain, where do we go next?”

Yuan turned towards the thornweed patch and then sneered before he said, “Since things became like this, then let’s be impolite and go to the Demon Realm’s territory. Those Demons always run to the Machine Field to bully us. I think it’s time for us to return the favor.” Then after he said that, he flew towards a direction in the core battlefield.

Zhao Hai and the others weren’t very familiar with the places in the Six Realms Battlefield, so they just followed behind Yuan. But at this time, Zhao Hai noticed that the others from the team had changed their attitude towards him.

Battles in the Six Realms Battlefield happen every day. In this place, strength defines the chances of your survival as well as your contributions. The stronger you are, the more contributions you can gain. Therefore, everyone in the Six Realms Battlefield respected the strong. And the strength that Zhao Hai displayed was enough for these people to give him respect. While everyone was being polite to Zhao Hai, they were also secretly happy. After all, with a powerful teammate like him around, their safety was more assured.

Small eyes = shortsighted

Chapter 1286: Emergency

Before heading out, Zhao Hai already understood that they would go hunting in the core battlefield for more than a day or two. The core battlefield was just too large. Moreover, with how many people were here, sneak attacks were quite common. And once a big fish arrives, people would immediately want to destroy them. However, such a case couldn’t be done in one or two days, it would at least take ten days or even half a month. This was something that everyone knew.

This was also the reason why Yuan urged Zhao Hai to get more food before heading out. And this lies the disadvantage of those from the Machine Field. People from the Machine Field needed to eat while those from the other realms only consume fasting pills and similar medicines.

Also, besides the other inhabitants, one should pay attention to the Six Realms Battlefield’s beasts.

The Six Realms Battlefield might sound like it was under the control of the Six Realms. However, this wasn’t really the case. There were plenty of extremely powerful beasts in here. These beasts were different from Demons. Demons were those who practiced to the point where they gained a humanoid form. On the other hand, no matter how strong these beasts become, they don’t have any humanoid form.

However, one should not underestimate these beasts just because they don’t have humanoid forms. These beasts were extremely strong, they weren’t any less powerful than those in the Six Realms Battlefield. These beasts control their own territories and are also united with the other beasts, forming the Beast Alliance. The territory controlled by the Beast Alliance was a place where nobody could just enter.

And this Beast Alliance was quite unusual. Not only do they control their own territory, they could also benefit and make use of their surroundings. There were multiple forbidden areas in the Six Realms Battlefield where a large number of beasts inhabit. If anyone from the World of Cultivation entered these places, then they would no doubt be slaughtered.

There are a lot of people in the World of Cultivation but they couldn’t invest too much manpower in the Six Realms Battlefield. Once a group sent a large number of people to the Six Realms Battlefield, then the other realms would unite against them. Because of this, the core battlefield would only have small parties going around it. The size of a party would generally be below 100 people.

A team of 100 people would never in their right minds enter the territory of these beasts. These beasts couldn’t be annoyed because of their formidable strength. Moreover, low-level beasts were fearless. Their fearlessness was no less than the Bug Race. Because of this, nobody dared to provoke them.

All realms in the Six Realms Battlefield have their own controlled territory. But at the same time, there were also territories that they didn’t fully control. Such places will become points of brutal fights.

People from other realms would go to these semi-controlled territories to cause trouble. Their purpose was to steal herbs and other resources as well as to kill people.

No which realm people came from, they would definitely be equipped adequately when they go to the Six Realms Battlefield. This allowed them to be ready for battle at any time. And to some extent, these equipment could be regarded as plunderable resources.

The equipment of those sent to the Six Realms Battlefield were no doubt top-tier. And because the dead don’t need equipment, these top-tier items became a resource in the battlefield. Whether they were magic artifacts, spirit artifacts, or devil artifacts, these items were all made of the finest materials. With enough technique, these items could be reforged and refined once more. Because of this, besides mining for resources and picking herbs, people in the Six Realms Battlefield also resort to hunting other people.

Yuan was very familiar with the situation in the Six Realms Battlefield. So he advanced carefully. Each time they go some distance forward, they would stop and send scouts ahead. They were also resting much more frequently. Yuan wanted the team to maintain their best states as much as possible.

Yuan knew very well how dangerous the Core Battlefield was. It was impossible for one to know when they would run into an enemy. If your strength wasn’t at its peak once you met an enemy, then you would have a very hard time.

Yuan carefully bypassed the beast territories while paying attention to their surrounding environment and keeping the team’s combat power at its peak. It can be said that if one hasn’t experienced multiple life and death situations in the Six Realm Battlefield, then they wouldn’t have been able to do this. What Yuan has done wasn’t easy.

Zhao Hai followed beside Yuan while also paying attention to the surroundings. The Six Realms Battlefield was really too big. Although the silver needles were mapping the battlefield for the past few days, it had yet to cover a significant amount of area. Moreover, Zhao Hai discovered that the map wasn’t very useful in his current situation. A map may allow one to grasp a general setup of an area, it was still difficult for it to show the level of danger present.

While they were flying forward, Yuan suddenly stopped at a foot of a hill. Zhao Hai saw Yaun frowning, so he couldn’t help but ask, “Captain, what’s wrong? Why do you seem worried?”

Yuan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, how long do you think we’ve been out?”

Zhao Hai thought about it and said, “About 8 hours. Is there something wrong about this?”

Yuan nodded and said, “There’s something wrong. The Machine Field still has control over the area four hours away from Lock Mountain Range. Beyond that is an area that we don’t completely control. This area will be the start of the core battlefield. But generally, we would either spot an enemy or receive an attack two hours after heading into this area. At most, the peace wouldn’t last for three hours. And now, from what you can see, we’re already four hours in. This situation is very unusual.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare when he heard Yuan. Then his expression sank. Although he doesn’t fully understand the situation in the Six Realms Battlefield, from what Yuan said, then the situation was indeed unusual.

When he thought of this, Zhao Hai immediately looked at Yuan and said, “Captain, how about I send some Undead to scout the surroundings? If there’s something wrong, then we would only lose the Undead. What do you think?”

Yuan paused for a moment when he heard Zhao Hai, then he nodded and said, “Alright, but can your Undead scout properly?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Captain can rest assured. My Undead are intelligent.” Then he waved his hand and released five Demon Mice Undead. These were Hao Donglai and his team. Then Zhao Hai waved his hand once more as the five Mice vanished into the hill.

Yuan and the others dumbfoundedly looked at the Mice. Their injuries had disappeared, they didn’t look like Undead at all. If they didn’t see Zhao Hai kill them, then they would have believed that Hao Donglai and the others were still alive.

As Hao Donglai’s group dug into the ground, Yuan finally responded as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, were those Hao Donglai’s group?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Yes, they want to steal our thornweed so I turned them into Undead. It’s appropriate for them to scout for us.”

Yuan heard Zhao Hai and couldn’t help but laugh. Then he patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder without saying anything. At this time, Xiong Li and the others noticed what was happening so they approached Zhao Hai.

Xiong Li looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Little Hai, what happened? Why did you send those Undead?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Captain suspects that it has been too peaceful. It’s not normal. So I sent some Undead to take a look. If something happens, then we would only lose those Undead.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Li Kuangren smiled and said, “So it’s like that. We’ve been in the Six Realms Battlefield for several days already but my weapon has yet to be used. It’s annoying really.”

Dongfang Yu smiled faintly and said, “We’ll certainly be able to fight. But we still need to be careful. After all, this is the Six Realms Battlefield. If we can’t save Little Hai when the time comes, then we brothers will lose a lot of face.”

Sun Fei chuckled and said, “I really want to try my new spells. But I haven’t had the opportunity. In any case, I’ve been saved by Fifth Brother several times already, so I don’t mind being saved once more. I’m actually getting used to it.”

When they heard Sun Fei, Donfang Yu and the others couldn’t help but laugh. On the other hand, Yuan and the others were somewhat confused. The Six Realms Battlefield was an extremely dangerous place. Even Nascent Soul Experts would tread these waters with caution. If they were careless for even a moment, then there’s a good chance for them to be killed. But now, Dongfang Yu and the others weren’t worried at all. Instead, they looked excited. Yuan and the others could see that this attitude was caused by their infinite confidence in Zhao Hai. This caused them to be puzzled.

At this time, a Demon Mouse came back and approached Zhao Hai. Then after hearing the situation, Zhao Hai’s expression changed. He waved his hand to receive the Demon Mouse before turning his head to Yuan and saying, “Captain, a group of Machine Field Experts are being attacked by Sprites in the east. It seems like the situation is critical. What do we do?”

Yuan stared for a moment before he said, “Are you sure that they’re from the Machine Field?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “The Demon Mouse that just returned said that the team leader is a man with a long blade. He has around 30 subordinates with him. On the other side, the Sprites have 50 people. The situation isn’t looking so good.”

Chapter 1287: Trap

“Eight-star Liu Zhen”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Yuan’s expression finally changed, “So it’s Liu Zhen. They should need our help. Let’s head towards them.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then flew towards the direction that the Demon Mouse came from. While he stayed at Lock Mountain Range, he also heard Eight-star Liu Zheng’s name being talked about.

Eight-star Liu Zhen was nicknamed such because he guarded Eight-star Peak of Lock Mountain Range. This person used a long blade. His blade attacks seemed infinite and his strength was extraordinary. ‘Eight-star’ was the name given to him by the other realms.

A character that was given a nickname like Yuan couldn’t be a simple man. Therefore, Zhao Hai also paid attention to Liu Zheng. However, since Eight-star Peak was far away from Yuan’s fort, Zhao Hai wasn’t able to see him. Zhao Hai didn’t expect to meet him at this time.

Everyone followed behind Zhao Hai. Not long after they began flying eastwards, they heard the sound of fighting in front of them. The group increased their speed before seeing all kinds of Sprites surrounding a group of Machine Field experts.

The strength of the Machine Field experts wasn’t bad. They formed a circle formation with Mages in the middle. They were constantly casting spells while the Warriors weren’t actually using their sword qi. Instead, they used their own weapons to defend against the Sprite summons.

Including their summons, the Sprites had 100 people all in all. Their summons looked like tree spirits. These tree spirits were very tall and huge. In addition to their humanoid forms, their entire body was composed of bark and tree roots. Their actions were quite robotic, but they were no doubt strong.

Meanwhile, on the periphery of the tree spirits were a group of Sprites flying in the air. However, these Sprites were different from the Sprites Zhao Hai had seen before. These Sprites were wearing full-body armor. At this time, the Sprites were talking with each other with no worry on their faces. It was as if they were already convinced of their victory.

As soon as he saw this, Yuan immediately wanted to rush forward. However, he was stopped by Zhao Hai. Yuan was stunned, but he knew that Zhao Hai wouldn’t stop him for no reason. So he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “What’s wrong?”

Zhao Hai pointed around as he smiled bitterly and said, “We’ve been tricked. This is a trap. They deliberately made Liu Zhen survive in order to lure us in.”

Yuan looked around and found that tree spirits were beginning to appear around them. These tree spirits were the same as the tree spirits that were attacking Liu Zhen’s group.

Besides these tree spirits, there were also Sprites surrounding them. They had fully encircled Zhao Hai’s group.

Yuan’s expression couldn’t help but change when he saw the surroundings. There were now more than 200 opponents surrounding them. And just like the ones attacking Liu Zhen’s team, Yuan and the others were being attacked by another team of 50 high-level Sprites. In terms of numbers alone, it was impossible for them to escape.

However, Yuan had experienced multiple life and death situations so he calmed down immediately. Then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, attack with all you have. We need to unite with Liu Zhen before planning what to do next.”

Zhao Hai nodded before letting loose a few spells. Then the group immediately started to move towards Liu Zhen.

Liu Zhen was also aware of the situation, so he made an effort to lead his troops to kill towards Zhao Hai and the others.

Meanwhile, it seems like the Sprites also wanted the two groups to meet. They didn’t spend any effort to stop the two from uniting. Before long, Yuan’s group and Liu Zhen’s group met.

Once the two groups united, the circle formation became larger. More Mages were placed in the center while the Warriors went to the front to defend. However, the Sprites didn’t make any moves. They just surrounded the group and stayed.

Liu Zheng looked at the situation outside before he said, “Brother Yuan, it seems like we brothers will be trapped here today. The Elves sent two Nascent Soul experts and also those that are at Core Formation. It will be very hard for us to leave with our lives. Haha.”

Yuan smiled bitterly and said, “It seems like these guys have been planning for this for a long time. I just don’t know if they planned to deal with the two of us together. But if they did, then this matter is more dangerous than we thought.”

Liu Zhen understood what Yuan meant. There’s no fixed schedule as to when a team would venture out to the core battlefield. Each action was up to each team leader. If the Sprites knew that both of them would appear, then the implications were too dangerous. This meant that someone from the Machine Field may have informed them.

Liu Zhen nodded before looking at the enemies surrounding them. The Sprites had yet to attack. This caused Liu Zheng to frown as he said, “What’s going on with them? Why don’t they attack?”

Yuan coldly snorted and said, “Who knows, maybe they’re just showing off.” And just as he said that, several Sprites flew towards Zhao Hai and the others.

These Sprites were wearing attractive full-body armor, this was especially true for the two Sprites in front. The Sprites weren’t very tall, so their armors looked more like decorations with their hollow patterns.

With their armors looking like decorations, one might see that these armors don’t provide much defensive capabilities. However, one shouldn’t rely on their common sense while they’re in the World of Cultivation. In this world, the appearance of an armor doesn’t necessarily translate to defensive strength. Being able to cover the entire body wasn’t as important as the materials and manufacturing method of the armor. Although the Sprite’s armor had hollow patterns carved into them, as long as they’re made of good materials and refined in a great way, then its defensive strength was certainly good.

The two Sprites looked quite old. Although their bodies were as youthful as the other Sprites, their eyes couldn’t betray their age.

One could sometimes see a person’s age through their eyes. A person who had lived through life couldn’t have eyes as pure as a child’s. Except, of course, if a person was mentally disabled.

Although the two Sprites looked very young, their facial expressions and eyes showed their wisdom and experiences. One could see from this that they were old.

The two Sprites led their group until they were 100 meters away from Zhao Hai and the others. One of the elder Sprites smiled coldly and said, “Liu Zhen, Yuan, I didn’t really expect that we would catch two big fishes at once. Hahaha. Both of your hands are filled with the blood of my brethren. It’s time for you to pay your debts.”

Yuan looked at the Sprite and then laughed, “Look who it is, so it’s the Old Wooden Sprite. What? You’re here to avenge your apprentices?”

As soon as the Sprite heard this, his face turned blue as he coldly snorted and said, “Yuan, you don’t have to sound proud. Do you really believe that you can escape today? I hear that you have attained diamond body. I want to see if the rumors are indeed true.”

But before Yuan could retaliate, a loud yawn was heard. This captured everyone’s attention. They all looked towards the source of the yawn – which was Zhao Hai. Seeing that everyone’s eyes were on him, Zhao Hai shrugged his shoulders before saying, “I don’t understand why you need to waste so much words before a fight. Do you really need to talk too much? Is this your way to feed your feeling of superiority? I don’t understand. I really don’t understand.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Xiong Li and the others laughed loudly. Then Li Kuangren said, “I reckon that they’re feeling inferior because of their height. They always use this method to show that they’re superior to us. Unfortunately, no matter what they do, they will always look like dolls to me.”

And even bigger laugh came from Xiong Li as he added, “Fourth Brother has a point. However, they don’t look like dolls to me. They look more like butterflies. I really want to catch a couple of them and place them in a cage. What do you think?”

Li Kuangren shook his head and said, “I don’t like raising such things. If I keep them in a cage, then I would need to feed them. Moreover, I would have to clean the cage. It’s a pain in the ass.”

This solicited a louder laughter from Xiong Li. Even the anxious Yuan couldn’t help but chuckle. In their opinion, if they really were to die today, then they might as well be like Li Kuangren irritating the Sprites as much as they could. And it seems to be working. The Sprites all had dark expressions on their faces.

The Sprites had indeed been insulted, especially the two elder Sprites. The two of them were well-known experts of the Six Realms Battlefield. But now, their faces were being slapped by some youngsters, so how could they bear it?

The Sprite who spoke before shouted, “Ignorant kid. I will let you die without a proper burial!”

Li Kuangren laughed and said, “Old fogey, if I don’t insult you, then would you give me a proper burial? If you want to fight, then let’s fight. If you don’t want to fight, then unfortunately, I don’t have the energy to grind teeth with you here.”

The Sprite couldn’t bear the insults anymore, so he shouted, “Kid, you’re courting death!” Then he waved his hand as a tree spirit appeared in front of the team. Then the spirit proceeded to punch towards Li Kuangren.

Li Kuangren roared as he took out his axe. When the axe appeared, it instantly enlarged and chopped towards the tree spirit.

However, the axe was later deflected. Li Kuangren harrumphed. It was clear that he had suffered a loss in this clash.

The tree spirit didn’t stop its attack as it continued to punch towards Li Kuangren. But at this time, Xiong Li took out his chained hammers and pounded towards the tree spirit. However, the tree spirit ignored it as its attack continued on.

Bang, bang. Xiong Li’s chained hammers hit the body of the tree spirit. But the tree spirit remained unaffected, its fist was still headed towards its target. At this time, Lu Dingtian, Dongfang Yu, and Sun fei made their move. It must be said that their weapons were like the weapons from the Cultivation realm. These weapons could fly out and hit their enemies and also had the ability to enlarge and shrink. After the group continually attacked, the tree spirit could no longer stop them and was forced to head back.

The clash between the two sides occured in a blink of an eye. This time, without Zhao Hai’s support, the brothers were able to move together and drive back a spirit of a Nascent Soul Sprite. This was an extraordinary feat.

In addition to their new Cultivation Methods, Li Kuangren and the others’ weapons also played a vital role in this clash. Their weapons were all manufactured by Zhao Hai and contained the weapon shattering formation. This caused their attacks to be much more powerful than before. If it weren’t for the weapon shattering formation, they wouldn’t have driven the tree spirit back.

Although the tree spirit was driven back, this didn’t mean that it was injured. However, this was enough to make Yuan and the others startled. Yuan didn’t expect that Zhao Hai’s brothers would also be formidable. One must know that a Nascent Soul Sprite’s spirit wasn’t just a normal puppet.

At the same time, the elder Sprite didn’t expect Li Kuangren and the others to be this strong. What surprised him the most were the weapons used by Li Kuangren and the others. The weapons were actually the same kinds as the ones used in the Cultivation Realm.

“Has the Machine Field mastered how to use the Cultivation Realm’s magic artifacts?” The elder Sprite couldn’t help but think this. The reason why he said that the Machine Field has mastered the use of using the Cultivation Realm’s artifacts instead of saying that the Machine Field has learned to make magic artifacts was because creating the Cultivation Realms magic artifacts wasn’t actually that difficult. Besides the formation core as well as the formations that would be added by specific artisans, the Machine Field has all the means to create magic artifacts. So it wouldn’t be surprising for the Machine Field to make magic artifacts of the Cultivation Realm.

On the other hand, the method to control magic artifacts was a very difficult thing to learn. Methods to control magic artifacts in the Cultivation Realm were tied up with someone’s cultivation method. Without a cultivation method, then one wouldn’t be able to control a magic artifact. This was also the reason why close to nobody in the Machine Field used magic artifacts.

Also, cultivation methods weren’t uncommon in the Machine Field. When Yuan arrived in the Machine Field, he brought with him a lot of cultivation methods. However, the reason why these methods couldn’t propagate in the Machine Field was because of spiritual density and lack of medicine.

The spiritual density in the Machine Field was much less compared to the Cultivation Realm. The Cultivation Realm’s cultivation methods relied on this high spiritual density in order to progress. Even ordinary places in the Cultivation Realm couldn’t support these Cultivation Methods. One would need to be close to a spiritual vein to progress. Moreover, in order to gain further results, a Cultivator would need the support of pills. And since these things were very rare in the Machine Field, the use of cultivation methods didn’t become popular in the realm. And without the means to practice the Cultivation Realm’s methods, magic artifacts in the Machine Field were useless. This is why nobody used magic artifacts in the Machine Field.

Chapter 1288: Conflict Escalation

The Six Realms Battlefield had great spiritual density and was a good place for cultivation. However, the Machine Field couldn’t send people to cultivate here for a long time. This was because the Six Realm Battlefield was too dangerous. There weren’t many people like Yuan who stayed here for six or seven years that were alive and capable.

And even if the Machine Field sent a lot of people into the Battlefield, the other realms wouldn’t allow it. The other realms understood that the Machine Field’s biggest weakness was their individual fighting skill as well as their progression.

If the other realms let the Machine Field increase their fighting strength, then in addition to their battleships, even the Cultivation Realm would have a hard time dealing with them.

Because they knew about this, the other realms couldn’t allow the Machine Field to send a large number of people to the Six Realms Battlefield for cultivation. But at the same time, the other realms couldn’t send a lot of their own people to the battlefield. Although the spiritual density in the battlefield was great, it wasn’t a giant improvement compared to spiritual veins. In this case, these people would just cultivate in their own sects. Additionally, danger was everywhere in the battlefield and the casualty rate was high. Therefore, people consider this place as a place for honing their skills, not a place for cultivation.

It was for this reason that the people from the Machine Field had never used magic artifacts. Even if they had cultivation methods from the Cultivation Realm, they would rarely practice it. Everyone would still learn the Mage and Warrior paths because it required less spiritual qi.

The reason why Xiong Li and the others were able to learn the Cultivation Realm’s methods was because they have only been in the Machine Field for four years. Because they hadn’t been in the Machine Field for long, they weren’t too tied up by the Machine Field’s methods. At the same time, Zhao Hai gave them potions to practice with. It can be said that Xiong Li and the others were able to circumvent the need for spiritual qi because of these potions. This allowed them to gain enough strength to contend with the old Sprite’s spirit.

The Sprite gawked, his face turning uglier. He was a Nascent Soul Expert. However, five Machine Field juniors managed to drive him back. This was humiliation he couldn’t endure.

However, the Sprite didn’t make another move. He knew that attacking Li Kuangren and the others once more wouldn’t do anything. So he waved his hand and led the other Sprites back to the tree spirits. Then he ordered the tree spirits to attack.

It must be said that the attacks of these tree spirits weren’t very good. Otherwise, Liu Zhen and the others wouldn’t have lasted for so long. These tree spirits were spirits that possessed the trees of the Six Realms Battlefield. Being made out of common material affected their compatibility.

But this common nature also supplied the Sprites with endless supply of tree spirits. There was already a large pile of tree spirits that had been killed by people from the Machine Field.

While the fight was happening, Zhao Hai didn’t make any impactful action. Although he sent a spell or two out, those who understood him knew that he wasn’t fighting at full power.

Yuan and the others might have an idea on Zhao Hai’s strength, but Liu Zhen’s group was completely clueless. Liu Zhen and the others thought that Zhao Hai was as strong as Li Kuangren and the others. Therefore, they were fighting as though they were prepared to die in battle. Every single one of them were going all out.

Zhao Hai didn’t fight at full power because he wanted Xiong Li and the others to fight more. This would allow them to get used to their weapons and techniques more.

The tree spirits’ attacking patterns weren’t hard to deal with, so Xiong Li and the others wouldn’t be in any immediate danger. These tree spirits were suitable for their training. Because of this, the two sides were at a deadlock for some time. Zhao Hai was also holding back because he was guarding against the Sprites. The Sprites were using basic spirits for the fight. Just earlier, the Nascent Soul Sprite only used a basic spirit to battle with Li Kuangren and the others to a standstill. This showed how much power each Sprite had. This was especially true once they used their life source spirit. Seeing that the Sprites were using basic spirits only meant that they were waiting for an opportunity. Once an opportunity emerges, then these Sprites would send their life source spirits to deal the final blow.

When two armies fought, the victor would often be the one with more numbers. This principle could also be applied here. Those with a larger number would most likely win the battle.

The battle between both sides continued on for an hour. A lot of tree spirits fell but they were quickly replaced by newer tree spirits. This caused Yuan and the others to have a difficult time.

Zhao Hai had also increased his speed in releasing magic formations, and his frown grew deeper and deeper. These Sprites were summoning tree spirit with no effort at all. They would just wave their hand and a nearby tree would come to life. Such methods were really surprising for Zhao Hai.

Moreover, Sprites were said to be able to communicate with everything. There were so many trees here making the Sprite’s resources inexhaustible. And even if the trees run out, the Sprites could still use the earth, the wind, and everything else.

Looking at the growing number of tree spirits surrounding them, Zhao Hai knew that things couldn’t go on like this. If things continue as is, then they would begin to suffer casualties. When he thought of this, Zhao Hai waved his hand and released a large number of Undead in front of him. Then he commanded the Undead to attack the tree spirits.

These Undead had already learned the cultivation methods of the Cultivation Realm. Although the time they cultivated was short, their combat power was still greater compared to the tree spirits. As soon as the Undead entered the battle, the numerical advantage of the tree spirits vanished. Their attacks were blocked by Zhao Hai.

Yuan felt the pressure on him becoming light. Then he noticed that the tree spirits were being blocked by Zhao Hai’s Undead.

When Yuan saw this, he couldn’t help but stare. Then he shook his long sledgehammer as he looked at the Undead battling the tree spirits. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have this many Undead.

Xiong Li and the others also began to relax as they went beside Zhao Hai. Xiong Li patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said, “You finally made a move. For a moment there I thought I would be overwhelmed.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he pointed towards Sprites who were stunned, then he said, “Now let’s see what they would do. These Sprites certainly have other methods.”

Then just as Zhao Hai said that, a person from the Machine Field suddenly cried out pitifully before falling. Zhao Hai stared before his expression changed. Then he waved his hand and released a 1000-layer formation. He sent the attack towards a certain direction. There wasn’t anything in that direction, only air. This caused Xiong Li and the others to be confused.

But at this moment, where there was nothing before, a distortion appeared. Then a transparent character appeared, blocking Zhao Hai’s attack.

It was also at this time that people discovered a wind spirit. The person from the Machine Field fell under this wind spirit’s hand.

Moreover, this was a Sprite’s life source spirit. Therefore, it’s quite strong. If it weren’t for Zhao Hai’s early discovery, then more people from the Machine Field would have been killed.

After the wind spirit blocked Zhao Hai’s blow, its body flickered and disappeared again. Not only could this wind spirit hide from view, it could also block spiritual force from detecting it. Sneak attacks were certainly its strong point.

However, this wind spirit had met its match. Zhao Hai didn’t notice it before so it was able to kill someone. But now that Zhao Hai had noticed its existence, it had already been tagged by the Space. It was already impossible for this wind spirit to sneak attack.

Zhao Hai threw spells one after another, causing the wind spirit to block them all and stopping its attack.

After clashing with Zhao Hai’s spells multiple times, the wind spirit finally knew that it couldn’t escape Zhao Hai’s attacks. The wind spirit materialized and then waved its hand. This caused wind spirits to appear around Zhao Hai and the others to attack them.

These wind spirits weren’t as formidable as the life source spirit. However, they still had their basic capabilities such as transformation and stealth.

Seeing this, Zhao Hai had to command the Undead to protect his people and also attack the approaching wind spirits. At the same time, Yuan and the others resumed their attacks.

These newly made wind spirits didn’t have the ability to block spiritual force detection. This allowed Yuan and the others to detect them and launch a counter-attack.

The Sprites also resumed their attacks. They began to make a large number of tree spirits to reinforce the wind spirits. Additionally, they also summoned earth spirits. But besides that life source wind spirit, the others kept their life source spirits from making a move.

Seeing the Sprites summon more and more spirits, Zhao Hai would naturally be impolite as he also released more Undead. Both sides launched a full-scale war in the surrounding forested region. Moreover, the scale of the battles became bigger and bigger as more Undead, tree spirits, wind spirits, and earth spirits were being summoned. The situation was escalating as time went by.

At this moment, Zhao Hai as well as the Sprites discovered that the battle had gone out of control. They made such a huge move that it’s certain that they have alarmed the other people in the core battlefield. And both sides don’t have any spare energy to deal with these people.

Now, in the surrounding area, people from the other realms were beginning to congregate. This wasn’t good for the Sprites and Machine Field. If they kept fighting like this, then they would be picked off by the others with very little effort.

Chapter 1289: Golden Battle Beasts

There were no good people in the Six Realms Battlefield. And it was very hard to see cheap hunts in the core battlefield. If Zhao Hai and the others continued fighting with the Sprites, then it’s certain that the spectators would never let them off.

The Sprites were no fools as well. They were also aware of their present situation. The Sprites dispatched their team in order to kill Liu Zhen. They would only deal with Liu Zhen and nothing else. Yuan coming over was just a bonus. In the eyes of the Sprites, Yuan being here was a good opportunity.

Buddhist Warrior Yuan, Eight-star Li Zhen, these were two people that other realms dreaded. If one of these people were to die, then the Machine Field would suffer a huge blow.

Fifty people versus 200, to the Sprites this was an assured task. Even if they don’t use their life source spirits, they could still achieve success with no effort.

However, they didn’t expect that there was a remarkable person in the Machine Field’s party. Although the Sprites were summoning endless amounts of tree spirits, they were still blocked by the Undead. Besides that one person that fell in the hands of the wind spirit, the others from the Machine Field were very well defended.

Now that there were so many people spectating, the Sprites knew that if they don’t deal with Zhao Hai soon, then things would become more troublesome.

The lead Sprite turned his head and said, “Gaitt, let everyone fight.. Only when we deal with Yuan and the others will we be safe. We have 200 people. As long as we don’t suffer a lot of losses, those fellows outside wouldn’t dare make a move on us.”

There were almost no battalions in the Six Realms Battlefield. At most, teams would consist of 100 people. Teams with 200 people like the Sprites were very rare.

Also, the people from the other realms who were spectating weren’t a lot. Otherwise, they would have already made a move against the Sprites.

The Sprite called Gaitt understood what the lead Sprite said. It was time for them to use their life source spirits. Gaitt immediately sent the order for all the Sprites to let their life source spirits out.

The life source spirits were released and they immediately attacked towards Zhao Hai and the others. Zhao Hai was also paying attention to the moves made by the Sprites. Upon seeing them make a move, he would naturally be impolite. He released another large batch of Undead and he also took his Liquid Silver out. Then Zhao Hai waved his staff and released 12 giant golden beasts.

Each of these golden beasts towered at ten meters high. They were the beasts of the original golden combat suits. These twelve zodiac beasts were strong, but they had been inside Zhao Hai’s staff for a long time. And Zhao Hai judged that now was the correct time to use them.

Once these giant battle beasts were released, all of them roared to life. Zhao Hai waved his hand, sending them towards the Sprites. At the same time, Zhao Hai stopped in front of two tree spirits. These two tree spirits were the life source spirits of the two strongest Sprites present. Both were equivalent to Nascent Soul Experts.

After blocking the two tree spirits from moving, Zhao Hai released a 10,000-layer formation to attack them.

Although these two tree spirits looked like they were dumb, their wisdom wasn’t actually low. Moreover, these two were very well coordinated with each other. One of them threw a punch to scatter Zhao Hai’s magic while the other transformed its arm into a wooden net to pull Zhao Hai in. Zhao Hai released another 10,000-layer formation to block the two spirits’ attack.

Because of the Undead, the Sprites still weren’t able to get to Yuan and the others despite releasing a lot of life source spirits. They had no way to proceed. The combat power of the twelve battle beasts were also very extraordinary. The most horrifying thing about these beasts was that they can transform into any kind of beast, allowing them an endless amount of fighting patterns. There were already several life source spirits that were injured by these beasts.

When the Sprites discovered that they still couldn’t get to Yuan and the others despite releasing their life source spirits, they couldn’t help but be shocked. In their minds, as long as they released their life source spirits, then things will be finished in no time. They also didn’t expect the two Nascent Soul life source spirits to be blocked by one person.

And after seeing that several life source spirits were injured, the Sprites finally understood that they wouldn’t be having a great day today.

The lead Sprite looked at Zhao Hai with hatred in his eyes. He knew that the Sprites had already failed their mission. And this failure was because of Zhao Hai. All of the Undead who blocked the tree spirits were all from Zhao Hai. All these golden beasts taking down life source spirits were also from Zhao Hai. And Zhao Hai himself blocked two Nascent Soul life source spirits. He alone made the attack of the Sprites useless. In the elder Sprite’s eyes, Zhao Hai was extremely hateful.

However, they couldn’t do anything to Zhao Hai. Gazes alone couldn’t kill anyone. And since their life source spirits were being blocked by Zhao Hai, they were in a stalemate.

There were more and more people who gathered around the battle. These people were from all the other realms. The Sprites felt that they were standing in the middle of a wolf pack.

At this time, a roar was heard from outside the battlefield. Then a small group rushed towards the Sprites. This group wasn’t very large at only 50 people. And it can be seen that these people were all from the Machine Field. These people came here to see the fight and were hoping to pick up some cheap harvests. But after finding that it was Yuan and the others, they immediately rushed in to rescue.

The sight of this team cemented to the Sprites the idea that it was already impossible to deal with Yuan and the others today. If these people appeared, then more people from the Machine Field would come soon. Although the Sprites had surrounded Yuan and the others, they weren’t in any commanding position at all. Yuan and the others were blocking the attacks very well. It would be very hard to break through their defense in a short time.

The old Sprite’s expression turned ugly. However, he loudly said, “Withdraw. We could no longer deal with them.”

The other Sprites were also looking at Zhao Hai with ruthlessness. Then they took back their life source spirits before forming squads and leaving.

But even if the Sprites left, the tree spirits were still assaulting Zhao Hai and the others. They even attacked the approaching people from the Machine Field. Naturally, these tree spirits were set up by the Sprites to tie Zhao Hai and the others down, allowing them safe retreat from the battle.

Zhao Hai didn’t think of pursuing them. Although the Sprites had retreated, their safety wasn’t completely assured. There were still wolves around them.

The Sprites had great fighting ability, other realms wouldn’t easily attack them. However, nobody could say if this still bodes true when motivation exists.

Fortunately, after the Sprites retreated, the tree spirits quickly lost their power and were quickly dealt with by the Undead. No additional casualties appeared among the Machine Field’s people. The additional 50 people were also fine.

Before long, the two groups converged. Zhao Hai didn’t say anything and just took out several bottles of potions and distributed them to everyone. Nobody held back and immediately took the potion without even knowing what it was.

After everyone drank the potions, Zhao Hai looked at the people surrounding them. Some have already left while the others had yet to make a move.

These people also saw the fight between Machine Field and the Sprites. They couldn’t help admit that they weren’t as strong as the Sprites. If they tried to make a move on Zhao Hai and the others, then they wouldn’t be able to win.

Since they can’t be sure, then they wouldn’t attack. It also needed to be said that two lunatics from the Machine Field were present, Buddhist Warrior Yuan and Eight-star Liu Zhen. These two had already proven that they couldn’t be easily dealt with.

Yuan and Liu Zhen had already been known as lunatics in the Six Realms Battlefield. They weren’t people one could easily fight against. This was especially true for Yuan. People had tried multiple times to kill him but they inevitably failed.

After the group drank their potions, Yuan and Liu Zheng went to Zhao Hai’s side. Yuan looked at Zhao Hai with shining eyes as he laughed and said, “Good, Little Hai, good job! I didn’t really expect that you would have such a powerful Undead. It seems like you’ve been busy slaughtering people.”

Zhao Hai just chuckled and replied, “If it weren’t for these Undead, then how could we get the top 6 in the elimination round? To tell you the truth, we relied on these Undead to kill the bugs back in Fabio Planet.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Yuan laughed once more. Meanwhile, Liu Zhen looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, this Liu Zhen owes you one. If you need anything in the future, then don’t hesitate to come to my place. I’ll try my best to help.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and expressed his gratitude.

Yuan looked at the people slowly retreating as he coldly snorted and said, “These bastards, they only came here to get cheap rewards. They aren’t afraid of breaking their teeth. This Yuan was just about to teach them a lesson.”

Liu Zhen smiled and said, “Old Yuan, don’t brag too much. You just saw Little Hai’s strength and you want to fight again? I think you should just forget it. Those Sprites wouldn’t just let us off that easily.”

Yuan nodded and said, “The Sprites really wanted to deal with the both of us at the same time. It seems like it has been a long time since I beat them up. Their skins must be getting itchy.”

Liu Zhen nodded, “We should retaliate, but depending on our present state I’m afraid that would be difficult. Let’s just head back and think about ways to deal with the Sprites.”

Yuan shook his head and said, “I’m not too anxious about dealing with the Sprites. I still have something left to do. Hao Donglai just tried to steal our thornweeds. I must go to the Demon territory to vent some anger before heading back.”

Chapter 1290: Tunnel

When Liu Zhen heard Yuan, he couldn’t help but gawk. Then he said, “Hao Donglai? You met that Old Mouse? And he dared to go into our territory to steal? His guts are surely big.”

Yuan smiled and said, “Rest assured, Little Hai has already killed that mouse and turned him into Undead. In fact, it was Old Mouse Hao’s subordinate who discovered you being attacked.” Liu Zhen nodded. He wasn’t startled that Zhao Hai was able to kill Hao Donglai. If Zhao Hai could block two Nascent Soul Experts, then killing a Core Formation Demon Mouse wasn’t anything surprising.

Liu Zhen was also a bold and courageous person. When he heard Yuan, he thought for a while before saying, “Since we have nearly 100 people here, then we should go visit the Demons and make some noise. Let’s return the favor.”

Yuan nodded and said, “That is also good. I wouldn’t have dared to go too far before this, but now that we have Little Hai we can finally be noisy.”

Although they looked like formidable elders, Yuan and Liu Zhen actually had hearts of fiery youths. After resting for some time, the group left towards the Demon Race’s territory.

Yuan was still being extra careful along the way. Although they knew that Zhao Hai was strong, they knew that one couldn’t be careless in the Six Realms Battlefield. Yuan and Liu Zhen were famous characters from the Machine Field. People from the other realms couldn’t wait to eat them up. And if there was a chance to get rid of the two of them at the same time, then that would be best.

Although there weren’t any battalion-sized troops in the Six Realms Battlefield, it wasn’t impossible for a battalion-sized army to be mobilized just to get rid of the two. Yuan and Liu Zhen were also cautious people, otherwise they wouldn’t have survived this long in the Six Realms Battlefield. Yuan was famed for being unafraid of death, but he would still give himself a chance to escape whenever he fought. It was said that Yuan went into deadly battles without any fear of dying, but in reality he would only fight such battles if he was sure that he would survive.

There were experts everywhere in the Six Realms Battlefield. Core Formation experts were as common as dogs in a city. Yuan was also at Core Formation-level, not Nascent Soul. If he really didn’t care about his life and only knew how to fight, then he would have already died a long long time ago.

Liu Zhen was also the same. The two were the kinds of people who planned before making a move. And whenever they decided to move, they would go all out. Bit by bit, this strategy earned them their nicknames in the Six Realms Battlefield. And this also made the other realms stop underestimating the Machine Field.

Lu Zhen’s weapon was a long blade engraved with 1000 offensive formations, making its strength extraordinary. On the other hand, Yuan had a long hammer that was extremely heavy. The weapon was engraved with 1200 formations, making its might not any less than the Cultivation Realm’s magic artifacts. Although they couldn’t control their weapons to fly, their sword qi could reach 100 miles. Moreover, their attacks were very strong.

The Six Realms Battlefield was very rich in resources. Because of this, the Machine Field also invested heavily in their holdings in this subspace. All the weapons used by their practitioners here would surely be the best.

The same was true for the other realms. Everyone was willing to invest in the Six Realms Battlefield because the resources inside it were just too valuable. And the more you invest, the more profits you would gain. If you equip yourself well, then you can rob others. Because of this, no realm chose to be stingy when it came to the battlefield.

However, there were some exceptions to this and that was the Demon Realm. Because they were extremely diverse, they had difficulties in refining weapons for each other. But they still had their own methods. Once they develop intelligence, they would choose a body part and refine it into their own artifact. It was like the Sprite’s life source spirit but instead of their soul the Demons used their body parts. The strength of these artifacts could contend with a life source weapon of a Cultivator, it was even possible for it to be stronger. After all, the weapon was a part of the Demon’s body. Demons generally call this specially trained body part as their Origin Weapon.

Hao Donglai also had his own origin weapon and that was his front claws. Almost all Mouse Demons make their claws as their origin weapons. Since Mouse Demons use their claws to dig the earth, then they would need sharp claws. Therefore, making their front claws as their origin weapons was a natural move.

Because of this, whenever someone from the Machine Field like Yuan kills a Demon, they would send its corpse back to the Machine Field. And then the Machine Field will process the Demon’s parts to make weapons and armor.

The Demon Race was composed of different types of races whose true bodies were animals and plants. And because of their long period of Cultivation, weapons and armor made from their body parts were very high-grade items.

However, there was a rule in the Six Realms Battlefield. Not only would your merit be recorded when you kill an enemy, all things from the one you killed will belong to you. Therefore, when Hao Donglai and his team were turned into Undead by Zhao Hai, Yuan and the others didn’t say anything.

The group slowly moved forward. Even if they ran into people from the other realms, Yuan didn’t make a move in fear of alarming the Demons. Because of this, the group took four days to arrive at the area that was partially controlled by the Demon Realm.

Since this place could be considered to be the land of the Demons, Yuan became even more careful. Yuan had come here before so he knew the surroundings well. Instead of attacking the Demons immediately, the group found a place in order to rest well.

The place that Yuan found was actually a tunnel. It was so covertly placed that most people wouldn’t notice it. Moreover, there were no important resources around it.

The tunnel was quite spacious. Moreover, it was very dry and clean, causing Zhao Hai to be surprised. Upon sizing the tunnel up, Zhao Hai turned his head to Yuan and said, “Captain, did you discover this place? It’s very good.”

Yuan smiled and said, “I once led a team to hunt in the Demon territory. At that time, we were met with trouble causing most of my team to be killed. After being pursued all over the place, I was able to discover this tunnel. Not only was this place hidden, its walls could also block spiritual force.” Zhao Hai nodded. He also tried to scan the place using his spiritual force before and discovered the tunnel’s ability to block any spiritual force scans.

Zhao Hai carefully investigated the tunnel and couldn’t find any traces of artificial excavation. In other words, this tunnel was created naturally, making it even more unusual.

While walking through the tunnel, Zhao Hai collected some stones and then sent them to the Space. Upon entering, the Space issued a prompt saying that the stone can block spiritual force. And that more of these stones were being added to the Space.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t happy about this. The stranger this place was, the more formidable the creator of the Six Realms Battlefield would be. For Zhao Hai, this wasn’t good news.

Naturally, Zhao Hai’s actions were seen by Yuan. Feeling confused about what Zhao Hai was doing, Yuan asked Xiong Li, “What is Little Hai planning to do with those stones?”

Xiong Li smiled and said, “Little Hai likes to research things. He’s a very strong refiner. The weapons we use were all made by Little Hai.”

When Xiong Li mentioned this matter, Yuan began to remember something. Then he looked at Xiong Li and said, “Now that I think about it, your weapons look like those used by the Cultivation Realm. So are you also practicing cultivation methods?”

Xiong Li smiled and said, “All of this is because of Little Hai. In addition to our weapons, Little Hai also gave us our cultivation methods. Back when we attended the Six Realms Beginner Competition, Little Hai killed some Cultivators to snatch their cultivation methods. This allowed us to cultivate those methods.”

Yuan frowned and said, “That’s not right. Cultivation methods of the Cultivation Realm are sealed inside jade slips. If one breaks those seals forcefully, then the information inside the jade slip will be erased. How did Little Hai get those methods?”

Xiong Li shrugged his shoulder and said, “Who knows, Little Hai has a lot of skills. You’ll get used to it soon. Right, Captain, you’re using an ordinary Machine Field weapon. If there’s some time, you can ask Little Hai to refine your weapon. I can guarantee that Little Hai could make your weapon easier to use and more powerful.”

Yuan looked at Xiong Li in confusion. Then Xiong Li just smiled as he took out his chained hammers. This pair of chain hammers weren’t the ones he was using. Their hammers were the ones given to him by his family. He handed the hammers over to Yuan and said, “Captain, look at this. This is the weapon I used before. It’s a pure Machine Field Weapon. It might not be equal to the Cultivation Realm’s weapons, but its strength will certainly surprise you.”

Yuan received the chained hammers and felt their weight in his hands. Then he used them to strike the ground. The ground of this tunnel was very special, even Yuan’s strength couldn’t do anything to it. However, when the hammers hit the ground, the earth shattered immediately.

The stone didn’t even splinter and directly turned into dust. A casual swing of these hammers caused an area of about a square meter to turn into sand.

Yuan as well as the nearby people from the Machine Field were startled. They didn’t expect Xiong Li’s weapon to be this strong.

One must know that Yuan’s weapons were refined in a way that would increase the range of their sword qi. As for close combat, they could only be used like ordinary weapons. If such weapons were also tailored for close combat, then the Machine Field’s Warriors would increase their combat prowess by about three layers.

Every person in this tunnel was a true elite from the Machine Field. They knew clearly well what this type of weapon could do. In an instant, everyone’s eyes focused on the weapon on Yuan’s hands.

Yuan raised the weapons and tried to inspect it. However, since he wasn’t an expert in refining, he wasn’t able to understand anything about it. So he turned his head to Xiong Li and said, “This is the weapon that Little Hai refined for you?”

Xiong Li nodded and said, “Right, Little Hai helped us to refine it. Actually, there’s nothing else special about this weapon besides the addition of a magic formation. Little Hai added the weapon shattering formation that mechs generally use.”

Yuan stared, “Weapon shattering formation? Those formations used by Mechs and Battleship? But I heard that it couldn’t be used in weapons?”

Xiong Li smiled and said, “This is Little Hai’s skill.”

At this time, Zhao Hai walked over towards Xiong Li and Yuan. Naturally, he was able to hear their conversation. In any case, Zhao Hai wasn’t planning to hide this information for long. After all, these weapons would have a direct impact to the strength of the Machine Field. He didn’t intend to take this secret to his grave.

Seeing Zhao Hai walking over, Yuan immediately said, “Little Hai, can you help us refine our weapons? If we have weapon shattering, then our strength will definitely increase.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “That’s not a problem. I’ll help you refine them after we head back. Actually adding weapon shattering to weapons isn’t that difficult, it could even be mass produced by the Machine Field. However, even if I only made a small modification to the formation, its specific arrangement is very important. If it isn’t arranged properly, then even if it could increase a weapon’s power, it would also reduce the weapon’s lifespan. And because everyone used different weapons, mass production of this formation hasn’t been ideal.”

Yuan nodded and said, “We don’t need it to be mass produced. After returning, we’ll hand our weapons over to you. No wonder Xiong Li and the others were able to face the spirit of a Nascent Soul Expert. Xiong Li and the others are clearly Foundation Establishment-level. With their strength, not to say five, even ten people wouldn’t be able to contend with a Nascent Soul Expert. It seems like their weapons contributed a lot to their strength.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he smiled and said, “Right, this formation is very useful in fights. I’ll find time to refine your weapons when we head back. If others want their weapons refined as well, they can just look for me. No matter what, we’re all allies. I’m more than happy to help everyone.”

Yuan didn’t say anything else and just patted ZhaoHai’s shoulder. Then he turned to everyone and said, “Alright, let’s take a rest for two hours before making trouble with the Demons.” Everyone simultaneously nodded. But this time, the way they looked at Zhao Hai has changed. It was now filled with admiration.

Chapter 1291: Ironwood Demon and Blood Gold Mine

In the Six Realms Battlefield, people admire those who have strength. However, this property only benefited the strong person and not others. If you were strong, then you would be able to kill more enemies and in turn gain more spoils. All of these achievements would be yours and wouldn’t benefit others. Therefore, in addition to admiration, people would also feel envy. They wouldn’t necessarily treat you as one of them.

However, a good crafting master that could make great weapons and wasn’t stingy in helping others was something that everyone wanted to be in a good relationship with. Zhao Hai’s refined weapons could improve their survivability in the battlefield.

Weapons and armor were a fighter’s second life, this was something that everyone knew. At this moment, the people from the Machine Field were inferior compared to the Cultivation Realm. One of the reasons for this was because their weapons were inferior.

Although it was said that when confronting the enemy one shouldn’t let go of their weapons, people from the Cultivation Realm were able to let go of their weapons and have them attack by themselves. Moreover, one person can operate several weapons at the same time.

However, the people from the Machine Field didn’t share this advantage. Even if the Warriors could release sword qi, the close combat capabilities of their weapons were still worse than the Cultivators. Most importantly, since they only have two hands, Warriors could only operate two weapons at most.

Xiong Li’s hammers have the weapon shattering formation engraved in them. People from great families weren’t clueless about the weapon shattering formation. This was a formation specially used by Mechs and Battleships mainly to pierce armor. This armor piercing ability was used to deal with other Mechs and Battleships. After all, internal conflicts were still present within the Machine Field, and there were also the space pirates. Mech battles and Battleship engagements caused people to research ways to deal with their enemies much more easily. The result of this research was the weapon shattering formation. The ability of this formation to pierce everything was first-class. It was just a pity that it couldn’t be used in weapons used by Warriors.

Although there were plenty of magic formations inside Warrior weapons, their general attack was very monotonous. To be honest, Warriors in the Machine Field were quite similar to Sword Cultivators. Sword Cultivators focus on the sword to break ten thousand obstacles. Meanwhile, Warriors also focus on destroying ten thousand obstructions, but they don’t have the appropriate weapon to do so.

Therefore, among all other realms, the Warriors from the Machine Field had the most intense desire to get their hands on a good weapon. And Xiong Li’s hammers were the definition of a good weapon.

Because of this, the position of Zhao Hai in everyone’s heart had increased. Everyone wanted to be on good terms with him and flatter him. How intense their feelings about this was something that Zhao Hai didn’t expect.

After resting for two hours in the tunnel, Yuan gathered the group and then took out a map. This map showed the partially controlled territory of the Demon Race. This map was something that Yuan would never give to others.

Yuan pointed at a position on the map and said, “We’re not far from this area. This is a special place for the Demons, the Ironwood Demon Forest!”

Upon hearing the words Ironwood Demon Forest, everyone couldn’t help but suck in a cold breath. This was because Ironwood Demons were famous Demons. The original body of these Demons was the Ironwood Tree. These trees were slow-growing but had bodies that were as strong as steel. Even their saplings were as firm as fine steel. These saplings were also heavy and might even be mistaken as weapons.

Despite these great qualities, Ironwood Trees had very high chances to become Demons. Moreover, after becoming Demons, their fighting strength wasn’t something to scoff at. They were the main strength of the Demon Race.

Liu Zhen looked at Yuan and said, “Old Yuan, are you sure you want to face those Ironwood Demons? From what I heard, that forest has several Nascent Soul Demons. Although Little Hai is strong, it’s not good for us to go there.”

Yuan smiled and said, “I’m not planning to go there, I’m not that crazy yet. Those Ironwood Demons are strong. After all, they’re the main fighting force of the Demon Realm. Going to that forest will just be courting death. Moreover, moving the Ironwood Demons will bring trouble to the Machine Field. The gains don’t justify the trouble.”

Everyone laughed and agreed. This Ironwood Demon Forest was very famous in the Six Realm’s Battlefield. It was originally a hill with rich spiritual qi. Afterwards, Ironwood Demons began grouping up there before it slowly formed into a forest.

The influence of the Ironwood Demons was very strong, it even extends to the World of Cultivation. Therefore, nobody easily provoked them. And as time went by, the Ironwood Demons became stronger and stronger.

Yuan continued, “We’re not going to the Ironwood Demon Forest. We’re going here.” Then he pointed towards a place not far from the Ironwood Demon Forest. It’s one of the rare barren mountains in the Six Realms Battlefield.

However, this barren mountain was also famous in the battlefield. This was because this barren mountain produces soft gold. Soft gold was a malleable metal with strong metal-element energy. Moreover, it can be melted at a very low temperature, making it a good material to fuse with other metals as it could also increase the metal element in other metals. It’s an excellent resource for crafting.

A place like this was strictly controlled by the Demons. And they would make sure that the other realms couldn’t take advantage of it. However, because soft gold was very easy to use, it was impossible for the Demons to completely take control of the mountain.

Originally, the Demon Realm had a garrison on this mountain. However, the other realms united and harassed it for the soft gold. In the end, after the Demons suffered serious casualties, they withdrew the garrison, giving the other realms the opportunity to mine the resource.

Of course, the Demons wouldn’t just let the other realms mine in peace. It can be said that the soft gold mine was one of the places where people die the most in the Six Realms Battlefield. This also gave soft gold the name Blood Gold.

With the Ironwood Demon Forest close by, it can be said that the Demons were making the Ironwood Demons take care of the soft gold mine. Relatively speaking, the Demons still have the majority of the mined soft gold.

The Demons have the majority, but this didn’t mean that they had complete control over the mine. One could imagine the chaos in this mine. The region was seen as the best turbid water to catch small fish. Naturally, this place was teeming with sharks hungry for prey.

At first when Yuan pointed towards the mine, everyone gawked. Then after some time they laughed. Then Liu Zhen said, “Yuan, you’re really cunning. Good, the soft gold mine is a good choice. Although there are a lot of Demon Experts in that place, powerful experts are very rare. I heard that the realms had reached an agreement to not send powerful experts in that place. The strongest person allowed should be a Nascent Soul Expert, and those Nascent Soul Experts act alone. With Little Hai’s protection, we can guarantee our lives. Also, the mining tunnels stretch in all directions. Even if we don’t win, at least we can retreat easily.”

Yuan nodded and said, “Exactly. We can go there to bring trouble. Not only can we deal with the Demons, we might even be able to take some soft gold back. And since Little Hai can refine weapons for us, we can exchange his services for soft gold. After all, we cannot make Little Hai work for nothing.” After Yuan said that, everyone laughed. Then they looked at Zhao Hai and teased him for a bit. Zhao Hai chatted with everyone for some time, making the atmosphere very warm.

After some time, everyone stopped talking. Then Yuan said, “Although we don’t have to worry much, we still need to be careful. After all, the soft gold mine isn’t far from the Ironwood Demon Forest. If those Ironwood Demons discover that something isn’t right, then we will be unlucky.”

Everyone nodded. Zhao Hai looked at everyone and thought for a moment before he said, “Everyone, back in the competition, I was able to get some good loot. Let me share it with you all.” Then he waved his hand and took out a pile of things. This pile consists of walnut-sized pale orbs. They weren’t very good looking.

However, Yuan and the others were able to recognize what it was. These were yin lightning mines. Yuan’s eyes shone. One must know that yin lightning mines were very rare in realms other than the Devil Realm. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have this much.

Yuan carefully inspected the yin lightning mines, then he nodded and said, “Great, these really are yin lightning mines. Little Hai, how did you manage to get all of these?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “The Devil Realm’s Tu Mietan wanted to kill me using these things. However, I was able to kill him before he was able to use them, so I took them as my spoils. I reckon these would be useful to us at this time. With these mines, everyone’ safety will be even more guaranteed.

Yuan and the others were moved. One must know that because of the yin lightning mines’ rarity, those who have them would hesitate to make use of it. But now, Zhao Hai took them out for everyone. Everyone couldn’t help but feel more intimate with him.

Yuan wasn’t polite, he waved his hand and said, “Alright, then everyone should take one for themselves.” Everyone knew that being polite at this time would just alienate themselves. Therefore, they each took one yin lightning mine for themselves. The remaining ones were taken by Yuan and Liu Zhen.

Zhao Hai won over everyone with this move. He planned to do this because he knew that forming a connection with these people would benefit his position in the Machine Field. These people weren’t from External Halls but were Core Members of their respective families. Their words hold weight in their own families.

These people belong to powerful Mage and Warrior families. And in a place like the Six Realms Battlefield, the relationships they forge here would be stronger than usual. As long as they establish a friendship in the battlefield, then they would definitely be a great help for Zhao Hai in the future.

Chapter 1292: Killing for Treasures

Ever since he discovered that the Six Realms Battlefield was made by someone, Zhao Hai decided to speed up his own plans. But Zhao Hai couldn’t increase his strength in a short time. At this moment, his strength wasn’t invincible in the World of Cultivation. So he could only expand his influence. He needs to create more contacts, much much more contacts.

Fortunately, the Six Realms Battlefield was a very good place to establish new connections. One could see this from Yuan’s relationship with Ma Rulong. Yuan stayed in the Six Realms Battlefield in order to take revenge. But if he went out, then Ma Rulong would certainly help him. After all, the two formed a friendship from near death.

If Zhao Hai wanted the Space to level up, then he would need the resources of the World of Cultivation. However, if one doesn’t have a strong backer, then they wouldn’t be able to easily get their hands on precious resources. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to increase his own circle of influence.

After everyone took their own yin lightning mines, Yuan said, “Alright, it’s time to depart. Everyone, remember to keep close to each other. Being alone in the soft gold mine is equivalent to courting death.”

Everyone nodded, then Yuan began to lead the team out of the tunnel. But as he was about to leave, Yuan was blocked by Zhao Hai. Then Zhao Hai said, “Captain, we’re in the Demon Realm’s territory. Since we need to carefully advance, let me scout first.” Then he waved his hand and released some Undead.

What’s different about the Undead this time was that these Undead were small. There were some small mice, snakes, and other critters. Zhao Hai also had them transform into their normal appearances so that they wouldn’t attract any attention. These critters were best for reconnaissance.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wasn’t depending on these small Undead to scout. His main scouting method were still the silver needles. Actually, the silver needles were about to arrive at the soft gold mine. This move not only hid the existence of the silver needles, it would also increase everyone’s impression of him.

Yuan smiled and said, “Kid, having you really removes a lot of my worries. How about you follow me everywhere from now on?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Forget it, Captain. Do you also want me to follow you to the toilets? Even if you order me, I still won’t go.” When Zhao Hai said this, everyone couldn’t help but laugh. Even Yuan who was teased joined in on the laughter. These people shared life and death together, so a harmless joke like this wouldn’t affect their minds.

After this conversation, Zhao Hai gave a nod which made everyone go out of the tunnel. Once they were out, Yuan reorganized the surrounding area to remove their traces. Then everyone flew towards the soft gold mine.

Although the Undead were paving the way ahead, Yuan still proceeded forward carefully. The group flew slowly and even flew in a circle to circumvent the Ironwood Demon Forest.

Meanwhile, Zhao Hai had no worries since the silver needles had already reached the soft gold mine. It was also at this time that Zhao Hai understood Yuan’s caution towards the region. The place was truly chaotic. In fact, upon looking at the mine, the first word that Zhao Hai thought about was the bug caves.

The soft gold mines had tunnels in all directions. And with the mountain where the mine was at being 6000 meters tall, the entire complex looked like a giant hive. And because it was a mine, its tunnels were more concentrated compared to the Bug Caves in Fabio Planet.

The tunnels built by the bugs also extended in all directions, however the tunnels were dug systematically. Moreover, each tunnel was covered with bug secretions making it as stable as concrete structures.

On the other hand, the soft gold mine’s tunnels were completely unmanaged. People dug wherever they could dig. With the wanton digging happening all the time, there were a lot of collapsed tunnels in the mine.

Also, since battles happen from time to time, more tunnels collapsed. Because of the mine’s unstable state, sounds of tunnels collapsing were commonly heard every day.

What attracted Zhao Hai’s attention the most were the people mining soft gold ores. There were people from all races here. And each team was only made out of a single race. Whenever two different groups of people meet, a battle would certainly happen. Fighting was a constant in the mines, it would make any newcomer here speechless.

After travelling in a circle, Zhao Hai and the others finally reached the mountain. Looking at the large mountain, everyone couldn’t help but stare. And just as they were staring, a loud explosion was heard before a tunnel close by collapsed. The group quickly evaded the debris that came out of the explosion.

When the group arrived at a safe location, Yuan smiled bitterly and said, “Good, this soft gold mine is still the same as before. Hahaha. Good, this is fantastic.”

As soon as they heard this, the group looked at each other. Actually, most of them were newcomers to the mines. They only heard that this place was terrifyingly chaotic. The reason why they never came here was because they weren’t qualified to go near this place.

Generally, most people from the Machine Field wouldn’t go too far from their territory. This allows them support whenever events happen. It can be said that there were only a few people like Yuan from the Machine Field who would actively seek the other realms for trouble. This also allowed Yuan to visit the other realms’ territory.

Upon hearing Yuan, a Warrior at the side said, “Captain, is the mine always like this? Then why didn’t it completely collapse?”

Yuan smiled and replied, “It’s not easy for the mine to collapse completely. Have you seen those collapsed places? Soon people will clean it up and take soft gold ores. Hahaha. Tunnels will continually collapse and re-dug. This is the reason why the mountain looked like this.”

XIong Li turned towards the mountain and said, “Captain, does this mountain still have soft gold ore left? From what I can understand, this place has been turned over several times already?”

Yuan smiled and said, “Not just several times, I reckon it’s been turned for several tens of times. At this point, there’s little soft gold ore left in this place. But do you really think that those who came here were only after the soft gold ores?” Upon hearing Yuan, people began to understand. Besides mining for soft gold ores, other people would also come here in order to seize treasures. This was the greatest shortcut to becoming rich.

Yuan looked at everyone and said, “Alright, don’t think about it too much. In any case, we’re already here. So why don’t we try our luck, aren’t we here to kill?” Everyone smiled and followed Yuan towards one of the surface tunnels. This tunnel wasn’t very big, but it was so deep that they couldn’t see the end.

Everyone entered the tunnel with heightened caution. All of them had their weapons out. However, upon seeing the Undead critters from time to time, they began to relax.

With these Undead, at least they wouldn’t have to be afraid of being ambushed. But they weren’t only alert because of ambushes, they were also paying attention in case the tunnel collapsed. The collapse of the tunnel earlier had left a deep impression on them.

After walking for some time, Zhao Hai stopped and waved towards the others. Everyone looked at Zhao Hai as they gripped their weapons tighter.

At this time, a small Undead appeared in the distance and then crawled over to Zhao Hai. After a short moment, it turned around and left. Zhao Hai turned to Yuan and said, “Captain, there are several people from the Cultivation Realm mining. What do we do?” Yuan asked, “Cultivators? Where are they?”

Zhao Hai replied, “There are ten of them. After turning left and then right, we would reach them after flying for 15 minutes.”

Yuan nodded, “Let’s go eliminate them.” Then he followed Zhao Hai’s directions and led the way. Zhao Hai and the others also hastily flew behind. In the Six Realms Battlefield, people from the Machine Field weren’t very afraid of Cultivators. They fought these people at least once every month, all fear they had already disappeared a long time ago.

As they flew, the group could feel bursts of energy coming from the front. It seems like the Cultivators were using spells. Upon detecting this, the group accelerated. However, the Cultivators were able to sense them, they immediately turned around and ran without pause.

One shouldn’t think that every Cultivator was arrogant. It was impossible for them to carry their pride and fight to the death wherever they go. Among all six realms, the people from the Cultivation Realm fear death the most. They treasure their lives more heavily compared to the other realms.

This was because people from the Cultivation Realm knew that they have longer lifespans compared to the people from the other realms. As long as they suffer no accidents, then they will live for a very long time. Therefore, it’s common for Cultivators to fear death.

Upon seeing that the people from the Cultivation Realm were escaping, Zhao Hai’s figure moved and then vanished in place. Then in the next moment, Zhao Hai was already fighting with the Cultivators. The others from the Machine Field quickly caught up and before long a group battle commenced. Zhao Hai sent 1000-layer formations continuously, completely entangling the Cultivators.

Nobody held back as attacks came crashing down on both sides. These Cultivators all had Core Formation strength. If this was the Cultivation Realm, then these people would be a region’s strongest experts. But in the Six Realms Battlefield, they only became prey for the Machine Field. And even if these people died, then nobody would know where to take their revenge.

The fight started in a flash and also ended quickly. In less than half an hour, all Cultivators were killed. Seeing the bodies in front of him, Yuan said, “Collect the loot first, then we’ll divide them when we go back.” Nobody disagreed and immediately took the weapons of the dead and stored them away.

Chapter 1293: Ten Thousand Transformations Staff

When he saw that everyone was taking away the spoils, Zhao Hai looked at Yuan and said, “Captain, I don’t want the loot. But I want the corpses. What do you think?”

Yuan froze for a moment when he heard Zhao Hai, but he quickly understood what he meant. Yuan smiled and said, “You want to turn these fellows into Undead? Alright, no problem. In any case, nobody here has any use for them. As for the spoils, we’ll discuss it after we head back.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he waved his hand and sent the dead Cultivators into the Space. Naturally nobody opposed this action. Zhao Hai led them here and even stopped the Cultivators from escaping. It can be said that without him, they wouldn’t be able to get any of these loot.

Everything has been taken care of and everyone was ready to leave. However, Zhao Hai stayed put. Seeing Zhao Hai, Yuan couldn’t help but ask, “Little Hai? What’s the problem?”

Zhao Hai smiled as he touched the tunnel walls and felt it. Then he looked at Yuan and said, “Some people heard our battle and are heading here. They’re Demons.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, everyone’s eyes shone as one of them said, “Demons? Fantastic! Captain, let’s clean them up.”

Yuan smiled as well as he said, “Of course, we’ll deal with them. We came here to cause trouble to the Demons. Whether we’ll be able to clean them up or not, we’ll still fight them.”

At this time, Zhao Hai said, “Captain, there’s about 30 Demons coming over. One of them is at Nascent Soul. I’m afraid if we’re unable to deal with them in a short time, then we’ll be attracting more Demons over to this place.”

Yuan nodded. Although their group was quite large for the soft gold mine, this place was still the Demon Race’s territory in the end. Majority of people occupying this mine were Demons. If Yuan and the others stayed in the same place for too long, then more and more Demons would come over. When the time comes, they would be in dire trouble.

However, this was an opportunity that Yuan couldn’t just easily pass up. Then suddenly, Yuan had an idea. He looked at everyone and said, “This chance is too good to let go. Everyone, prepare the yin lightning mines that we got from Little Hai. Once the Demons arrive, immediately use them. Let’s see how the Demons deal with this many mines.”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he smiled. He didn’t say anything. He had a lot more mines inside the Space, but he can’t take a lot of them at the same time. Yuan knew how precious these rare lightning mines were. But now, Yuan decided to use them to deal with the Demons. It seems like he was really prepared to be ruthless to the Demons.

As soon as everyone heard Yuan, they also couldn’t help but stare. But not one of them said anything as they all took out their yin lightning mines and prepared to use them.

Although the Machine Field also had their own territory in the Six Realms Battlefield, and the area they controlled wasn’t any less compared to the other realms, the people from the Machine Field couldn’t freely head out to hunt. This caused them to feel aggrieved. They weren’t insane enough like Yuan who liked to stir trouble everywhere. They were the opposite of Yuan, they wouldn’t dare stir up trouble. When they arrive at the core battlefield, they would just dig for herbs and hunt lone beasts. And when they were faced with the other realms, they were usually at a passive position and would seldom make any moves. This caused them to feel suffocated inside. Now that they had the opportunity to return the favor, everyone was feeling excited.

The Demons didn’t make Zhao Hai and the others wait for a long time. Perhaps in their opinion, although Zhao Hai’s group had a lot of people, the mines were still in the Demon Race’s partially controlled territory. So even if there were only 30 Demons, they didn’t hesitate to attack.

It didn’t take long before the Demons appeared opposite Zhao Hai’s group. These people were all in battle uniforms and in their humanoid forms. The weakest of them was at Foundation Establishment while those with Core Formation Cultivation were the majority. There’s also one Nascent Soul Expert. The Nascent Soul Expert assumed command of the team. With such a leader, no wonder they brazenly approached a group that outnumbered them. Naturally they were here to get some loot.

When the Demon party saw that Yuan and the others were in a formation and were just waiting there, they couldn’t help but be happy. They roared as they entered battle. Only the Nascent Soul Expert stayed behind.

Yuan and the others looked at the attacking Demons. The Foundation Establishment Demons had transformed into their true body. Although the Core Formation Demons hadn’t fully transformed, a part of their body had changed and turned into a menacing weapon.

Demons were generally divided into three forms: the true form, weapon form, and humanoid form. True form is when they transform into their true bodies. Weapon form was transforming a part of their body into weapons for the battle. And lastly, the humanoid for where they emulate the form of a human.

When in their humanoid form, the Demons could also use weapons as well as spells. However, only a few Demons would use that form in battle. Most of them preferred to use their weapon form.

A Demon’s true weapon and their bodies were closely linked. Moreover, since a Demon’s body was innately formidable, their true weapons were the most powerful parts. A true weapon’s attacking strength was extraordinary. Most importantly, the more a Demon fought using their true weapons, the true weapon would get stronger and stronger. It was the opposite of a Cultivator’s life source weapon where it got stronger the more it was nourished in the dantian. In this case, Cultivators would only use them when very necessary. It was also because of this that most Demons don’t use magic artifacts and would instead fight in their weapon forms.

As the Demons were charging, Yuan was calculating their distance. The power of the yin lightning mines was big. Moreover, its explosion might collapse the entire tunnel. Therefore, Yuan needed to properly gauge the distance. If they use the mines too early, then the Demons might be able to react. But if they use the mines too late, then they might risk damaging themselves as well.

The tunnel was very long and the Demons were charging over like a swarm of bees. The Demons didn’t say anything at all and just attacked. This was also a special phenomenon in the soft gold mine. There were no exquisite plots to speak of when attacking an enemy. After all, they were here to snatch treasures and retreat. There was no need to waste any breath conversing with the enemy.

When the Demons were about 500 meters away from Yuan’s group, Yuan suddenly shouted, “Begin!” As he said his command, 50 yin lightning mines were thrown towards the approaching Demons.

This caused the Demons to stare. However, they were already 500 meters away from Yuan’s team. For Core Formation experts, throwing something 500 meters away could be done in a blink of an eye. Therefore, before the Demons could react, they heard a loud explosion before the whole tunnel collapsed.

Yuan and the others underestimated the strength of the yin lightning mines. One must know the explosion that happened when Zhao Hai used his yin lightning mines back in the Void Arena was different. After all, back then, it was an open area so the force of explosion was dispersed quickly. But now, they were in a tunnel – a closed space. It’s natural for the explosive strength to increase by a few folds.

The tunnel collapsed immediately following the xplosion. The part of the tunnel that Yuan and the others were in had collapsed as well. It’s fortunate that Zhao Hai was able to quickly react and erected a protective shield around them. Otherwise, there might be casualties on their side.

After the tunnel collapsed and calmed down, Zhao Hai proceeded to clean the place up with Magic. The original tunnel was no longer there, the only thing left was a pile of rubble.

However, Zhao Hai knew that not all of the Demons died. The Foundation Stage Demons were all dead, but some Core Formation Demons had survived albeit in very serious conditions. As for the Nascent Soul Demon, it was unscathed. However, it had already turned into its true form, its eyes were full of killing intent.

What made Zhao Hai surprised the most was that the Nascent Soul Demon was actually a pangolin. It was currently a hundred meters long. Its scales were glittering yellow while its front paws were visibly sharp. It cleared tens of meters of rubble with one swipe. It wouldn’t take long for it to reach where Zhao Hai and the others were.

Zhao Hai didn’t hesitate and immediately said, “Captain, lead everyone back quickly!” Then he waved his hand as a huge magic formation appeared. Then when the spell was released, a tunnel appeared on the rubble behind them.

When he heard Zhao Hai, Yuan immediately nodded before shouting, “Quickly fly through the tunnel!” The others obeyed hastily.

While the others were retreating, Zhao Hai waved his hand once more and released a 10,000-layer formation to attack in front of him.

This formation set has weapon shattering in it, causing a huge hole to appear. The Demon opposite Zhao Hai also felt this attack. It immediately curled up into a huge golden ball. When Zhao Hai hit the pangolin’s scales, its body rolled back 100 meters away.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t relieved. Although the other party had been pushed back, this was also a good thing for the Demon. Zhao Hai’s attack wasted his energy but it didn’t do any substantial damage to the Demon.

Sure enough, after rolling for 100 meters, the pangolin stopped. Then it waved its claws, sending attacks towards Zhao Hai. The trajectory of the attacks didn’t leave Zhao Hai with any route to retreat.

The two were currently in a collapsed tunnel. Since the place was so narrow, it was impossible to avoid each other’s attack. The Pangolin could only take Zhao Hai’s attack but the same was true for Zhao Hai. The two could only fight head on against each other.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and another 10,000-layer formation appeared in front of him to block the incoming attack. Seeing Zhao Hai block the attacks it sent, the Pangolin roared and then charged forward.

The Pangolin was very fast. Moreover, it was very intelligent. Seeing that Zhao Hai was a Mage, it immediately wanted to get in close-combat with him.

But how could Zhao Hai be afraid of close combat? Seeing his enemy approach, Zhao Hai turned his staff into a sledgehammer and smashed it towards the Pangolin. The Pangolin stared when he saw this. Zhao Hai didn’t change his weapon. His original staff became the sledgehammer, which made the Pangolin curious.

Actually, the Pangolin heard about these transforming weapons before. This weapon was known as the Ten Thousand Transformations Staff in the World of Cultivation. It was said that this weapon was inside the Floating Palace of the Cultivation Realm’s Buddhist Sect. Naturally, this weapon was legendary and only a few people had seen it. Nobody dared to offend the Floating Palace. The Floating Palace was a holy place for Buddhism. They had Inner Sect Monks numbering 100 thousand, their Outer Sect members couldn’t be counted. It was a formidable existence that nobody wanted to provoke. And since it was in the Floating Palace, the Ten Thousand Transformations Staff couldn’t be easily taken out. Maybe it could only see the light of day when the sect was in a threat of extermination.

However, since the Floating Palace was a huge influence, a scenario where it would be destroyed was practically impossible. At the same time, they had numerous powerful artifacts. Only when everything was exhausted would the staff be taken out.

Beside the Ten Thousand Transformations Staff, the Pangolin hasn’t heard of any other weapon that can transform. Therefore, when it saw Zhao Hai’s staff transforming, it couldn’t help but be stunned.

As the Pangolin was thinking about this, Zhao Hai’s sledgehammer hit its body. The Pangolin had fought a lot of battles so it was only stunned for a very short time. It quickly recovered. It was now certain that Zhao Hai’s artifact wasn’t Floating Palace’s Ten Thousand Transformations Staff. Otherwise, this strike would kill him instantly. He also heard how powerful the staff was, so how could it be in the hands of someone from the Machine Field.

With this thought in mind, the Pangolin calmed down. He curled his body once more and rolled away. But as he rolled away, the Pangolin’s tail lashed out like an iron whip and attacked Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai’s sledgehammer path didn’t change. The hammer hit the tail and a ‘Wen!’ sound was heard. Pain immediately assaulted the Pangolin from the place the hammer hit. Zhao Hai’s hammer shattered three scales, naturally the Pangolin was in pain.

But in the end, Zhao Hai only crushed three scales and didn’t injure the Pangolin too much. Although its tail was injured, the Pangolin’s attack didn’t stop. Seeing that it was mistaken in its offensive approach, the Pangolin itself rolled towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai immediately turned his sledgehammer into a big shield. When the Pangolin hit Zhao Hai’s shield, it unfurled and grabbed it with his claws.

However, much to the Pangolin’s surprise, it couldn’t grasp the shield. He was surprised that he couldn’t grab such a large shield. He was beginning to doubt whether Zhao Hai’s weapon was really not the Ten Thousand Transformations Staff.

Chapter 1294: Submit or Die!

Just like its name implies, the Ten Thousand Transformation Staff could come in all kinds of forms. And it was said that the staff was as firm as diamond. It was also rumored that the staff doesn’t have the same style as a Buddhist staff. Although it wasn’t as beautiful as Buddhist staffs, its might was astonishing.

The Pangolin was very confident in its claws. Pangolins use their claws to dig, so it was the most tenacious part of their body. Ever since he gained spiritual wisdom, the Pangolin had been nurturing its claws as weapons. This made the strength of its claws unimaginable.

The Pangolin had also fought people from the other realms and among them were experts with Nascent Soul strength. There were very few weapons that it couldn’t grab with its claws.

But in the process of fighting Zhao Hai, the Pangolin couldn’t get any advantage. And instead, its strong scales were destroyed by Zhao Hai and his shield could block his claws. Moreover, there were no scratches on Zhao Hai’s shield. Such weapon caused the Pangolin to feel afraid.

The Pangolin was sure that Zhao Hai wasn’t using the Ten Thousand Transformations Staff. But Zhao Hai’s own transforming weapon still caused it to feel a headache.

Seeing that his attack was useless, the Pangolin retreated quickly. Its small eyes couldn’t hide the amazement it felt. It had already calmed down from its anger and was starting to consider its own situation.

Zhao Hai looked at the Pangolin and smiled as he said, “What? Scared? I thought Demons are unafraid of death? I’ll give you two options. Either you surrender to me, or die and be skinned!”

Hatred flashed through the Pangolin’s eyes. Then it opened its mouth and coldly said, “Are certain that you can stop me from escaping?”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “I am sure that you can’t escape from me. If you don’t believe me, then you can look behind you. It’s already impossible for you to escape.”

The Pangolin suddenly felt a savage aura coming from behind it. When it turned to look, it discovered that a giant bug had appeared. It was the Silverback Gold-winged Bug that Zhao Hai subdued!

The fighting strength of the Silverback Gold-winged Bug was in no way inferior to the Pangolin. It might even be more powerful than the Demon. After all, it had been transformed by the Space.

Although the Pangolin was a Demon, it also knew about the Bug Race. The Bug Race and the Demons were different. Although the Bugs were also technically Demons, the Demons were somewhat weaker while the Bugs were a headache to the Cultivation Realm.

The Silverback Gold-winged Bugs had a reputation among the Bugs, so how could the Pangolin be unaware of it. With Zhao Hai in its front and the Silverback Gold-winged back at its back, the Pangolin knew that it no longer had any chance of victory.

The Pangolin’s heart turned cold. It knew that it was in trouble, so it looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Who are you?”

This Pangolin had been in the Six Realms Battlefield for a long time but he doesn’t know who Zhao Hai was. Additionally, the Demons don’t have many computers and they also didn’t like to use them. Therefore, even if it heard Zhao Hai’s name, it couldn’t recognize him from his face.

Zhao Hai looked at the Pangolin, then he smiled faintly and said, “I’m called Zhao Hai.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai’s name, the Pangolin couldn’t help but stare, then it muttered, “So you’re Zhao Hai. No wonder you’re so strong.”

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything and just looked at the Pangolin. The Pangolin also knew that if it didn’t submit, then it would certainly die. Between death and submission, naturally it knew which one to choose. It wasn’t a Demon that was faithful to its race until death. Thinking that it would perish, it had no choice but to submit to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t compel the Pangolin to make its decision. He only stood there and waited for the Pangolin to respond. Before long, the Pangolin turned into its humanoid form and moved forward. The humanoid pangolin looked very ordinary. It had yellow body armor and was quite buff. However, its face was very generic, he looked like an army man.

Zhao Hao saw this and knew that the Pangolin had decided to submit. The Pangolin gave Zhao Hai a salute and said, “Jia Ding Shan submits to Master. I wish the Master would take me in.”

Upon hearing the Pangolin, he nodded and said, “Go in.” Then he waved his hand and opened a spatial rift. Jia Ding Shan stared. But after seeing the Silverback Gold-winged Bug staring at him, it had no choice but to enter the Space.

From the moment Jian Ding Shan announced that he submits to Zhao Hai, the walls to its heart had already fallen. It had completely lost all courage to rebel. Naturally, it wouldn’t dare defy Zhao Hai’s orders.

Just as Jia Ding Shan entered the Space, the Space immediately issued a prompt, “Partially submissive creature detected. Subduing completely, subjugation complete. The creature is a demon-class lifeform. Its body is in the form of a pangolin. Extracting the demonic spirit of the Pangolin and fusing it with the Space. Extraction successful. All armored creatures in the Space will now increase in strength.”

Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. The prompt was good news to him. Jia Ding Shan has been completely subdued, this was certainly good news.

Actually, in the World of Cultivation, subduing another practitioner and making them your servant wasn’t an unusual matter. However, this was generally done by powerful practitioners to those lower-ranked than them. There were very few people who would submit to those of equal level. Moreover, with the Machine Field’s reputation, making other people from other realms submit to them was close to impossible.

Jia Ding Shan being subdued by Zhao Hai would certainly cause a massive stir in the World of Cultivation. However, Zhao Hai didn’t mind it for now as he released large quantities of Undead to clean the battlefield. There were more than 30 Demon corpses waiting to be cleaned up.

The yin lightning mines caused the Demons directly hit by them to be vaporized. However, there were several Demons whose bodies survived after the explosion. There were also a few surviving ones, but the Undead wouldn’t have any problems dealing with them.

Actually, Zhao Hai could send the injured Demons to the Space to cure their wounds after subjugating them. However, Zhao Hai didn’t want to do that since this would leave Yuan and the others very little loot. Although they had killed the group of Cultivators earlier, the loot they gained was still lacking. If Zhao Hai subdued the surviving Demons, then Yuan and the others would gain even less spoils.

Therefore, Zhao Hai didn’t subjugate the Demons and just killed them off. Then he took their bodies to the Space while taking Jia Ding Shan out.

After releasing Jia Ding Shan, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately call Yuan and the others over. Instead he looked at the collapsed mine and tried to see if he could get some soft gold ores.

Zhao Hai turned to look at Jia Ding Shan and said, “You’ve been here for some time, did you manage to find some soft gold ores?”

Jia Ding Shan respectfully replied, “Replying to the Young Master. I haven’t really come across any soft gold ores. In fact, there are very few soft gold ores left in this mountain. I’m afraid finding some wouldn’t be easy.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he had the same idea. Then he looked at the rubble and said, “Go take a look at those rocks and try to see if there are some soft gold ores.”

Jia Ding Shan nodded and immediately began to sort through the rocks. The collapsed tunnel was huge, so its collapse should have informed other people. But since nobody wanted to explore a collapsed region, this gave Zhao Hai the opportunity to investigate.

Zhao Hai kept silent as he looked at Jia Ding Shan being busy. He was also paying attention to the people outside. Yuan and the others had escaped the collapsed tunnel and were waiting for him to come out.

Zhao Hai sent them out because he was afraid that they would get caught in the fight. One should know that fights between Nascent Soul Experts weren’t peaceful. Zhao Hai wasn’t sure if he could keep everyone safe from being attacked.

At the same time, Zhao Hai realized that his strength was still lacking. If he didn’t have the Silverback Gold-winged bug, then Jia Ding Shan wouldn’t have surrendered. It’s possible for the Pangolin Demon to find an opportunity to run away. No matter which realm in the World of Cultivation, and no matter from which influence they came from, Nascent Soul Experts always had ways to save their lives. They couldn’t be easily dealt with.

The Demons weren’t the strongest in the World of Cultivation Realm. It can be said that their strength was at the middle of the ranking. However, Jia Ding Shan was already a very strong Nascent Soul Expert that was difficult for Zhao Hai to deal with. When he thought about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but whisper, “It seems like I had been a little carried away.”

Zhao Hai knew that those he met weren’t the strongest experts of the World of Cultivation. At least these people hadn’t been integrated into the very core of their own sects. At the very least they were Inner Disciples. For people like these, Zhao Hai couldn’t be proud even after defeating them.

He had already shown his strength before to the Cultivators. In the future, the Cultivation Realm would only want to deal with him. They would certainly send more powerful experts. When that time comes, things would only get more troublesome.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai secretly made a warning to himself. He needs to be careful or else he would suffer a loss.

At this time, Jia Ding Shan happily held a rock the size of a person’s head. Besides being more yellow than the other rocks, it looked nothing special. However, this piece of rock actually made people feel a strong aura.

Jia Ding Shan handed the rock over to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, our luck is really good. This is soft gold ore. If we refine it, I reckon we can get 2 to 3 bars of soft gold.”

Zhao Hai received the ore and immediately felt that it was heavy. It seems like its gold content was high. Otherwise, it would be impossible to get 2 to 3 bars by just relying on this piece of ore alone.

Zhao Hai nodded and then threw the ore to the Space which immediately made ore veins out of it. Then he looked at Jia Ding Shan and said, “Good job. Keep looking.” Jia Ding Shan nodded and then resumed digging. But at this time, Zhao Hai’s expression suddenly changed as he hurriedly stopped the Pangolin.

Chapter 1295: Elder of Sword Pavillion

Jia Ding Shan looked puzzled at Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai’s expression turned serious as he said, “Follow me.” Then his body moved as he brought Jia Ding Shan out of the tunnel and then led him towards Yuan and the others.

Although Jia Ding Shan didn’t know what Zhao Hai was doing, he had already submitted to him so all he could do was obey. He followed behind Zhao Hai as they flew forward.

Zhao Hai was in a hurry to go out because he discovered that Yuan and the others were under attack. They weren’t being attacked by the Demons. Instead, their opponents were people from the Cultivation Realm.

There were about 50 Cultivators that were being led by two Sword Cultivators with Nascent Soul strength. Such a team wasn’t an opponent for Yuan and the others.

To be honest, Yuan’s previous battles against the other realms only involved Core Formation Experts. As for those with Nascent Soul strength, Yuan wouldn’t normally dare make them his enemies. Only when they have vast numerical advantage would Yuan try to fight them.

But at this time, although their team had more than 100 people, the Cultivation Realm had 50 and two of them were Nascent Soul Sword Cultivators. In this case, it was impossible for Yuan and the others to be their opponent.

They could still survive for some time, but Yuan and the others were being desperate. They came to the soft gold mine because of Zhao Hai’s assurance. But now, Zhao Hai was left inside the tunnels and Yuan couldn’t check up on him. They won’t dare to leave the area as well. The only thing they could do was to defend the exit. However, they didn’t think that they would meet a team of Cultivators. Faced with so many Cultivators, Yuan and the others were in great trouble.

Fortunately for them, behind them was the collapsed tunnel, so they weren’t surrounded at all sides. They could also head back inside. Moreover, they still had 50 yin lightning mines left, those could still be taken out to be used.

But they couldn’t make a move at this time since it’s not yet necessary. They still don’t know Zhao Hai’s situation. If they risked retreating back into the tunnel, then they might bring trouble to Zhao Hai. The same was true for using the yin lightning mines.

Because of this, Yuan forbade the others from retreating back into the tunnel when the fight began. They also weren’t permitted to use the yin lightning mines. At this time, they could only defend against the attacks of the Cultivators. Before long, they were at a complete disadvantage.

However, even if they were at the back foot, their casualties weren’t that big. Currently, they only have injured people with no deaths. But Yuan wasn’t in a happy mood. This was because the two Nascent Soul Sword Cultivators had yet to make a move.

The two Sword Cultivators were the strongest people in this team. Without them making a move, Yuan and the others were already at a disadvantage. If these Sword Cultivators made a move, then the Machine Field team would certainly be finished.

At the same time, Yuan could see that the members of the Cultivator team were Sword Cultivators. It seems like they were from the same Sect and they went to the soft gold mine for training. Yuan and the others were being treated as training partners for these Cultivators.

Although he was aware about this, Yuan couldn’t be angry. He knew that this was the reality in the World of Cultivators. If you have the strength, then you can treat others like pigs and dogs. If you were weak, then you can only be treated as a pig or dog to be slaughtered.

Fortunately, the Machine Field had experience in fighting Cultivators. They were very methodical in their actions, allowing them to block the attacks of the Cultivators.

At this moment, Yuan noticed that the two Nascent Soul Sword Cultivators had shifted their attention into the tunnel behind them. Yuan’s heart skipped a beat as he also paid attention to the hole behind him. He knew that his senses weren’t as good as the two Nascent Soul Sword Cultivators. The two Sword Cultivators must have found something. If Zhao Hai came out of the hole, then that would be good. However, if it wasn’t Zhao Hai, then Yuan and the others would be finished.

It didn’t take long before Yuan saw two people flying out of the hole. One of them was Zhao Hai, but who was the other one? Was it the Nascent Soul Demon from before? What was going on? Why did Zhao Hai go out with the Demon?

While Yuan was puzzled, Zhao Hai and Jia Ding Shan flew out of the tunnel. Zhao Hai saw the situation and without hesitation let lose several 1000-layer formations to drive back the Cultivators. Yuan and the others also took this chance to go behind Zhao Hai.

While he was behind Zhao Hai, Yuan also looked at Jia Ding Shan. He discovered that Jia Ding Shan was standing behind Zhao Hai as though he was a servant. This discovery caused Yuan’s heart to shake.

However, Yuan was an experienced person. His strength might be lacking, but his vision made up for it. As soon as he saw Jia Ding Shan, he knew that the Demon had been subdued by Zhao Hai. Otherwise, it wouldn’t have acted like this.

To be honest, this seemingly normal result was something that Yuan still couldn’t believe. This was because he knew clearly that if Zhao Hai was really able to do this, then that would make him terrifying. Jia Ding Shan was a Nascent Soul Demon, but it was actually subjugated by another person. This only meant that the other party had strength so great that it forced the pangolin to submit.

As Yuan thought of this, the Cultivators paused their attack. The Cultivators stopped attacking because the two Nascent Soul Sword Cultivators could see that Zhao Hai and Jia Ding Shan were also at Nascent Soul. In this case, the Core Formation Cultivators needed to retreat or they would be courting death.

The two Sword Cultivators also noticed the strange arrangement between Zhao Hai and Jia Ding Shan. After observing for a while, one of the two Sword Cultivators looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Who are you? You seem to be someone new here. I haven’t heard about you.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then gave the Sword Cultivator a bow. Then he said, “This one is Zhao Hai. You should be able to recognize my name. Might I have the honor to know your names?”

When the two Sword Cultivators heard Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but stare. They had certainly heard about Zhao Hai’s name. The first place spot of the Six Realms Beginner Competition was just snatched by someone named Zhao Hai. So how could they not know of his name? They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be in the Six Realms Battlefield.

The Sword Cultivator who asked Zhao Hai cupped his fist and answered, “I’m an Elder of the Sword Pavillion Zhou Fang. This is Song Qing, my junior brother.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I didn’t expect to meet Cultivators from the Sword Pavillion. It’s an honor. This one is my servant Jia Ding Shan.”

Upon hearing that Jia Ding Shan was Zhao Hai’s servant, everyone present were shaken. Although they had already made this guess, they were still shocked when they heard it from Zhao Hai’s mouth.

Jia Ding Shan’s expression didn’t change as he cupped his fist towards Zhou Fang and Song Qing. The two Sword Cultivators didn’t dare neglect the greeting as they also cupped their fists. Although Jia Ding Shan was a servant, he was still a Nascent Soul Expert – someone with the same level as them. The World of Cultivation spoke with strength. If they underestimate Jia Ding Shan because he was a servant, they would risk offending him. And offending a Nascent Soul Expert was never a good idea.

After the two exchanged greetings, Zhao Hai immediately went straight to the point as he said, “We should all be aware that we are in the soft gold mine. I won’t say anything about you attacking my people. Of course, I can also fight back, but it’s obvious that it’s not suitable for us to fight. How about we all take a step back? What does Mister Zhou think about this?”

When Zhou Fang and Song Qing heard Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but gawk. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to go straight to the point. They looked at each other and exchanged a look. Then Song Qing turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister Zhao Hai’s words are very reasonable. This one wants to exchange notes with Mister Zhao Hai. I wonder if Mister Zhao Hai can agree to my request?”

Upon hearing Song Qing’s reply, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh. Then he said, “Alright, that’s a good idea. This one has always wanted to compare notes with Sword Cultivators. I remember being able to see people from the Sword Pavilion back in the Yellowsand Planet trial. But it’s a pity that we only brushed past each other. Being able to spar with an Elder of the Sword Pavilion is my good fortune.”

Song Qing didn’t say anything else after hearing Zhao Hai. He took a step forward and then said, “Since Mister agrees, then forgive me for being impolite.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Mister Song, please!”

Song Qing wasn’t polite as he moved his hand and took his sword out. The sword didn’t delay and immediately thrust itself towards Zhao Hai. The thrust looked ordinary, there’s nothing special about it at first glance. However, Zhao Hai knew that he couldn’t dodge this sword or else Yuan and the others would suffer bad luck. Song Qing’s sword had a very intense astral qi. It’s clear that he was able to absorb some astral qi into his body.

Zhao Hai’s eyes flashed a cold light. Then he took a step forward and released a punch. The fist shaped qi flew towards Song Qing’s sword. This fist was different compared to the previous punches he threw before. This time, Zhao Hai used astral qi in his attack.

Zhao Hai had also absorbed astral qi into his body before. However, he had yet to clash with an enemy who managed to do the same. Astral Qi could increase offensive strength so he was preparing to use it as a trump card. But this time, he had to use it because Song Qing also had astral qi. If Zhao Hai sent out an ordinary punch, then it might not be able to block the incoming sword.

The attack of the two happened very quickly. When the sword and the fist hit each other, a fierce ‘Bang’ was heard before the tunnel they were in shook. Fortunately, the tunnel didn’t collapse.

Dust fell but Zhao Hai was able to blow it off easily. On the other hand, Song Qing had already sheathed his sword. Zhao Hai just stood there and didn’t move. The two parties were looking at each other before they laughed at the same time. Song Qing cupped his fist towards Zhao Hai and said, “Mister has great technique. I have learned so much. I hope to meet you again in the future.”

Chapter 1296: Toxic Sand Ra

t

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “That would be great.”

Song Qing gave Zhao Hai a salute once more before he waved his hand and led the other Cultivators away. Seeing the Cultivators leave, Yuan began to feel relieved. Then he went to Zhao Hai’s side and said, “Little Hai, who is this?” He didn’t dare disrespect Jia Ding Shan even if he was aware that he had become Zhao Hai’s servant.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Yuan and then he smiled and said, “This is a servant that I acquired recently, Jia Ding Shan. Jia Ding Shan, this is Captain Yuan of the Machine Field.”

Jia Ding Shan cupped his fist towards Yuan and said, “I have heard about Captain Yuan’s name. It’s an honor to meet you.”

Yuan was somewhat stunned by Jia Ding Shan’s greeting. The others also couldn’t believe what was happening as they looked at Zhao Hai and Jia Ding Shan. Nobody spoke for some time.

Zhao Hai looked at everyone and then he smiled faintly and said, “Captain, I think we should leave this area. Otherwise, more and more people would arrive. Right, let me give these to you.” Then he waved his hand as he took a pile of Demon corpses and threw them into the ground.

Yuan looked at the corpses on the ground and then stole a glance at Jia Ding Shan. He discovered that Jia Ding Shan didn’t have any change in his expression. Yuan put away the corpses of the Demons and said, “Let’s head out. There’s too much disturbance here. People will definitely check it out.” Everyone knew this so they followed Yuan and left the area.

Meanwhile, after they left and made two turns, Song Qing’s expression turned pale. Then he quickly took out a medicinal pill and swallowed it down.

When Zhou Fang saw Song Qing’s appearance, he couldn’t help but get surprised. He hastily held on to Song Qing and asked, “What happened? Are you injured?”

Song Qing nodded, then he smiled bitterly and said, “I was negligent. I didn’t expect Zhao Hai to also absorb astral qi inside his body. I was at a disadvantage when we clashed. But I can see that he was holding back. Otherwise, he wouldn’t be able to subdue Jia Ding Shan. I heard that he’s known as one of the leaders of the armored Demons. His strength isn’t weak. I didn’t expect him to surrender to Zhao Hai.”

Zhou Fang nodded and said, “I heard that Jia Ding Shan is a Demon Pangolin. Their defenses are very powerful. Additionally, they have very sharp front claws. They’re very hard to deal with. I didn’t expect him to become Zhao Hai’s servant.”

Song Qing smiled bitterly and said, “We have vastly underestimated Zhao Hai’s strength. The only reason why Zhao Hai took a step back today was because we have two Nascent Soul Experts. If it was just one, then I’m certain he wouldn’t be polite.”

Zhou Fang frowned and said, “Just how did Zhao Hai cultivate? I heard that he has only ascended for about a year. It’s unbelievable that he is already that strong.”

Song Qing frowned as well. Then he said, “His sudden appearance in the Machine Field couldn’t be good for the Cultivation Realm. Do you think we should invite a Transcending Tribulation Expert to deal with him?”

Zhou Fang furrowed his brows and said, “Forget it. We’re not even sure if we can get a Transcending Tribulation Expert to take action. And if we can, so what? Zhao Hai is already treated as a treasure by the Machine Field, so they wouldn’t just let him be harmed. Although the Machine Field has been keeping silent, they are absolute lunatics when it comes to battles. Provoking them isn’t something that our Sword Pavillion could bear. Let’s just leave Zhao Hai’s matter to the Great Sects.”

Song Qing let out a breath and said, “Right. Let the Great Sects worry about him. We should head back. Now that my strength has been affected, it’s not good for us to stay in the soft gold mine. Otherwise, we might suffer some losses. We’re taking the Pavilion’s elites with us, it’ll be a pity if we lose them.”

Zhou Fang looked at the other disciples and then said, “Alright. Everyone, prepare to head back.” Then after he said that, the two Elders led the Sword Pavilion’s disciples away from the soft gold mine.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai and the others didn’t leave the mine. After they left the area, they looked for a secure cavern in order to cure the injured.

Fortunately, the wounds weren’t very serious. At most, they were just flesh wounds. After taking care of the injured, Yuan called Zhao Hai and Liu Zhen in order to discuss what to do next.

Yuan said with a solemn expression, “We made too much noise this time. Even the Demons in the mine have been alarmed. I think we should leave. After we head back, we can try to cause some trouble with the Sprites. Little Hai, what do you think?”

Zhao Hai replied with a smile, “I have no problems with that. I also think that we should go back. It’s too dangerous in this mine. We’ve been here for a short time but we have already fought three groups of people. It’s already clear that this isn’t a good place. Now that we have dealt with some Demons, I think it’s alright to head back.”

Liu Zhen also nodded and said, “I also think that we should go back. Although we have a lot of people, we aren’t as strong as the others. And after we return, we can have Little Hai help us refine our weapons. This way, we can be more confident the next time.”

Yuan smiled and said, “Alright. But Little Hai, we’ll have to be impolite and ask for your help. This is really important to us.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Of course I’ll help you. You don’t have to worry about it. However, I don’t have any materials at hand. So I’ll have to depend on you to come up with them.”

When Yuan and Liu Zhen heard this, they couldn’t help but laugh. They knew that Zhao Hai was joking with them. The words of the trio weren’t lowered at all so everyone heard it. Knowing that Zhao Hai was going to refine their weapons, their hearts couldn’t help but be moved.

After an agreement was made, the group rested inside the cave for some time before leaving the soft gold mine. With Zhao Hai leading the way, their travel was naturally peaceful. They didn’t run into any enemy. After leaving the soft gold mine, they circled around and then returned to the tunnel they were in before. Then after resting for one day, they proceeded towards the Machine Field’s territory.

This time, they were able to meet people from other realms. However, since these people were small in number, a dozen at most, they immediately avoided Zhao Hai’s team at first sight.

Zhao Hai didn’t chase them either. Right now, what they want to do was to return to the Machine Field’s territory to have a good rest before causing trouble with the Sprites.

After flying for several days, the team finally entered the partially controlled territory of the Machine Field. Although it wasn’t really the territory of the Machine Field, everyone’s safety was also somewhat guaranteed in this area. After all, they were close to the Lock Mountain Range. It would be easy for the people from the Machine Field to ask for reinforcements in this region.

Yuan was also able to breathe comfortably now. He was truly nervous this time. He had been to the soft gold mine two years ago. However, he didn’t expect the mine to become more hostile since then.

But now, they were able to return safely. Moreover, they returned with a huge harvest. Not to say about the other things, the 30 Demon corpses alone were worth a lot.

Yuan looked around them and then smiled as he said, “I’ve always felt that our territory is better than any place.”

When he heard this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh. Then he replied, “It’s always better in your own place. But the Machine Field is indeed a little better compared to the other realms’ territory. At least, here in the Six Realms Battlefield, we are more united compared to those from the other realms.”

Yuan nodded and said, “That’s right. When it comes to unity, the other realms couldn’t compare to the Machine FIeld. It was through this unity that we were able to keep such a large territory. In order to keep this territory, the Machine FIeld pays thousands of lives every year. It would even reach ten thousand if the situation was worse.”

Zhao Hai nodded and didn’t say anything more. Then suddenly, a series of explosions were heard in front of them. Zhao Hai and then others stared before their expressions changed. This was because they could hear that the explosions were coming from Yuan’s camp.

Yuan immediately said, “Little Hai, go ahead and take a look. Did someone try to attack our headquarters? Their mother. Who is so bold and attacks this Yuan’s place?”

Zhao Hai complied and flew ahead. Actually, he didn’t need to know who was attacking the camp. He already knew the perpetrator, the Demons! An aura of a Nascent Soul Expert could be felt ahead. Currently, several people from near Yuan’s camp were rushing over in order to help fight the Demon. The attacker was a Demon in its true form, a Demon Mouse!

Upon seeing this Demon Mouse, Zhao Hai immediately knew why the Demons dared to attack a camp in the Lock Mountain Range. This huge Demon Mouse should be Hao Donglai’s elder. Upon discovering that Hao Donglai was killed, it immediately made a move.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. It seems like Hao Donglai’s status wasn’t simple, or else this Elder wouldn’t have moved. But since it came over, there’s no need for it to leave.

Jia Ding Shan followed beside Zhao Hai as the two sped up. Before long, they arrived at Yuan’s camp. At this time, the camp was very lively. Magic cannons were attacking the Demon Mouse while the reinforcements were keeping a distance and sending sword qi.

It seems like the Machine Field were used to dealing with such situations. Although the Demon Mouse was rampaging, it couldn’t cause too much damage. Naturally, this Demon Mouse was discovered long before it entered the Lock Mountain Range.

As soon as he saw the situation, Zhao Hai knew that the situation wasn’t going to end well. This Demon Mouse wouldn’t easily retreat. There were only two reasons why it attacked: the Demons sent him to demonstrate their strength, or Hao Donglai’s status was just too special. If it was the former, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t let him off. If it was the latter, then the Mouse wouldn’t retreat. In any case, the Demon Mouse wouldn’t be able to leave today.

At this time, the Demon Mouse opened its mouth and sent two shots of poisonous sand towards the fort. Mages in the fort immediately released magic at the same time. The poison sand assaulted the magic formations. Explosions were heard as magic formation after magic formation were crushed. But in the end, it was blocked because there were a lot of magic formations.

But before the Demon Mouse could make another attack, the Warriors in the fort released sword qi to attack it. However, it seems like the Demon Mouse didn’t care about them. It just let the attacks hit its body.

Seeing this, Zhao Hai coldly snorted before he shouted, “Who dares attack our Machine Field territory!” Then he and Jia Ding Shan flew towards the camp.

The Demon Mouse could feel that Zhao Hai’s aura was uncommon. It moved to a safe distance before transforming into its humanoid form and flying towards Zhao Hai and Jia Ding Shan.

Before long, Zhao Hai and Jia Ding Shan were 100 meters in front of the Demon Mouse. Zhao Hai looked at the humanoid form of the Mouse. It was a middle-aged man with small eyebrows and eyes. It had canine teeth and big ears. It was also wearing a white robe. It actually looked funny.

The Mouse was also sizing Zhao Hai and Jia Ding Shan. When he noticed Jia Ding Shan, it couldn’t help but stare. Then it asked, “Jia Ding Shan, what are you doing here?”

Jia Ding Shan looked at the Demon Mouse, then he turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, this person is called Hao Sha, nicknamed Toxic Sand Rat. He’s a member of the Hao family in the Demon Realm. The Hao family is a medium-sized family in the Demon Realm. It was said that they have two members in their family who reached Transcending Tribulation. he is only an Inner Elder in his family, not a Core Member.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked at Hao Sha and asid, “Hao Sha, what gave you the courage to run to our territory and cause trouble? Are you courting death?”

Hao Sha laughed with its squeaky voice and said, “I can go wherever I want. Who do you think you are? Do you think you can decide my actions?”

“Bastard. You dare talk like that to the Young Master? I will destroy you today!” But before Jia Ding Shan rushed over, he was stopped by Zhao Hai with a wave of his hand. Hao Sha also noticed this interaction, his expression couldn’t help but change.

He knew that Jia Ding Shan was one of the Kings of the Armored Races. He was quite famous in the Demon Realm. But since Jia Ding Shan doesn’t have his own family, he was only a Guest Elder to powers in the Demon Realm. In terms of identity, he was a bit worse than Hao Sha. However, when it came to strength, he was equal to Hao Sha.

Someone like Jia Ding Shan actually listened to Zhao Hai. It was clear that Jia Ding Shan wanted to fight, but he was stopped by Zhao Hai. Moreover, Jia Ding Shan wasn’t aggrieved at all. This caused Hao Sha to feel dread towards Zhao Hai.

Although Hao Sha was rampant in his words, he was also probing Zhao Hai. Now that he saw Jia Ding Shan’s conduct, his eyes couldn’t help but shrink. The danger he felt about Zhao Hai increased by multiple levels!

Chapter 1297: Ancient Demon Artifac

t

Zhao Hai looked at Hao Sha and then smiled, “Hao Sha, I’m really curious. What caused you to be this crazy? Are you that confident in your strength? To be honest, I want to make you submit. But now I changed my mind. Rather than making you my servant, I’d rather turn you into an Undead. Just like what I did to Hao Donglai.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Hao Sha’s expression turned into wild rage. His voice was now close to a shriek as he said, “So you’re the one who killed my grandson Donglai? Zhao Hai, I’ll kill you. I’ll kill everyone here!”

Zhao Hai looked at Hao Sha’s reaction and then coldly snorted and said, “You won’t have that opportunity. Jia Ding Shan, go on.”

Jia Ding Shan has been waiting for these words. Upon hearing Zhao Hai, he immediately charged forwards towards Hao Sha. Along the way, he also transformed into a giant pangolin.

Seeing Jia Ding Shan going towards him, Hao Sha would naturally retaliate. He transformed into a huge mouse and clashed with the pangolin.

It must be said that a battle between two Demons was much more ferocious compared to fights between other realms. This was because the Demons have much more formidable bodies. Most people would protect their bodies during fights while Demons just allowed their opponents to hit them. Because of this, their battles looked very brutal.

A Demon Mouse and a Demon Pangolin clashed a few times in the air. However, none managed to gain an advantage over the other. Jia Ding Shan had a few of his scales peeled out but Hao Sha also suffered some gashes on his skin.

Although the battle already looked brutal, this was just the two sides probing each other. They had yet to go all out. A large part of this was because Hao Sha was also paying attention to Zhao Hai.

The Toxic Sand Rat had never seen Zhao Hai attack, but he knew things about Jia Ding Shan. Also, he recognized Zhao Hai’s name. Zhao Hai was an ascender who currently doesn’t have power in the World of Cultivation. For Hao Donglai, it was unbelievable for Zhao Hai to be able to subdue Jia Ding Shan. But if Jia Ding Shan couldn’t be subdued, then he could only be killed in battle.

With these few clashes, Hao Sha was able to gauge Jia Ding Shan’s strength. The pangolin wasn’t any weaker than him, especially when it came to defense. In this case, if Zhao Hai can subdue him, then Zhao Hai should have enough strength to be considered as a threat.

Hao Sha was beginning to feel regret. If he just retreated, then it’s still possible for him to preserve his life. But now, it was already too late if he wanted to escape.

But at the same time, Hao Sha spoke his previous words because he was confident. This confidence stems from an ace that he has. And this ace was actually an artifact.

Demons barely used artifacts, but this didn’t mean that they didn’t use them. In fact, there are many Demons who use magic artifacts. After all, these artifacts could give them an advantage in battle. Moreover, as time passed, more and more Demons would use artifacts.

However, artifacts used by Demons weren’t the same as artifacts used by the Cultivators. The Cultivators had a lot of magic artifacts. They could use different artifacts according to the situation. However, the Demons don’t use this method. Most Demons don’t pay attention to quantity but to the quality of the artifact.

Although Demons couldn’t use these artifacts like life source weapons, they were very meticulous in choosing their artifacts. It can even be said that they were more picky than Cultivators.

The Demon Race’s techniques in refining artifacts might not be as good as the Cultivators, but their focus on the craft was much more intense. They would strive for perfection with each artifact they make.

Demons also use artifacts differently compared to Cultivators. Cultivators would generally use their magic artifacts all throughout the battle. On the other hand, Demons would treat their artifacts as hidden weapons. They would only use it when they’re sure that their enemy wouldn’t be able to escape the attack.

The artifact in Hao Sha’s hands was extraordinary. In his hands was a demon artifact. This demon artifact wasn’t something that he bought from a Demon. Instead, while he was exploring, he was able to discover a cave on a bleak planet. Inside this cave residence was a skeleton with the Demon Artifact.

Demon artifacts and magic artifacts were different. Although both were used to kill people, the refining of demon artifacts required sacrifices. There were even times where a demon artifact required numerous lives in order to be completed. It was also because of this refining method that demon artifacts had stronger attacks compared to magic artifacts.

But the demon artifact in Hao Sha’s hand was even stronger. It was an ancient demon artifact so it required a lot of energy in order to use it. Therefore, Hao Sha hadn’t been able to use it. However, even if he hadn’t been able to use it, Hao Sha was still very confident due to this artifact.

Ancient magic artifacts and ancient demon artifacts were very rare in the World of Cultivation. But each one of them contained tremendous power. Hao Sha tried to use his artifact before and was able to flatten a mountain in one shot, which showed it’s great power.

Hao Sha’s artifact looked quite unique. It looks somewhat like a crescent spade that Buddhists used. However, this spade had intense ghost qi around it. One could feel that it hadn’t been used in a good way.[1]

It was because of this artifact that Hao Sha had confidence even if he were to face two Nascent Soul Experts.

Naturally, Zhao Hai was unaware of this. However, he also didn’t treat the matter too lightly. Zhao Hai had met arrogant enemies before. Most of these arrogant people would have secret cards that they could play. Also, Zhao Hai would never lower his guard no matter who his enemy was.

After another few clashse, Zhao Hai began to frown when he saw that Jia Ding Shan and Hao Sha were still fighting. He knew that Hao Sha was on guard against him, and he was also aware that Hao Sha still had some cards he could play. Normally, people in Hao Sha’s position would find a way to escape. However, Hao Sha doesn’t have any intention of leaving. This showed that his card should be very powerful, or else he wouldn’t be this confident.

When Zhao Hai thought about this, he waved his hand and made a move. However, he didn’t enter the fight. He just took Liquid Silver and released several 1000-layer formations.

Although 10,000 layer formations were very strong, it was impossible for it to deal with a Nascent Soul Expert. Therefore, Zhao Hai used this approach to harass Hao Sha.

Hao Sha had been waiting for Zhao Hai to make a move. He wanted to see how strong Zhao Hai was in order to decide how to kill him. After all, he came here to avenge Hao Donglai.

Zhao Hai continually sent attacks over to Hao Sha. Although he didn’t injure Hao Sha, he was beginning to push him back. Hao Sha also knew that it was time to make a move. Zhao Hai’s magic was already beginning to make him lose.

With this thought in mind, Hao Sha’s eyes flashed a cold light. Then he called out as a jet black crescent moon spade appeared beside him. Then the weapon revolved around his body before attacking Zhao Hai.

Ghastly shrieks resounded as the crescent moon spade moved. The spade was divided into segments. The middle pole seems to be made out of bones. Both ends of the spade resembled fangs and a crescent moon – both ghastly in their own right. It looked terrifying.

The moment he saw the crescent moon spade, Zhao Hai immediately felt that something was different about it. This spade was giving him extremely dangerous vibes.

Zhao Hai’s expression sank. Then he thrust his staff outward. The magic staff’s aura increased instantaneously in preparation to meet the spade. Then Zhao Hai began to use Liquid Silver to release a 300,000-layer formation. This was the strongest formation that Zhao Hai could arrange.

This was the first time that Zhao Hai used Liquid Silver fully ever since it had been completed. Of the 300,000 magic formations in this formation set, a large majority of it comprises weapon shattering formations. The weapon shattering formations caused an exponential increase in the staff’s offensive strength.

‘Bang!’ A loud explosion was heard when the staff and the crescent moon spade hit each other. Liquid Silver was thrown back. Zhao Hai had also been shaken. Since the strength of the staff had been massively amplified, its rebound caused him to be shocked. Although Zhao Hai didn’t underestimate the crescent moon spade, he discovered that his estimates were still lacking. Just now, the collision between the two weapons caused a huge impact inside his mind. If it weren’t for his mind being stronger than normal, then he would have suffered a serious injury.

Zhao Hai was affected, and Hao Sha’s situation wasn’t any better. The crescent moon spade was knocked back, causing Hao Sha to feel that he had been hit by a thunderbolt. He vomited blood and his body couldn’t help but fall down. Jia Ding Shan didn’t miss this opportunity as he grabbed Hao Sha by the throat using his claws. However, Hao Sha didn’t make any resistance. The moment he fell down from the sky, he was already dead.

Zhao Hai calmly reclaimed Liquid Silver while waving his hand to retrieve the crescent moon spade. Even after going against the full strike of Liquid Silver, the crescent moon spade was still undamaged. This just showed how extraordinary it was.

As he sent a clump of dark fog towards Hao Shai to turn him into an Undead, he carefully inspected the crescent moon spade. The ghost qi of this spade was very dense, enough to cause anyone to be frightened. Surprisingly, the spade wasn’t very heavy. It felt like it wasn’t made out of metal. But if it was hit, it made a metallic sound. This caused Zhao Hai to be more curious about it.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and sent the crescent moon spade to Cai’er. It would be sent to the scanner and he would look at the results later.

Zhao Hai thought that since it was a powerful weapon, then it would certainly have an artifact spirit. But after he sent the weapon to the Space, he discovered that he was wrong. If there was an artifact spirit, then the Space should have issued a prompt. But now that there was no prompt, then this meant that the crescent moon spade doesn’t have an artifact spirit.

Such a powerful weapon unexpectedly doesn’t have an artifact spirit. This incurred Zhao Hai’s curiosity even more. He couldn’t wait to read the scanner’s results about the weapon.

Chapter 1298: Crescent Moon Spade

However, before Zhao Hai was able to get the results, the people in the camp welcomed them. It was Wu Yang who led everyone out. Wu Yang’s relationship with Zhao Hai was quite good, so he led the group.

Seeing him come, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then flew forward as well. The two opened their arms and hugged each other as they laughed.

After some time, the two let go of each other. Then one after another, those who knew Zhao Hai gave him a hug of gratitude. Zhao Hai could feel that they were very moved.

These people couldn’t do anything earlier since their strength wasn’t enough. However, they could clearly see that Hao Sha was a Nascent Soul Expert.

In the past, when Nascent Soul Experts attacked the Machine Field territory, the only way they could deal with them was with human wave attacks. There was nobody among them who could face a Nascent Soul Expert one-on-one and win. However, Zhao Hai actually achieved this. Although it wasn’t really a one-on-one, being able to kill the opposite party was still an extraordinary result.

After some time, Wu Yang looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, where’s Captain?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “He’s behind me. Their speed is slow, so when he discovered what was happening, he made me go first.”

Wu Yang nodded and said, “Fortunately, you returned on time. Otherwise, who knows how many people we’ll lose. Come with me, let’s greet the people from other forts who came to help.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then followed Wu Yang into the fort in order to meet the people from the other forts. And because Yuan had taken him to the other forts before, a lot of them already knew each other.

These people came to support them, so Wu Yang can’t just ask them to leave. Wu Yang invited them in and then prepared them something to eat. This was to thank them and also so that they could meet Yuan.

Although the Six Realms Battlefield was very dangerous, the resources sent here doesn’t need to be mentioned. The Machine Field was very willing to send the very best food and drinks here. Even if it cannot be compared to those eaten by the Great Families in the realm, it was far better than those eaten by most families.

While Wu Yang was very busy waiting on their reinforcements, Yuan and the others arrived. Wu Yang welcomed them happily. And without even waiting for Zhao Hai to talk, he retold the entire fight to them.

When Yuan heard that it was Hao Sha, he immediately understood why they were under attack. And after hearing that Zhao Hai killed him, he didn’t say anything. Zhao Hai’s approach was the same as Yuan’s. If it was him, then he’ll kill Hao Sha as well. Naturally, this was if he had the strength to do so.

Yuan didn’t talk about much with Zhao Hai and he just made Wu Yang prepare the food. At the same time, he arranged a place for Liu Zhen and his team to stay in. The fort wasn’t small, so there was enough room for everyone.

Although Liu Zhen had his area to defend, their actions weren’t restricted at all. Additionally, there were enough people left in the fort to defend. Therefore, it wouldn’t be a problem for them to stay in Yuan’s camp for several days.

Naturally, Liu Zhen decided to stay here and not leave because he wanted Zhao Hai to help them refine their weapons. But since there were so many people present, it wasn’t an appropriate time to bring the topic up.

Yuan proceeded to thank everyone who offered help and gave them a toast. Then after the celebration, everyone left. It was already dark and the team had been travelling for several days. Therefore, they went back to rest early. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai returned to the Space.

Cai’er just finished analyzing the crescent moon spade. However, the result was both very disappointing and very exciting for Zhao Hai. This was because it returned a prompt that he hadn’t heard from before, “The Host’s level is too low to comprehensively analyze the weapon. Only the method to use it can be given. Asking the Host to work harder.”

It’s been a long time since Zhao Hai heard this prompt. Currently, the Space’s level is 180. This wasn’t a very low level. And even in such a case, it was still not enough to analyze the weapon. This just shows how powerful the weapon was. In addition to his excitement, Zhao Hai was also somewhat worried.

He was happy because he gained a powerful weapon, but he also knew that there weren’t a lot of these kinds of items in the World of Cultivation. He didn’t even know where it came from.

The crescent moon spade, as well as the Six Realms Battlefield, told Zhao Hai that there was something more powerful than the World of Cultivation. They may be people who controlled the World of Cultivation the same way as Lu Wei was controlling the Divine Realm. If that was the case, then Zhao Hai was going to face more powerful enemies later.

Zhao Hai could now be considered as a Nascent Soul Expert in the World of Cultivation. And because of the Space, he was an invincible existence among the other Nascent Soul Experts. However, since he hadn’t met Transcending Tribulation Experts yet, he doesn’t know how strong they were.

However, Zhao Hai believed that every weapon made in the World of Cultivation could be analyzed by the Space. Even weapons made by the Great Sects would be the same.

Also, whether it was the Cultivation Realm’s magic artifacts or the Demon Realm’s demon artifacts, as long as he wanted to, he could check them online. Even those who had been lost could still be searched.

But in these databases, there was no mention about the crescent moon spade. This caused Zhao Hai to believe that the crescent moon spade was far greater than the artifacts of the World of Cultivation. This was because Zhao Hai was confident that no weapon used by a Nascent Soul Expert could face Liquid Silver’s full attack and remain unnscathed. The crescent moon spade remaining undamaged despite clashing with Liquid Silver only meant that it was very formidable.

All of this evidence showed that the crescent moon spade doesn’t belong to the World of Cultivation. With this thought in mind, Zhao Hai called over the Undead Hao Sha. Although Hao Sha has been turned into an undead, it was able to retain its original body. At this time, Hao Sha was in his humanoid form as he respectfully stood before Zhao Hai.

Jia Ding Shan followed Zhao Hai inside the Space and stood on the side. Since he has been subdued by the Space, then Zhao Hai doesn’t need to hide its existence from him. And since Jia Ding Shan lost a few scales in his battle with Hao Sha, Zhao Hai had to bring him into the Space to heal his wounds.

Laura and the others were currently sitting in the living room. But this time, they weren’t looking at the computer and were instead inspecting the crescent moon spade.

Although there was a dense amount of ghost qi around the crescent moon spade, Laura and the others weren’t afraid of it. Instead, they were very curious about the spade.

Zhao Hai looked at Hai Sha, then he pointed towards the crescent moon spade and said, “Hao Sha, where did you get this thing?”

Hao Sha immediately replied, “Answering the Young Master. I got this thing inside a cave residence on a deserted planet. Besides this weapon, there’s also a skeleton of a Cultivator inside that cave. From what I can see, the Cultivator might have been seriously injured and died.”

Zhao Hai gently knit his brows and said, “You couldn’t find the status of the Cultivator?”

Hao Sha shook his head and said, “I was unable to find out. The Cultivator had no identification in his body. He doesn’t even have his spatial equipment. Only the crescent moon spade was there. But the Cultivator was supposed to be wearing defensive robes. I found some fragments of the robe on his bones, but I don’t know what it was made from. The bones of the Cultivator were also very strange. Every inch of his bones was broken, it looked very horrible.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Then he thought deeply about the strangeness of the situation. This crescent moon spade was very formidable, Zhao Hai rarely found something more powerful. However, the owner of the crescent moon spade actually had every inch of his bones broken. What kind of attack did he experience? What was more terrifying was that despite every inch of his bones broken, the man was still able to escape to a planet before dying. The resilience of this person surpassed Zhao Hai’s imagination.

Zhao Hai believed that the owner of the crescent moon spade escaped to the planet on his own. Otherwise, his enemy wouldn’t have left the crescent moon spade alone. As for why the person didn’t have any spatial equipment, perhaps he could use space magic or perhaps his spatial item has been destroyed. All of these were possible.

With this thought in mind, Zhao Hai looked at Hao Sha and said, “Hao Sha, what did you do to that person’s skeleton? Can we still find it?” Zhao Hai wanted to see the man’s bones with his own eyes in order to learn more about him.

Hao Sha replied, “Replying to the Young Master. Because I took his weapon, I prepared a coffin for his skeleton. However, the moment I came in contact with the skeleton, it immediately turned into ash. The garments were also the same. I’m afraid the Young Master wouldn’t be able to see them anymore.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “This weapon is very strong. Why didn’t you use it in the beginning of the fight? If you did, then Jia Ding Shan would have been severely injured.”

Hao Sha replied, “With my present strength, I’m not able to control the weapon completely. Every time it was used, it would consume massive amounts of my energy. It would also cause damage to my mind, causing me to be weakened for a long time. And if I kept using it, my wounds would only get more and more severe.”

Zhao Hai nodded. At this time, he took the data from Cai’er. When he looked at how the weapon was used, Zhao Hai’s expression couldn’t help but stare. This weapon was more demanding than he thought. Moreover, the energy and spiritual force requirement of this weapon was very high. Even if Zhao Hai used this weapon, he wouldn’t be able to use it repeatedly – just like Hao Sha. But fortunately, Zhao Hai has Liquid Silver, so he has no need for the crescent moon spade.

After looking at the weapon, then he waved to Hao Sha to make him retreat before storing the crescent moon shovel. Then he turned to Jia Ding Shan and said, “Jia Ding Shan, you’ll be staying in Planet number 30 to teach some disciples.”

Chapter 1299: Plan for the Space’s Beasts

Planet Number 30 was a low-level Cultivation Background. There’s nothing inside it besides a large mansion. Zhao Hai made Jia Ding Shan live there in order to cultivate as well as teach the armored race inside the Space.

The armored race in the Space weren’t ordinary pangolins. As it turns out, the pangolins in the Space were the Dwarves’ iron armor beasts. Not only were their defenses very strong, they also have incomparably sharp front claws. When Jia Ding Shan has been subdued by the Space, his genes were extracted and injected into those iron armor beasts. This made the beasts more formidable.

After knowing about this, Zhao Hai thought that if the World of Cultivation could have a Monster Demon Race, then why can’t the Space? Therefore, he let Jia Ding Shan teach the iron armor beasts how to cultivate, then perhaps the Space would be able to produce a Demon Pangolin Clan.

Jia Ding Shan had a very few understanding about the Space. Although he doesn’t understand what Zhao Hai wanted to do, he didn’t ask and just complied. Zhao Hai had Cai’er send Jia Ding Shan to Planet Number 30 and then arranged some iron armor beasts for him.

When Jia Ding Shan saw Planet Number 30 as well as the iron armor beasts, he became happy. The spiritual density of Planet Number 30 was like a small spirit vein. Jia Ding Shan was a rogue cultivator and doesn’t have a family, he always took to heart the fact that he doesn’t have a successor.

One must know that inheritance was different for Cultivators and Demons. As long as one can practice, then anyone can become a disciple for a Cultivator. In this way, a sect can continue existing.

On the other hand, there were a lot of limitations for the Demon Race. The first issue was the race. There were many kinds of Demons and they all had specific cultivation methods. Take Hao Sha, for example. He’s from the Mouse Clan. His cultivation methods would only work for other Demon Mouse. It was impossible for him to teach those that weren’t from his race. Imagine, how could a Mouse teach a Cat how to cultivate? It was impossible no matter how you thought about it.

Besides the race, one should also take into account spiritual wisdom. If a Demon wanted to cultivate, then they would first need to develop spiritual wisdom. Otherwise, no amount of effort would work. Under such restrictions, finding a successor wouldn’t be very easy. Because of this, Demons pay more attention to their successors compared to other realms. It was also for this reason why Hao Sha was enraged upon knowing that Hao Donglai had been killed.

But for the pangolins in the Space, they didn’t have an appropriate cultivation method. Therefore, they couldn’t practice and only ponder on their own. This would certainly not yield any great results. One must know that the methods of the Demons were developed over many years. The beasts in the Space had just started, so it’s normal for them to not have any results.

As for the spiritual wisdom of the beasts in the Space, it was being controlled. For example, beasts in the Space used for consumption couldn’t have spiritual wisdom. Beasts that could have spiritual wisdom were those who could help Zhao Hai fight. After all, those with spiritual wisdom were more effective in combat compared to those who don’t.

And once beasts develop their spiritual wisdom, they can practice and would become a Demon. At this point, Zhao Hai hadn’t subdued a lot of Demons, and most of them were Undead. Naturally, because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t hold back and prepared some planets so that the Space’s beasts could be trained. The Undead Demons would be the ones teaching them.

It was almost daylight when everything had been arranged. Zhao Hai called Jia Ding Shan out again. When they head out this time, he would have Jia Ding Shan close up. This way, nobody would suspect him once he goes to the Space.

Even if Jia Ding Shan was left behind, Zhao Hai still had Hao Sha. Hao Sha’s fighting strength was on par with Jia Ding Shan. And now that Hao Sha has been turned into an Undead, his fighting strength had increased.

When Zhao Hai went out of his room, Yuan and the others had already gotten up. Jia Ding Shan was also standing outside his own room. This was something that Zhao Hai deliberately set up. Yuan also prepared a room for Jia Ding Shan to stay in. This way, when other people went out of their rooms, they would see that Jia Ding Shan wasn’t together with Zhao Hai.

When Zhao Hai came out of his room, Jia Ding Shan stepped forward and then gave Zhao Hai a bow as he said, “Young Master, I have a sudden feeling of enlightenment. I’m asking for your permission to allow me to close up.”

Naturally, this was Zhao Hai’s plan all along. So when he heard Jia Ding Shan, he pretended to frown as he said, “You want to close up?” At this time, Yuan and the others went closer. It’s clear that they heard Jia Ding Shan.

Yuan laughed and said, “It’s no big deal. If he wants to close up, then he can close up. Our Lock Mountain Range has places for these kinds of things. Let me send a request so that Jia Ding Shan can go there.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, you can listen to Captain.” Jia Ding Shan expressed his gratitude towards Yuan. Then everyone went to the dining room to eat.

After their meal, Yuan led Jia Ding Shan to the place where he can close up. Once Jia Ding Shan entered, the entire place was sealed. Yuan was also aware that people from the other realms can survive without food for a very long time, so he didn’t bother preparing any for Jia Ding Shan.

After sending Jia Ding Shan away, Yuan and the others went to the fort’s training grounds in order to divide the spoils. The spoils included artifacts as well as Demon corpses. The Demon corpses were those who followed Jia Ding Shan. Since they weren’t that strong, Zhao Hai didn’t bother making them into Undead and just handed them over to Yuan to become loot.

But now, because of his earlier plans, Zhao Hai wanted to turn these Demons into Undead. This way, he could have more beasts in the Space cultivating.

However, since he already told Yuan that he didn’t want these corpses, Zhao Hai naturally wouldn’t go back on his word. And even if he could ask for these Demon corpses when he refined their weapons later on, Zhao Hai still wouldn’t do it. In the end, he decided that he couldn’t ruin the impression these people have of him just for a few Undead. In any case, he could just return to the soft gold mine in order to hunt more Demons.

After taking out the spoils, Yuan looked at the pile before turning to everyone and saying, “These are all of our spoils. How do you think we should split it?”

Nobody spoke for some time. But it was clear that they were incredibly excited. In the past, the person with the most contributions would be able to choose first and then the Demon corpses would be transformed into contribution points which everyone would divide.

But this time, everyone knew that most of the contribution was held by Zhao Hai. Without Zhao Hai, then they wouldn’t have gotten these spoils. Therefore, nobody was able to say anything.

Yuan looked at everyone and then smiled as he said, “Brothers, I have an idea. To tell you the truth, these artifacts are relatively useless to us. So we might as well give all of them to Little Hai. We’ve already confirmed that his refining is very good. He can reuse the artifacts and use it as raw materials for our weapons. With this, we can save the trouble of looking for raw materials ourselves. What do you think?”

Upon hearing Yuan, everyone looked at him strangely. These people knew that although what Yuan said was reasonable, this wasn’t the real case.

Weapon refining of the World of Cultivation was unusual. There were plenty of weapons made with different styles of refining. The Machine Field currently doesn’t have any means to reuse these materials. And if the process went wrong, then these artifacts would be destroyed and then turned into scrap. Such matters were incredibly common in the Machine Field. Yuan’s words pushed all of the benefits towards Zhao Hai, this was the reason why everyone felt strange.

Zhao Hai also gawked when he heard Yuan. He looked at Yuan and knew that Yuan wanted to give the weapons to him. But to say that Yuan wouldn’t provide him with raw materials was impossible. Yuan just relayed that these weapons weren’t useful to them, so they might as well give it to Zhao Hai.

Then after a moment, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “If fellow brothers don’t have any problems, then I’ll receive these and you won’t need to prepare any materials when I refine your weapons.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Yuan gawked, then he quickly said, “Little Hai, don’t misunderstand. We’ll give these artifacts to you in hopes that you can make use of them. If they turn to scrap, then it’s fine as well. We’ll still be providing you with materials regardless. We wouldn’t make you suffer a loss.” Yuan was truly afraid that Zhao Hai had misunderstood him for wanting to profit off of the situation. Therefore, Yuan hastily explained.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Captain, I’m not kidding. If you give me these artifacts, then I can deconstruct them into useful materials. And even if I were to add more materials, it wouldn’t be that expensive for me. Moreover, I killed Hao Sha yesterday and turned him into my Undead. In fact, I’ve taken benefits away from you all. So you can let this be my contribution.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Yuan’s eyes shone as he said, “Little Hai, are you really confident about recycling these artifacts? Even if they’re high-quality?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “As long as you bring them to me, I can deconstruct them.”

Yuan laughed and said, “Alright, fantastic, then that’s settled. I also have some artifacts on hand from previous events. I’m unable to use them so I’ll hand them over to you. As long as you prepare me a good weapon, then I don’t care what you do with them.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That won’t be a problem. You can rest assured.”

After he said this, Zhao Hai was approached by the others. Besides newcomers, everyone in the Six Realms Battlefield had advanced-level goods in their hands. Since these artifacts were high-level, the materials used to make them were high-quality as well. Since the success rate of recycling these artifacts was very low, they didn’t dare try it. Now, upon hearing that Zhao Hai was confident in his ability, they would naturally hand these goods over to him. If they could trade these artifacts for 1 or 2 good weapons that they could use, then it would be worth it.

Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t decline. This wouldn’t be a hassle for him and he could also gain some advantages. At the very least, the Space would obtain more types of materials. As for the others, they would be able to get rid of things they can’t use. So it was a win-win situation for everyone.

Seeing Zhao Hai accept their artifacts, more people handed their artifacts over. Naturally, Zhao Hai accepted everything. At this point, the only thing left to be divided were the corpses.

Yuan looked at the corpses and said, “We’ve processed these things before. It’s useless if we keep them here, so let’s sell them to the Machine Field and turn them into contribution points.”

At this moment, the nearby Liu Zhen shook his head and said, “Also, don’t forget that we need to pay Little Hai. So let’s just give them all to him. It’s the least we can do for his efforts.”

The others didn’t speak, but a lot of them nodded. The most important thing for them was a good weapon. They could just earn contribution points later on. Compared to contribution points, a good weapon from Zhao Hai was the biggest priority.

But this time, Zhao Hai actually waved his hand and said, “No need. To be honest, the artifacts that everyone will hand over to me can make me a lot of money. So I won’t be greedy and ask for the corpses as well. They should be exchanged for contribution points for everyone. No matter what, we can’t make everyone work for free.”

Seeing that Zhao Hai doesn’t want the corpses, Yuan nodded and said, “Alright, then let’s go with what Little Hai said. By the way, everyone should head back and get the artifacts that you don’t need. Otherwise, don’t blame me if Little Hai tampers with your weapons.” Everyone laughed at Yuan’s joke. They experienced life threatening events together, so they wouldn’t mind these kinds of jokes. Then everyone headed back to their rooms in high spirits.

After Yuan took the Demon corpses, he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, do you need me to prepare you a room for crafting?”

Zhao Hai initially thought that he would decline, but since he was heading back to the Space, then he would need a place where he wouldn’t be disturbed. Therefore, he nodded and said, “Captain, prepare a place for me where I won’t be disturbed. It would be best if this place is a little bigger. Also, when everyone returns, please have them write down their requirements for their weapons. I’ll keep an Undead outside and have it receive their requirements.”

Yuan nodded and said, “Alright. That’s not a problem. Wait for me here, I’ll be back right away.” Zhao Hai nodded, then Yuan flew towards his own room.